[
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bad or hurting others",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "afraid",
      "clever",
      "cruel",
      "hunt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "at last or at the end",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "angry",
      "clever",
      "finally",
      "reply"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to try to fight or hurt",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "attack",
      "middle",
      "pleased",
      "trick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to not let others see",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "agree",
      "hide",
      "safe",
      "well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the lowest part",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "bottom",
      "lot",
      "moment",
      "promise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "angry",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "happy",
      "low",
      "mad",
      "scared"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "moment",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a hole with water in it",
      "a short time",
      "at the center",
      "at the end"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "promise",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to say \u201cgood job\u201d",
      "to say \u201cI will\u201d",
      "to say \u201cthe end\u201d",
      "to say \u201cmaybe\u201d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reply",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to answer",
      "to get to a place",
      "to look for in order to kill",
      "to try to fight or hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "safe",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "fool",
      "having much or many",
      "not seen",
      "not worried about begin hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A clever person can solve a puzzle easily.",
      "When a plane arrives, it leaves the ground and goes into the sky."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "At noon, the sun is near the bottom of the sky.",
      "If I break my brother\u2019s bike, he will be angry."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is easy to hide in a dark place.",
      "Many kinds of fish are afraid of water."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "At night, your parents may say, \u201cHide your eyes and go to sleep.\u201d",
      "Heavy things will go down to the bottom of the ocean."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is cruel to keep a dog in a small cage all day.",
      "Your mother will be angry when you get good grades in school."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Animals cannot hunt because they do not have hands.",
      "It is a good idea to arrive early for class."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "People sometimes attack pictures to email messages.",
      "Some people are afraid of spiders."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A moment is like a second or two.",
      "New shoes are usually not very comfortable or clever."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Small animals do not usually attack big animals.",
      "There are twelve moments in a year."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A cruel person will try to help others at all times.",
      "You can use a gun to hunt in the forest."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "laboratory",
      "experiment",
      "shout",
      "smell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "shout",
      "carefully",
      "create",
      "laugh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "nervous",
      "terrible",
      "approach",
      "worse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "chemical",
      "secret",
      "loud",
      "noise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "nervous",
      "adventure",
      "project",
      "scare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "William wanted to make a new thing.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "create",
    "pre": "cre",
    "post": "ate"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I\u2019m not having fun, so let\u2019s go on an exciting trip.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "adventure",
    "pre": "adven",
    "post": "ture"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Mrs. O\u2019Malley asked me to get close to the desk and write my name.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "approach",
    "pre": "app",
    "post": "roach"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Don\u2019t worry. I won\u2019t tell anyone your thing that other people don\u2019t know.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "secret",
    "pre": "se",
    "post": "cret"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I have to finish my special job before I can go home.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "project",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "roject"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When the jar hit the floor, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "it made a very loud sound",
      "it shouted on the ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When the sun went down, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "it was scared",
      "the woods looked evil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "To test his idea, the scientist __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "went on an adventure",
      "did an experiment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Your phone will not work __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "someone kills the window",
      "if you don\u2019t carefully pay attention to your power supply"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The dog seemed unhappy when __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I approached it",
      "it created me"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Alex likes his class because he gets to __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "do fun projects",
      "be a laboratory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is wrong with your hair? __________!",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is a chemical",
      "It looks terrible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She\u2019s quite funny. We always __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "laugh at her jokes",
      "don\u2019t tell me your secret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Did you hear that? __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I just made it worse",
      "There was a noise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I have a very important test tomorrow. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I am nervous",
      "I will smell it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "friendly",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "space",
      "a list of information",
      "acting or behaving nicely",
      "a picture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "grade",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a score or mark on someone\u2019s work",
      "a small copy of something larger",
      "where you go to read books",
      "a paper written for school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "view",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to find an answer",
      "to not succeed in what you try to do",
      "to guess",
      "to look at something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ever",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "quickly and unexpectantly",
      "at anytime",
      "all around you",
      "to do the first thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "library",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "space and things in space",
      "from a different world",
      "a place where books are",
      "a round thing in space"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "report",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "many of something",
      "a round thing",
      "drops of water in the sky",
      "a paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "alien",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "something written for school",
      "a creature from a different world",
      "in place of",
      "a small copy of something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "chart",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a paper",
      "a copy",
      "a group",
      "a list"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "among",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "in the middle of something",
      "a score or mark",
      "at anytime",
      "to understand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "solve",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to guess",
      "to look at something",
      "to find an answer",
      "to not succeed in what you try to do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "everything that exists in space",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "universe",
      "instead",
      "suddenly",
      "view"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not an exact amount but less than many",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "ever",
      "among",
      "several",
      "solve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a creature from a different world",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "report",
      "alien",
      "chart",
      "among"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "in place of",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "solve",
      "suppose",
      "fail",
      "instead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to guess",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "fail",
      "suppose",
      "view",
      "comprehend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "What would be the most awesome gift you\u2019ve __________ received?__________ your home to me.",
    "options": [
      "ever",
      "describe"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ever",
      "describe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "This __________ tells what time the TV shows will play.I saw a movie about __________ from another planet.",
    "options": [
      "alien(s)",
      "chart"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "chart",
      "aliens"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I think the most interesting __________ is Saturn.I wonder how the __________ is Saturn.",
    "options": [
      "planet",
      "universe"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "planet",
      "universe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Do you like to __________ hard math problems?If I do not know the answers, I will __________ the test.",
    "options": [
      "fail",
      "solve"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "solve",
      "fail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "__________ days ago, I lost my backpack.The girls in my class like to __________ pictures of pop stars.",
    "options": [
      "several\/view"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "Several",
      "view"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The story about the police dog got to many people in town.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "spread",
    "pre": "spr",
    "post": "ead"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I was happy to sit and listen to music all night.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "content",
    "pre": "con",
    "post": "tent"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The house will move back and forth if a strong wind blows. sh_ _ _",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "shake",
    "pre": "sh",
    "post": "ake"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I waited for the monster to come out of the cave. ex_ _ _ _ _ _",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "expected",
    "pre": "ex",
    "post": "pected"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I didn\u2019t want to talk to my sister, so I staved away from her.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "avoided",
    "pre": "av",
    "post": "oided"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Before Kimberly sang, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the teacher reminded everyone to behave",
      "she instructed the people to go to sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When we heard the loud sound, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I turned around out of habit",
      "there was none left"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The man told us to be quiet, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "so I decided to stroll through town",
      "so I knew it was not appropriate to talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "They asked us to wait, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "so I felt concerned about them",
      "so I had to be patient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I met a new friend yesterday, and __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "frequently I would sit and read",
      "I shook his hand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The girl\u2019s positive words made me feel better.",
      "We took the village out of the house."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The calm girl yelled a lot.",
      "The team members asked Kate to represent them at the dinner."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I was content to stay at home by the warm fire.",
      "My mom punished me for doing my homework."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The man expected me to say yes.",
      "The issue did not taste very good."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I behaved wisely while I was asleep.",
      "I avoided my friend because she had laughed at me."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "At first I was nervous, but then I started to feel calm.",
      "The angry bear looked content."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "When my dog died, it made me feel positive.",
      "Few people live in the village."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I wanted to avoid food, so I bought a sandwich.",
      "The class needed to talk about the issue."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The students behaved quite well for their new teacher.",
      "Students are expected to be late to class."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I was punished because I broke the window.",
      "The man represented the award to the girl."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "roll",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to rest",
      "a rule",
      "to grow",
      "to move by turning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "error",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a nice man",
      "very old",
      "something you do wrong",
      "open land"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hurt",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to disagree",
      "how much something costs",
      "from nature",
      "to do something that causes pain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reside",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to relax",
      "to live in a place for long",
      "something that can be seen",
      "to know about something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "relax",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to keep going",
      "a large group of people",
      "to rest",
      "to move"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "continue",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to be in the right place",
      "to stay",
      "to have",
      "to keep doing something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "normal",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "the perfect amount",
      "friendly",
      "not strange",
      "different"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rare",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "quiet",
      "not full",
      "interesting",
      "not seen often"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "visible",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "from nature",
      "easy to see",
      "new",
      "normal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "field",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "open land",
      "to reside",
      "a thing",
      "a tool"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "in a severe or harmful way",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "continue",
      "wild",
      "judgment",
      "badly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the ability to form opinions or decisions",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "experience",
      "reside",
      "judgment",
      "result"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to fit or be in the right place",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "roll",
      "relax",
      "continue",
      "belong"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not strange or different",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "normal",
      "visible",
      "uncommon",
      "aware"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to do something that makes you feel pain",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "rare",
      "hurt",
      "error",
      "since"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My day at school was ",
    "underlined": "not strange",
    "correct": "normal",
    "pre": "nor",
    "post": "mal"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The bird was ",
    "underlined": "from nature",
    "correct": "wild",
    "pre": "wi",
    "post": "ld"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Sorry I can\u2019t come; I\u2019m ",
    "underlined": "feeling discomfort in my body",
    "correct": "hurt",
    "pre": "h",
    "post": "urt"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He\u2019s going to ",
    "underlined": "rest ",
    "correct": "relax",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "elax"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The man walked through a ",
    "underlined": "large area of land",
    "correct": "field",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "ield"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Sam was happy to ",
    "underlined": "go back",
    "correct": "return",
    "pre": "re",
    "post": "turn"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Her grandfather is a ",
    "underlined": "smart",
    "correct": "wise",
    "pre": "wi",
    "post": "se"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "William wanted an ",
    "underlined": "animal",
    "correct": "pet",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "et"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He studies ",
    "underlined": "what the condition of the air is like",
    "correct": "weather",
    "pre": "we",
    "post": "ather"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I have to ",
    "underlined": "deal with",
    "correct": "face",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "ace"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ lives in the old house.A scary place might cause __________.",
    "options": [
      "fright\/ghost"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ghost",
      "fright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The tree fell down because it was __________.I was __________ when I got a bad grade on the test.",
    "options": [
      "dead",
      "upset"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "dead",
      "upset"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After 10 hours of driving, I finally __________ California.He is smart and has a(n)__________ in class.",
    "options": [
      "advantage",
      "reached"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "reached",
      "advantage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He wanted to __________ from the room.He lived a long __________ from the school.",
    "options": [
      "escape",
      "distance"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "escape",
      "distance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man is a nice __________.The town is a small __________.",
    "options": [
      "community",
      "individual"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "individual",
      "community"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "It rained for two days, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "and caused the river to rise",
      "it was dead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "As I was walking home from school today, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I was a ghost",
      "I hardly noticed that a dog was following me"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "After my vacation, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I returned to work",
      "I was an advantage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Many people like him __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "because they make him upset",
      "because he is a wise man"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "They are afraid of the king because __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "he has too much power",
      "he has a quiet voice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I love my dog. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He\u2019s my favorite pet",
      "He causes fright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I like living here because __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I make many choices",
      "it is a nice community"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I want to live in Hawaii because __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "it has good weather",
      "smoking causes lung cancer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The storm was very bad, but __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "all of the people survived",
      "it went a very long distance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "We closed the door, but __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the dog escaped",
      "it was an individual"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something difficult that you have to do",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "condition",
      "sense",
      "challenge",
      "divide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the son of a king",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "prince",
      "expert",
      "famous",
      "force"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to do something to help succeed",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "contribute",
      "sudden",
      "harm",
      "peace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "for this reason",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "allow",
      "therefore",
      "announce",
      "beside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to stop someone from getting hurt",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "claim",
      "protect",
      "lay",
      "difference"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Sarah ",
    "underlined": "let ",
    "correct": "allowed",
    "pre": "allo",
    "post": "wed"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The child promised not to ",
    "underlined": "hurt ",
    "correct": "harm",
    "pre": "har",
    "post": "m"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "She was a ",
    "underlined": "well-known",
    "correct": "famous",
    "pre": "fam",
    "post": "ous"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "You should ",
    "underlined": "say it\u2019s true",
    "correct": "claim",
    "pre": "cl",
    "post": "aim"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The food was ",
    "underlined": "cut into smaller parts",
    "correct": "divided",
    "pre": "d",
    "post": "ivie"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "It wasn\u2019t right for the coach __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to make the race such a challenge",
      "to allow me to play"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "My sister and I were fighting. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "We announced the winners",
      "My sister claimed she didn\u2019t like me"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Everyone knew her __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "because I stood beside her",
      "because she was famous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The man would not buy the bike __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "because of his difference",
      "because of its bad condition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "No one could win against Sally __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "because she was an expert",
      "because she never used force"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "We were scared because the dog __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "might harm us",
      "might bring us peace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The police wanted __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to protect us from danger",
      "to not make any sense"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "You are too sick to play outside. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Don\u2019t lay your feet on the table",
      "Therefore, play inside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She was surprised by __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "the expected amount contributed by the animals",
      "the sudden noise outside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Please be fair __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "when you meet the prince",
      "when you divide the land"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "She looks ",
    "underlined": "like someone that I know well",
    "correct": "familiar",
    "pre": "fami",
    "post": "liar"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Drinking water is something ",
    "underlined": "that she must do",
    "correct": "necessary",
    "pre": "nece",
    "post": "ssary"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He has an ",
    "underlined": "idea",
    "correct": "theory",
    "pre": "the",
    "post": "ory"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "reason that 1 am doing this",
    "correct": "purpose",
    "pre": "pur",
    "post": "pose"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My teacher will ",
    "underlined": "make me want",
    "correct": "encourage",
    "pre": "enc",
    "post": "ourage"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I ",
    "underlined": "agree with",
    "correct": "accept",
    "pre": "ac",
    "post": "cept"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "It is difficult to ",
    "underlined": "keep from falling",
    "correct": "balance",
    "pre": "ba",
    "post": "lance"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Her ",
    "underlined": "routine",
    "correct": "pattern",
    "pre": "pa",
    "post": "ttern"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "There is a ",
    "underlined": "big difference",
    "correct": "contrast",
    "pre": "c",
    "post": "ontrast"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The Earth has a ",
    "underlined": "solitary",
    "correct": "single",
    "pre": "s",
    "post": "ingle"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "used when something must be done",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "propose",
      "hang",
      "require",
      "tear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to stop something from falling down",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "balance",
      "arrange",
      "attend",
      "release"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a way that something is very different",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "grab",
      "success",
      "accept",
      "contrast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an idea about something",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "theory",
      "familiar",
      "necessary",
      "encourage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the only one",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "pattern",
      "single",
      "huge",
      "attend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "It started to rain, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "it hung on the wall",
      "so I grabbed my umbrella"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When she heard I was leaving, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "she proposed a party",
      "she had huge fun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Don\u2019t pull on my shirt, or __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "you might tear it",
      "you might arrange it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you try hard, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "you can attend many things",
      "you will have success"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When I catch fish, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I usually release them back into the water",
      "they require a good dinner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wave",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to pass from physical life",
      "salt water that surrounds land",
      "a raised line of water",
      "land in the middle of water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "taste",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to hurt",
      "to find",
      "flavor",
      "to walk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "against",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to be touching something",
      "to stop from happening",
      "maybe",
      "enjoyable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rock",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "feelings",
      "a place by the ocean",
      "honest",
      "a hard thing in the ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "throw",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to name something",
      "to put something into the air",
      "to make something work",
      "to stop something from being hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "island",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "land",
      "salt water",
      "feelings",
      "hard thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "discover",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to be nice",
      "to find something",
      "to stop",
      "to name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "step",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to keep from harm",
      "to be next to",
      "to walk",
      "to hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "beach",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "water that comes on land",
      "a sandy or rocky place by the ocean",
      "the flavor of something",
      "something could happen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fix",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to make something work",
      "to pass from physical life",
      "to be honest",
      "to make something move in the air"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to be touching something",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "beach",
      "against",
      "discover",
      "wave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to break something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "identify",
      "maybe",
      "damage",
      "ocean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a way that you feel",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "prevent",
      "emotion",
      "rock",
      "pleasant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very honest",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "still",
      "step",
      "throw",
      "frank"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "land in the middle of water",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "save",
      "taste",
      "island",
      "fix"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I like to play on the __________.The big __________ pushed the swimmer back.",
    "options": [
      "wave",
      "beach"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "beach",
      "wave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "They walked across the __________ to find food.I am scared of some animals that live in the __________.",
    "options": [
      "ocean",
      "island"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "island",
      "ocean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My dad knows how to __________ cars.If you __________ the light, we won\u2019t be able to see at night.",
    "options": [
      "fix",
      "damage"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fix",
      "damage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We have to go around that large __________.We are __________ planning to go to Florida this winter.",
    "options": [
      "still",
      "rock"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rock",
      "still"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Do you know how to __________ a football?Please __________ into the house.",
    "options": [
      "step",
      "throw"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "throw",
      "step"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "It is ",
    "underlined": "very important",
    "correct": "essential",
    "pre": "essen",
    "post": "tial"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "good thing",
    "correct": "benefit",
    "pre": "bene",
    "post": "fit"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I have ",
    "underlined": "problems",
    "correct": "trouble",
    "pre": "tro",
    "post": "uble"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I am ",
    "underlined": "sure",
    "correct": "certain",
    "pre": "cer",
    "post": "tain"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "job",
    "correct": "function",
    "pre": "fun",
    "post": "ction"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "That is the ",
    "underlined": "place",
    "correct": "site",
    "pre": "si",
    "post": "te"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I saw his ",
    "underlined": "picture",
    "correct": "image",
    "pre": "i",
    "post": "mage"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The twins don\u2019t like to be ",
    "underlined": "apart",
    "correct": "separate",
    "pre": "s",
    "post": "eparate"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I like to ",
    "underlined": "stay",
    "correct": "remain",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "emain"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "His ",
    "underlined": "part that comes out of his rear",
    "correct": "tail",
    "pre": "t",
    "post": "ail"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of the rain was slippery roads.The __________ of waking up early is being at work on time.",
    "options": [
      "effect",
      "benefit"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "effect",
      "benefit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She had to make a(an)__________ phone call.The __________ cause of my problems is laziness.",
    "options": [
      "primary",
      "immediate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "immediate",
      "primary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He was __________ when he got the best score.We __________ under the shade of a tree.",
    "options": [
      "rested",
      "proud"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "proud",
      "rested"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Her new school is __________ from here.She and her best friend hate to be in __________ classrooms.",
    "options": [
      "far",
      "separate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "far",
      "separate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I have to __________ my money from my little brother.I have to __________ in school for four more years.",
    "options": [
      "guard",
      "remain"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "guard",
      "remain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Every year for my birthday, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I return to the site of my birth",
      "my cat has a short tail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I believe her __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "because she has a chance to lie",
      "because she\u2019s certain of the facts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "My new watch is great. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It has many functions",
      "It causes me trouble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I was afraid __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "because I thought of a scary image of a snake",
      "because I didn\u2019t focus on my work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I eat many fruits __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "because they are essential for good health",
      "because they taste like grass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to marry",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "collect",
      "wed",
      "prepare",
      "introduce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a living thing",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "conversation",
      "truth",
      "creature",
      "decision"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to move a boat across the water",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "spend",
      "berry",
      "forest",
      "sail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "one thing orthe other",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "asleep",
      "compete",
      "either",
      "serious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "any longer",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "ground",
      "strange",
      "wake",
      "anymore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The doll broke when it fell onto the ",
    "underlined": "floor",
    "correct": "ground",
    "pre": "gr",
    "post": "ound"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I like to ",
    "underlined": "use my time",
    "correct": "spend time",
    "pre": "sp",
    "post": "end time"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He loved to ",
    "underlined": "travel in his boat",
    "correct": "sail",
    "pre": "sa",
    "post": "il"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I ",
    "underlined": "stop sleeping",
    "correct": "wake",
    "pre": "w",
    "post": "ake"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "area",
    "correct": "forest",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "orest"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person who paints, draws, or sculpts",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "magazine",
      "article",
      "artist",
      "alone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to decide that something is good or bad",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "neighbor",
      "judge",
      "meal",
      "compare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a way of doing something",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "method",
      "profit",
      "professional",
      "attitude"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "how good something is",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "apartment",
      "thin",
      "quality",
      "stairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something used to make other things",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "shape",
      "symbol",
      "material",
      "space"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like the ",
    "underlined": "person who lives near me",
    "correct": "neighbor",
    "pre": "neigh",
    "post": "bor"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I read a ",
    "underlined": "regular publication",
    "correct": "magazine",
    "pre": "maga",
    "post": "zine"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The doctor gave his ",
    "underlined": "expert and qualified",
    "correct": "professional",
    "pre": "profe",
    "post": "ssional"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He ",
    "underlined": "looked at the differences between",
    "correct": "compared",
    "pre": "co",
    "post": "mpared"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "She has a good ",
    "underlined": "way of thinking about things",
    "correct": "attitude",
    "pre": "a",
    "post": "ttitude"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "When you are alone, you are with another person.",
      "You can read articles in a newspaper."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you make a profit, you have more money than you did before",
      "If you have professional training, you can\u2019t do a difficult job."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The Earth is a very thin planet.",
      "If something is a symbol, it stands for something else."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You can use stairs to go up inside a building.",
      "Since she is a lawyer, people call my wife an artist."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "There are many apartments in one building.",
      "Your attitude is the way you look."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "You cannot get information from a magazine.",
      "If you compare two things, you say how they are different."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you judge something, you know if it is good or bad.",
      "Neighbors are people who live far from you."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A meal has food and a drink.",
      "A shape is something you cannot see."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A symbol is a picture of two different things.",
      "You must have space to add more things to a room."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If something has low quality, it is very good.",
      "A material is used to make something else."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the liquid in your body",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "spot",
      "blood",
      "cell",
      "owe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to set on fire",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "burn",
      "increase",
      "feed",
      "contain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "doing what you should do",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "demand",
      "raise",
      "position",
      "responsible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the same as something else",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hole",
      "structure",
      "lord",
      "equal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something interesting to see",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "sight",
      "correct",
      "whole",
      "crop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What did your father demand?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "He is not nice.",
      "That I clean my room."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Will you help me raise this?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes. How high?",
      "Yes, it goes lower."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What position were these in?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "They were next to each other.",
      "They came from the store."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Does that bottle contain water?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Yes. What is inside it?",
      "No, it has milk in it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Did you hear that Jim\u2019s house burned down?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "That is terrible!",
      "Is it bigger now?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The bad guy sat on the floor of his __________.Dad says the old __________ is not safe.",
    "options": [
      "structure",
      "cell"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cell",
      "structure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ ruled over 100 people in the town.I still __________ the bank money for my university loan.",
    "options": [
      "lord",
      "owe"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lord",
      "owe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Won\u2019t your legs hurt if you stay in that __________ for long?This is our favorite picnic __________.",
    "options": [
      "spot",
      "position"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "position",
      "spot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ class was excited.I dug a __________ to put a tree in.",
    "options": [
      "whole",
      "hole"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "whole",
      "hole"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Do not __________ any of the animals at the zoo.The farmer grew a __________ of potatoes.",
    "options": [
      "crop",
      "feed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "feed",
      "crop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He got a low score on the science ",
    "underlined": "test",
    "correct": "exam",
    "pre": "ex",
    "post": "am"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The evening was ",
    "underlined": "filled with special things that made it different",
    "correct": "magical",
    "pre": "ma",
    "post": "gical"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He loves to have the best ",
    "underlined": "things that are new to the world",
    "correct": "technology",
    "pre": "tech",
    "post": "nology"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I only read the ",
    "underlined": "plan for the story",
    "correct": "outline",
    "pre": "ou",
    "post": "tline"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The writer is good at making ",
    "underlined": "sentences about what someone looks like",
    "correct": "descriptions",
    "pre": "de",
    "post": "scriptions"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Have you been to the local cinema?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes, I went there yesterday.",
      "No, it is in the other city."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Will you go to the store?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "No, I saw it yesterday.",
      "Yes, I need a new hat."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Do you like the new coach?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes, he\u2019s very nice.",
      "No, it is too expensive."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What was your favorite scene?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I didn\u2019t like any of them.",
      "I bought it last week."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Did you buy the novel?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Yes, he was very nice.",
      "No, someone gave it to me."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I like to read,__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "so I buy many novels",
      "so I am a poet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He doesn\u2019t always use the best judgment,__________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "she suffers a lot",
      "so he makes some silly mistakes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He has many computers.__________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They are on sheets",
      "He loves technology"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I don\u2019t play on the soccer team__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "because I don\u2019t like the coach",
      "because the outline is too long"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She likes her teacher.__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He uses helpful examples",
      "He writes a lot of mail in class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The movie was too boring.__________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They shouldn\u2019t have printed it",
      "It needed more exciting scenes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "My dog won\u2019t bite you._________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I can control it",
      "He is doing an exam"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I need to buy some food, so_________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I\u2019m going to the store",
      "I am over the limit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She doesn\u2019t like that book because_________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "she has a local book",
      "the examples are not clear enough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When he travels,__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "he always takes a direct flight",
      "he gives a description of airplanes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something of value that is given to the winner",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "opportunity",
      "prize",
      "risk",
      "happen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lucky",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "extreme",
      "across",
      "fortunate",
      "yet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to eat",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "consume",
      "breathe",
      "realize",
      "observe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the feeling of being afraid",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "length",
      "fear",
      "happen",
      "characteristic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to do by chance",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "respond",
      "realize",
      "excite",
      "happen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "how long something is",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "length",
      "characteristic",
      "wonder",
      "mistake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to let air in and out of your body",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "observe",
      "breathe",
      "consume",
      "excite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something you did wrong",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "happen",
      "fear",
      "mistake",
      "risk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "up to this point",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "extreme",
      "length",
      "across",
      "yet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to understand",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "realize",
      "breathe",
      "respond",
      "observe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I had to walk ",
    "underlined": "to the other side of",
    "correct": "across",
    "pre": "acr",
    "post": "oss"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Brad chose not to ",
    "underlined": "give an answer",
    "correct": "respond",
    "pre": "resp",
    "post": "ond"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Sarah ran around the park to get ready for the ",
    "underlined": "contest where people run against each other",
    "correct": "race",
    "pre": "ra",
    "post": "ce"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Michael ",
    "underlined": "saw",
    "correct": "observed",
    "pre": "obs",
    "post": "erved"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Renee knew there was a ",
    "underlined": "chance of something bad happening",
    "correct": "risk",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "isk"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Being tall is a characteristic of many trees.",
      "I was fortunate because I received some useless gifts."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Because he left work early, Carl had an opportunity to go to the concert.",
      "I could feel the length of the air outside."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Angela felt fear when she got a good grade on her test.",
      "Our team won. We were fortunate."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Jeremy thought his hair was just the right length.",
      "Michelle left her characteristic at my house."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Theresa found an opportunity on the ground outside.",
      "Billy feels fear when he has to talk in front of people."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "exist",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "the first one",
      "to print a book",
      "to be real",
      "something to help you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "clue",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "hint",
      "steps",
      "heavy",
      "wood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "maybe",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "where you see shows",
      "possible or likely to be true",
      "where classes are held",
      "where you hear music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hidden",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "one hundred years",
      "level with no curves",
      "a nice man",
      "not able to be seen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wealth",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "old",
      "leader",
      "money",
      "season"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pound",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to hit hard many times",
      "the steps you take",
      "metal used in money",
      "the largest political division of a state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "century",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "first",
      "hundred",
      "school",
      "man"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "officer",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a leader in the arm",
      "where you listen to music",
      "a sports group",
      "something you use to help get a job done"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "theater",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "where you see a movie",
      "a lot of money",
      "a hint about something",
      "a piece of wood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ancient",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to be real",
      "possible or likely to be true",
      "very old",
      "to get a book ready to sell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "process",
      "maybe",
      "flat",
      "publish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "board",
      "century",
      "pound",
      "ancient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "county",
      "concert",
      "theater",
      "clue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "gentleman",
      "officer",
      "exist",
      "concert"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "ancient",
      "original",
      "process",
      "dictionary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "available",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to answer",
      "to win",
      "to decide",
      "able to get"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "level",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a point on a scale",
      "with much light",
      "different",
      "alone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "appreciate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to go away",
      "to have fun to show something is special",
      "to use little of",
      "to know why something is important"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "season",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a pool of liquid",
      "a part of the year",
      "a high area of land",
      "to move easily and continuously"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "solution",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "straight ahead",
      "to show choice between two things",
      "reasonable or in a right way",
      "a way to solve a problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "His final offer was ",
    "underlined": "very reasonable",
    "correct": "fair",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "air"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Don\u2019t ",
    "underlined": "throw it in the trash without using all of",
    "correct": "waste",
    "pre": "wa",
    "post": "ste"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The rabbit will ",
    "underlined": "go away",
    "correct": "disappear",
    "pre": "dis",
    "post": "appear"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He asked ",
    "underlined": "if",
    "correct": "whether",
    "pre": "wh",
    "post": "ether"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "You must ",
    "underlined": "decide",
    "correct": "determine",
    "pre": "d",
    "post": "etermine"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "empty",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "in your mind",
      "not containing anything",
      "easy to see",
      "sick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "depend",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to move forward",
      "to jump",
      "to need someone or something",
      "to look at something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "price",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a sweet candy",
      "how much something costs",
      "a music show",
      "a school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "select",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to change",
      "to keep doing something",
      "to choose",
      "to fight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "item",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a path",
      "someone who keeps the law",
      "a thing",
      "a place to watch a show"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tool",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "something you study",
      "a group of players",
      "a loud noise",
      "something that helps you do a task"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "crowd",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a group of people",
      "a flat piece of wood",
      "100 years",
      "a sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dish",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "something no one knows",
      "an answer",
      "a grown person",
      "a plate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "communicate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to shut",
      "to go to where you can\u2019t be seen",
      "to talk",
      "to leave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "exact",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "not on the to",
      "not light",
      "from a place nearby",
      "the perfect amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "achieve",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to think about something",
      "to get something",
      "to tell someone what to do",
      "to break into pieces"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reflect",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to tell someone what to do",
      "to think about something",
      "to damage something very badly",
      "to send back an image"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "opinion",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a thought",
      "a plant",
      "an animal",
      "a fight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "already",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "not made up",
      "before a certain time",
      "more than is needed",
      "very simple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "goal",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a thought about someone or something",
      "a fight between groups of people",
      "something you work toward",
      "a small amount of something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A basic tool has many parts.",
      "If a toy is worth $1, it costs $1."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Anyone can pet a real dog.",
      "If a man has extra socks, he does not have enough."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is not smart to lie to your parents.",
      "If a woman considers leaving, she doesn\u2019t want to go."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If a bike is worth $50, it costs much less.",
      "When you eat vegetables, you are eating plants."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "When a teacher advises her students, she asks them what they want to do.",
      "Some people entertain others by telling funny stories."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If a boy considers studying, he is thinking about doing it.",
      "Many people like making new types of vegetables."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A basic answer is a simple one.",
      "A bit of food is a lot of it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If a girl brings extra paper, she has more than she needs.",
      "People entertain others to make them sad."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "People believe others who lie often.",
      "When you advise your friend, you tell him what to do."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A real story never happened.",
      "A bit of paper is a small piece."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When I went to the hospital, ____________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the nurse gave me medicine",
      "all the doctors and nurses will leave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He arrived on time, but Sarah won\u2019t be here___________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "until much later",
      "leaves in the morning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I really like that writer. He wrote an___________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "effort of a story",
      "excellent book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "After I dropped the book on my foot,____________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I was in pain",
      "I hurried home"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He did not want to go to the party. He __________________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "appeared ready to go",
      "refused to get into the car"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Because the base of the lamp was broken, it could not stand up.",
      "I decided to leave early so that I could be late."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The roof was at the base of the house.",
      "I had an operation to fix my broken nose."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The various movies were all the same.",
      "I like dogs, though I don\u2019t like most animals."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I will leave early in the morning to catch my plane.",
      "My friends and I decided to throw an operation for my sister."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Though I was rich, I bought a lot of cars.",
      "I made an effort to get the job done."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He never used his brain when he faced problems!",
      "The job appeared very quickly."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I entered the house through the door.",
      "I threw the effort with all my might."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "She appeared very happy on her birthday.",
      "People use their brains to exercise."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I informed him of the new rules.",
      "I entered out of the room."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The rock informed me that I was too heavy.",
      "There were various things to do at the event."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to take something that does not belong to you",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "steal",
      "include",
      "amaze",
      "plate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to happen",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "manage",
      "set",
      "deliver",
      "occur"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make someone feel better",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "reward",
      "earn",
      "comfort",
      "contact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to get",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "receive",
      "gate",
      "charge",
      "actual"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person who buys something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "opposite",
      "mystery",
      "customer",
      "thief"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If I receive a present, I give someone something.",
      "If you steal money, you can get in trouble."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A man who is alone can contact many people.",
      "If a woman is sad, someone should comfort her."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "He was given a reward for his poor work performance.",
      "You eat dinner off a plate."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Everything that is for sale has a charge.",
      "A customer sells things to people."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If you earn something, you give it to someone.",
      "Postmen deliver mail from one house to another."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who should manage the classroom?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The teacher should be in charge.",
      "The students should go to the classroom."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When did the theft occur?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It happened this afternoon.",
      "It stopped early."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the actual number of people there?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "There are 31,872 people there.",
      "There are a lot of people there."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Did that movie amaze you?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Yes, I had seen it many times before.",
      "Yes, the ending surprised me very much."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where should I set this book?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Put it on the bookshelf.",
      "It came from the library"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Does the wall have a gate?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes, and it is often locked.",
      "Yes, the wall is very high"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Does the book include a CD?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "No, it is inside the book.",
      "No, we must buy the extra CD."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Has he received my present?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He got it yesterday.",
      "He sent it to you yesterday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What happened to the plate?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It broke when I dropped it.",
      "It helped me with my homework."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Did you hearthe news about the thief?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He stole some expensive diamonds from the jewelry store.",
      "There was a person buying something."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I need to find the other sock that ",
    "underlined": "is the same as",
    "correct": "matches",
    "pre": "ma",
    "post": "tches"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Please ",
    "underlined": "take away",
    "correct": "remove",
    "pre": "rem",
    "post": "ove"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "This is a(an) ",
    "underlined": "very normal",
    "correct": "average",
    "pre": "ave",
    "post": "rage"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The bell ",
    "underlined": "rattled",
    "correct": "sounded",
    "pre": "so",
    "post": "unded"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "William wanted to ",
    "underlined": "go forward",
    "correct": "advance",
    "pre": "adv",
    "post": "ance"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Clara is a ",
    "underlined": "person in a group",
    "correct": "member",
    "pre": "me",
    "post": "mber"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "jesse is a very good ",
    "underlined": "sports player",
    "correct": "athlete",
    "pre": "at",
    "post": "hlete"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "What is your favorite ",
    "underlined": "class",
    "correct": "course",
    "pre": "c",
    "post": "ourse"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He was a ",
    "underlined": "person taking a ride",
    "correct": "passenger",
    "pre": "pa",
    "post": "ssenger"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "What ",
    "underlined": "kind of character",
    "correct": "personality",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "ersonality"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I was behind the winner, so I won the race!",
      "Webs are made by spiders."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Reading increases your mental activity.",
      "We removed the city last week."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "My shoes were behind the couch.",
      "This mental exercise makes my arms tired."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Have you ever found a bird\u2019s web?",
      "I lowered the box onto the ground."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Could you help me lower my seat please?",
      "Be sure to remove the trash from the house."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to move through water",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "lower",
      "average",
      "advance",
      "swim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something nice to read",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "poem",
      "web",
      "member",
      "behind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the condition free from any danger",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "shoot",
      "safety",
      "athlete",
      "personality"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a metal or wooden stick used to support things",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "pole",
      "remove",
      "passenger",
      "sound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the way you act",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "mental",
      "match",
      "course",
      "behavior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "probable",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a word for something",
      "to hit",
      "a leader",
      "likely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lack",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to not have enough",
      "to try to make people act",
      "to have many parts",
      "to do activities to be healthy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "term",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "available for everyone",
      "to help something work",
      "a thing that happens",
      "a word for something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "unite",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a person who dislikes",
      "relationship between people who are friends",
      "to work together",
      "to do something to entertain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fit",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a large piece",
      "connection between places",
      "to be the right size",
      "a loud shout of encouragement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The car will ",
    "underlined": "hit",
    "correct": "strike",
    "pre": "st",
    "post": "rike"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The athletes ",
    "underlined": "run to stay healthy",
    "correct": "exercise",
    "pre": "ex",
    "post": "ercise"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I hope they will ",
    "underlined": "do in public",
    "correct": "perform",
    "pre": "pe",
    "post": "rform"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Is there a ",
    "underlined": "way to get from one place to another",
    "correct": "passage",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "assage"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Her ",
    "underlined": "effort to make someone do something",
    "correct": "pressure",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "ressure"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "They\u2019ve known each other for years__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "and have a good friendship",
      "go to a passage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I don\u2019t know where we are.__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "We need a guide",
      "Let\u2019s perform right now"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The concert tonight__________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "will strike the wall",
      "will be a fun event"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I gave him money because__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I support his company",
      "He didn\u2019t do any work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "At the end of her speech,__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "don\u2019t forget to cheer loudly",
      "fit into your clothes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "You don\u2019t have to pay to get in when__________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "an accident is probable",
      "you go to a public park"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "You must think hard because__________ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I am under pressure",
      "the problem is complex"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Glad is__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "another term for happy",
      "the way people unite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The artist made his art__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "from a block of wood",
      "the people cheered for victory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He thought the book was boring.__________ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He was a critic of it",
      "He really enjoyed it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "When you mix things, you take them somewhere.",
      "They make toys in a toy factory."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A feature of this computer is its small size.",
      "We populate over the ocean."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "We put the trash outside so it could be taken away.",
      "We ate chicken once, so now it is a tradition."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "He went to the tip of the school.",
      "Doing a book report involves reading."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The garbage truck came and produced some sunshine.",
      "I associate dogs with good pets."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You recognize someone whom you have already met.",
      "Blue is a range of color."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The sign was open all evening.",
      "I have a regular schedule. It doesn\u2019t change."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The tree is very wide because it is small.",
      "Don\u2019t forget to organize a meeting for next week."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The clothing store had a sale on medicine.",
      "Our environment has many plants and animals."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "An instance of kindness is sharing food.",
      "He had no period to work."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to keep something going",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "maintain",
      "react",
      "standard",
      "prove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not this one or that one",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "neither",
      "further",
      "along",
      "situated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "people and how they act",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "otherwise",
      "society",
      "advice",
      "climb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "describing the body",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "final",
      "drop",
      "physical",
      "attention"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make someone interested",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "imply",
      "suggest",
      "attract",
      "ride"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "How did Clare ",
    "underlined": "act",
    "correct": "react",
    "pre": "re",
    "post": "act"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "In this ",
    "underlined": "group of people",
    "correct": "society",
    "pre": "soc",
    "post": "iety"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I invited Jane and Lisa to my house, but ",
    "underlined": "not Jane or Lisa",
    "correct": "neither",
    "pre": "nei",
    "post": "ther"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I\u2019ve nearly finished the book. I\u2019m on the ",
    "underlined": "last",
    "correct": "final",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "inal"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I can jump higher than you. Watch me, and I will ",
    "underlined": "show you that I can do",
    "correct": "prove",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "rove"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Can I give you some __________?I __________ that you do your homework before you go out.",
    "options": [
      "suggest",
      "advice"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "advice",
      "suggest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I got everyone\u2019s __________ with my new dress.Where is your office __________ in the building?",
    "options": [
      "situated",
      "attention"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "attention",
      "situated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of his work is very high.I accidentally __________ my phone in the snow.",
    "options": [
      "dropped",
      "standard"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "standard",
      "dropped"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He __________ my attention by waving to me.She __________ badly to the news.",
    "options": [
      "attracted",
      "reacted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "attracted",
      "reacted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "How much __________ is the beach? I\u2019m tired!We walked __________ the path for two hours.",
    "options": [
      "further",
      "along"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "further",
      "along"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She was angry when __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "he implied that she was not smart",
      "he proved that she was right"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you want to win the race, you need to __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "be in good physical condition",
      "drop off all of your extra work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He said that I should play sports, so I __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "suggested playing football",
      "gave him my advice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The sound of the car\u2019s horn __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "got everyone\u2019s attention",
      "is situated next to the bus stop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "We are nearly at Jack\u2019s house. ________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It\u2019s much further down the road",
      "He lives along this road"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gift",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "somewhere you go",
      "something you give",
      "someone at a doctor",
      "something you think about"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "value",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "worth",
      "the ocean",
      "information",
      "not true"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "earthquake",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to see many things",
      "movement of the ground",
      "a need to eat",
      "to work well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "quite",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to feel awake",
      "instead",
      "to look at",
      "very much"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "puzzle",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sand",
      "to be gone a long time",
      "in fact",
      "a difficult question"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "deal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a lot of information",
      "an agreement with another person",
      "a game",
      "to want to do one thing but not another"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hunger",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a strong need for food",
      "a long trip to a place",
      "when you feel awake",
      "something worth a lot of money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "desert",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a place without water",
      "something you give someone",
      "in fact",
      "something that is not correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "effective",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to think in your head",
      "to go somewhere",
      "to choose something",
      "working very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "coast",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to look at something",
      "to see many things",
      "the ground moving",
      "the edge of the ocean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which would you have, juice or water?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I would like water, please.",
      "Yes, thank you."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where did you go on your trip?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "We went to Rome.",
      "We like to stay home."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Do you enjoy solving puzzles?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They don\u2019t taste very good.",
      "Yes, I think they are fun."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Try to imagine what your future husband or wife will look like.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "That\u2019s quite difficult.",
      "OK, I will go there tomorrow."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Have you studied Spanish? I\u2019m a little worried about taking the class.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Actually it\u2019s not as hard as you think.",
      "Actually I would rather sleep now."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I have a __________ for you. Do you think that my car has much __________?",
    "options": [
      "value",
      "gift"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "gift",
      "value"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I like to watch the ocean at the __________. It is hot in the __________.",
    "options": [
      "coast",
      "desert"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "coast",
      "desert"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Having dinner will make my __________ go away.Be careful around those dogs; they might __________ you.",
    "options": [
      "bite",
      "hunger"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hunger",
      "bite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I would like to take a __________ of the capital city sometime.I went on a __________ around the world last year.",
    "options": [
      "tour",
      "journey"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tour",
      "journey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I think this dress is __________ pretty.__________ your paper to check for mistakes.",
    "options": [
      "examine",
      "quite"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "quite",
      "Examine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "cancel",
      "see",
      "notice",
      "own"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "band",
      "boring",
      "instrument",
      "predict"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "magic",
      "rush",
      "tour",
      "trip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "bite",
      "within",
      "hunger",
      "share"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "schedule",
      "message",
      "stage",
      "list"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like this show. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is very boring",
      "It is a long list"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A treasure appeared in the middle of the room. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It owned us",
      "It was magic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The man read the weather report. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "He rushed through the building",
      "He predicted rain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I have many things to do today. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "My schedule is full",
      "I can share with you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When the play started, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the actors walked onto the stage",
      "there were no people within the room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "breakfast",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "power",
      "the first meal of the day",
      "having a lot of money",
      "the reason for something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "knowledge",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "something that you can do",
      "a good feeling about someone",
      "to become better",
      "what a person knows"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "president",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the leader of a country",
      "a little bit cold",
      "to change other things",
      "to tell people what to do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gain",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to get more",
      "to tell about",
      "important",
      "to want more than something else"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "audience",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "not hard",
      "the first meal of the day",
      "having a lot of money",
      "a group of people watching something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "somehow",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "unkind or unpleasant",
      "slightly cold",
      "in a way not known",
      "to change something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "competition",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a leader",
      "a game to find the best",
      "a reason for something",
      "something you can do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "skill",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "what you know",
      "power",
      "the ability to do something well",
      "to think someone is good"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mean",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "not short",
      "to get more",
      "big or important",
      "not kind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "assign",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to want more",
      "give",
      "to tell someone to do something",
      "having a lot of money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "section",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "higher",
      "the top layer",
      "a part",
      "to look at"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inside",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "in front",
      "the inner part",
      "proof",
      "someone very good at something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "proper",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a strong feeling",
      "to treat the same",
      "correct",
      "in the middle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "different",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "not influenced",
      "not the same",
      "to show howto do",
      "a phrase with a different meaning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "memory",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a bag in clothes",
      "a normal thing",
      "how much money",
      "something you remember"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "idiom",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "higher",
      "a meaning different from its words",
      "facts that prove something",
      "to look carefully"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "amount",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "how much there is",
      "a part of something larger",
      "to treat the same",
      "the right thing to do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "honesty",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "the top of something",
      "to learn about something",
      "in front of something",
      "the quality of being truthful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "master",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a way of acting",
      "someone who is very good at something",
      "to show how to do something",
      "a feeling that something is correct or true"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "scan",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to give something to someone",
      "to look carefully at something",
      "something that happens a lot",
      "something you remember"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Is his picture above mine?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Yes, it is much lower than yours.",
      "Yes, it is much higher than yours."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Should we go straight ahead to get to your house?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "No, we must turn left.",
      "No, it is in front of us."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Is this the correct amount?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "No, you must pay more money.",
      "No, that is the wrong answer."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is your belief about ghosts?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I think they are real.",
      "There are many movies about ghosts."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Did he put the table in the center of the room?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Yes, it is against the wall.",
      "Yes, it is right in the middle."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Is lightning common here?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "No, it happens all the time.",
      "No, it never happens here."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Can you demonstrate how to solve the problem?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes, I can show you.",
      "No, I know how to do it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Do you have evidence to prove it?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes, I have a news article.",
      "Yes, I think that I\u2019m a nice person."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How much did your shirt cost?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It was on sale for $15.",
      "I bought it at the mall last week."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Will he be an independent leader?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Yes, he always does what other people do.",
      "Yes, he makes his own decisions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a movement",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "pace",
      "intent",
      "lungs",
      "motion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to look for",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "seek",
      "possess",
      "shine",
      "desire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to pick up",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "eager",
      "lift",
      "remark",
      "spill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very fast",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "landscape",
      "household",
      "rapidly",
      "awful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "feeling worried",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "consisting of",
      "load",
      "polite",
      "anxious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "possess",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to look for",
      "to own",
      "to pick up",
      "to put in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "desire",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to want",
      "to make up of",
      "to have",
      "to say"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intent",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "an area of land",
      "an organ",
      "a plan",
      "a feeling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "shine",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to learn",
      "to make light",
      "to have something fall out",
      "to move fast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "polite",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "thoughtful",
      "worried",
      "fast",
      "excited"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is hard to seek for things when it is sunny.",
      "A landscape may have snow during the winter."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Most children are eager to get gifts.",
      "Good friends are awful to have around."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The lungs help move blood through the body.",
      "People may feel anxious when they give a speech."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It isn\u2019t polite to take things without asking first.",
      "You should help spill the dishes after dinner."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you work at a fast pace, things will get done quickly.",
      "It is important to lift your notes before a test."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "People are eager to leave when they don\u2019t want to go anywhere.",
      "You should get help when lifting heavy boxes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Some people live in the landscape while others live in the city.",
      "Everyone has awful days where nothing goes right."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is good to seek advice when you have a problem.",
      "Students feel anxious when they get good grades."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "When you breathe, air goes into your lungs.",
      "Some students pace to school every day."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Polite people do not say \u201cplease\u201d or \u201cthank you.\u201d",
      "When you spill something, you should clean it up right away."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "counsel",
      "explosion",
      "meteor",
      "bring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "northern",
      "remote",
      "meteor",
      "southern"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "land",
      "steam",
      "castle",
      "temple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "northern",
      "wing",
      "upper",
      "meteor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "statue",
      "command",
      "weed",
      "submit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The bird hurt its ",
    "underlined": "body part that helps it fly",
    "correct": "wing",
    "pre": "wi",
    "post": "ng"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "There are many ",
    "underlined": "stone images",
    "correct": "statues",
    "pre": "sta",
    "post": "tues"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The fire made the water turn into ",
    "underlined": "hot misty air",
    "correct": "steam",
    "pre": "st",
    "post": "eam"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The teacher told me to ",
    "underlined": "listen to and follow",
    "correct": "submit to",
    "pre": "s",
    "post": "ubmit to"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Go to the ",
    "underlined": "higher",
    "correct": "upper",
    "pre": "u",
    "post": "pper"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Many castles are built with thick stone walls.",
      "When you command somebody, you work for them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "All children bring live animals to the zoo.",
      "Some women wear jewelry on their ears and hands."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "You put on jewelry when you take a bath.",
      "When I counsel you, I am trying to help you."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It takes a long time to get to remote places.",
      "Weeds make a house more beautiful."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Good parents ensure that their children are safe.",
      "The people were happy when the monster was elected president."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The explosion made everyone sleepy.",
      "I forgot to bring my camera when I went on vacation."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If I command you to work, then I want you to work.",
      "You can easily ensure that it rains."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The scary monster caused much damage to the village.",
      "Students visit remote places after school every day."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Many people have a castle inside their house.",
      "If you don\u2019t keep your yard clean, weeds will grow."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Students must counsel their teachers.",
      "The explosion in the sky was caused by the fireworks."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Please put another __________ on the fire; it\u2019s getting cold in here.The woman shot the arrows with a __________.",
    "options": [
      "bow",
      "log"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "log",
      "bow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "If our country\u2019s army is weak, our __________ might attack us.Long ago, Greece had the most powerful __________ in the world.",
    "options": [
      "enemy",
      "military"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "enemy",
      "military"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because I respect my parents, I __________ their rules.We cannot __________ Bob because he often doesn\u2019t do what he says he\u2019ll do.",
    "options": [
      "obey",
      "trust"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "obey",
      "trust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I __________ a job with a big company yesterday.I __________ to go to the store, but I didn\u2019t have time.",
    "options": [
      "intended",
      "secured"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "secured",
      "intended"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The rain was a __________ for the other soccer team.During the __________ at sea, many ships sank.",
    "options": [
      "battle",
      "disadvantage"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "disadvantage",
      "battle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person of the highest rank",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "brave",
      "obey",
      "chief",
      "trust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "barely or almost unable to do",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "hardly",
      "unless",
      "secure",
      "disadvantage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to wrap around itself or another thing",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "steady",
      "arrow",
      "bow",
      "twist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to plan to do",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "laughter",
      "intend",
      "battle",
      "military"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "space used to go into an area",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "enemy",
      "entrance",
      "log",
      "weapon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I could not find the ",
    "underlined": "place to go in",
    "correct": "entrance",
    "pre": "entr",
    "post": "ance"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "At work. Mr. Smith is the ",
    "underlined": "person with the highest rank",
    "correct": "chief",
    "pre": "ch",
    "post": "ief"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He lost the fight because ",
    "underlined": "his object used for hurting people",
    "correct": "weapon",
    "pre": "wea",
    "post": "pon"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I ",
    "underlined": "barely",
    "correct": "hardly",
    "pre": "ha",
    "post": "rdly"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "His ",
    "underlined": "giggle",
    "correct": "laughter",
    "pre": "laug",
    "post": "hter"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "long, straight stick with a pointed end",
    "correct": "arrow",
    "pre": "a",
    "post": "rrow"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The little boy was ",
    "underlined": "not afraid",
    "correct": "brave",
    "pre": "b",
    "post": "rave"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Snakes ",
    "underlined": "wrap ",
    "correct": "twist",
    "pre": "tw",
    "post": "ist"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Johan was afraid of heights, but he remained ",
    "underlined": "under control",
    "correct": "steady",
    "pre": "st",
    "post": "eady"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "If we don\u2019t",
    "underlined": "If we don\u2019t",
    "correct": "unless",
    "pre": "Un",
    "post": "unless"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make a guess",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "threat",
      "estimate",
      "supplement",
      "terror"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not having much color",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "shade",
      "rough",
      "pale",
      "narrow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make happy",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "satisfy",
      "disturb",
      "impress",
      "scream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a long race",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "chest",
      "victim",
      "marathon",
      "consequence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a bad ending",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "confidence",
      "sensitive",
      "honor",
      "disaster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "There is always a __________ of falling when walking on an edge.I felt a sense of __________ when I woke up from the bad dream.",
    "options": [
      "terror",
      "threat"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "threat",
      "terror"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl had __________ that she made the right decision.His bad grade was a __________ of not studying for the test.",
    "options": [
      "consequence",
      "confidence"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "confidence",
      "consequence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man was a __________ of car theft.When my house flooded, it was a __________.",
    "options": [
      "disaster",
      "victim"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "victim",
      "disaster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "You should not __________ someone when they want to be alone.The boy wanted to __________ his hunger, so he ate a quick snack.",
    "options": [
      "disturb",
      "satisfy"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "disturb",
      "satisfy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The bumpy frog\u2019s skin was very __________.The man wore a coat because he was __________ to cold air.",
    "options": [
      "sensitive",
      "rough"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rough",
      "sensitive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Eating rotten eggs satisfies me.",
      "A marathon can last for hours."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I have confidence that I can win the race.",
      "It was a disaster when the students did well on the test."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Some people scream when they watch a scary movie.",
      "The narrow river was a mile wide."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A heart is inside a person\u2019s chest.",
      "My mother made a threat of giving me ice cream."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The consequence of stealing is being punished.",
      "If you win a prize, then you are a victim."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The boy wore pants on his chest.",
      "She supplemented her salary by working part-time on Saturdays."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The bully made several threats to scare his classmates.",
      "It\u2019s a marathon from my front door to my bedroom."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "When the girl did not know what to do, she had confidence.",
      "The town was a disaster after the hurricane struck."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "You should always scream in the library.",
      "The victim was badly hurt."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It was hard to stay on the narrow path.",
      "The boy created a consequence before the test started."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "praise",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a picture border",
      "to cover",
      "to show you like something",
      "to go in a direction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thick",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "wide and solid",
      "having no sound",
      "clean and untouched",
      "better or more important"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "incredible",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "oldest",
      "hard to believe",
      "wide and solid",
      "clear and beautiful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "border",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a heavy shoe",
      "a story from the past",
      "an edge",
      "a family member"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "heaven",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "of great value",
      "a place people go when they die",
      "a family member",
      "an edge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "surround",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to show you like something",
      "to close in from all sides",
      "to say you are happy for someone",
      "to cover"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ancestor",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a family member from the past",
      "of great value",
      "a heavy shoe",
      "to slowly fall in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "boot",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "an edge",
      "a story from the past",
      "a family member",
      "a heavy shoe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "proceed",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to cover",
      "to go in a direction",
      "to close in from all sides",
      "to show you like something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "silent",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "more important",
      "oldest",
      "having no sound",
      "hard to believe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "wrap",
      "praise",
      "surround",
      "proceed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "heaven",
      "frame",
      "border",
      "sink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "praise",
      "surround",
      "proceed",
      "congratulate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "silent",
      "incredible",
      "superior",
      "senior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "relative",
      "sink",
      "ancestor",
      "legend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Josh couldn\u2019t see anything from that ",
    "underlined": "direction from which he was looking",
    "correct": "angle",
    "pre": "ang",
    "post": "le"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "For school, I have to learn about ",
    "underlined": "a family member from the past",
    "correct": "ancestor",
    "pre": "ance",
    "post": "stor"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The TV was on. but it was ",
    "underlined": "not having any sound",
    "correct": "silent",
    "pre": "sil",
    "post": "ent"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Have you heard the ",
    "underlined": "story from the past",
    "correct": "legend",
    "pre": "le",
    "post": "gend"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The lake was filled with ",
    "underlined": "clear and beautiful",
    "correct": "pure",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "ure"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make mad",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "dive",
      "anger",
      "mood",
      "fee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to get something and give something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "lovely",
      "palace",
      "exchange",
      "abroad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very short",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "brief",
      "forever",
      "tribe",
      "permit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a woman who is getting married",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "guy",
      "disappoint",
      "bride",
      "sculpture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a time of being young",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "chase",
      "favor",
      "protest",
      "youth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When my sister lost my best sweater, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "it angered me",
      "I was in a good mood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I don\u2019t have much time, so __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "keep your story brief",
      "you can talk forever"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I am learning how to play the guitar, so __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "let\u2019s get some coffee",
      "I\u2019ll be able to play you a song soon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She needed help, so __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "she asked me for a favor",
      "she chased my dog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I wanted to go to the movies, but __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Jack protested that he wanted to go to the mall",
      "she exchanged phone numbers with me"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Mary\u2019s mother ",
    "underlined": "lets",
    "correct": "permits",
    "pre": "per",
    "post": "mits"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My friend asked me for ",
    "underlined": "some help",
    "correct": "favor",
    "pre": "fa",
    "post": "vor"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The police ",
    "underlined": "try to catch",
    "correct": "chase",
    "pre": "ch",
    "post": "ase"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "We saw a ",
    "underlined": "royal home",
    "correct": "palace",
    "pre": "pal",
    "post": "ace"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I will ",
    "underlined": "argue",
    "correct": "protest",
    "pre": "pro",
    "post": "test"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My friend was ",
    "underlined": "made unhappy",
    "correct": "disappointed",
    "pre": "dis",
    "post": "appointed"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "That ",
    "underlined": "man",
    "correct": "guy",
    "pre": "g",
    "post": "uy"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I don\u2019t want to live ",
    "underlined": "for all time",
    "correct": "forever",
    "pre": "fo",
    "post": "rever"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "What was the ",
    "underlined": "cost",
    "correct": "fee",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "ee"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My dream is to go ",
    "underlined": "to a different country",
    "correct": "abroad",
    "pre": "a",
    "post": "brod"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "volcano",
      "scholar",
      "colleague",
      "cage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "persuade",
      "basis",
      "mission",
      "debate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "depress",
      "colony",
      "occupation",
      "overseas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "route",
      "depart",
      "cheer",
      "fascinate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "ruins",
      "factual",
      "significant",
      "nevertheless"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He had a ",
    "underlined": "very important",
    "correct": "mission",
    "pre": "m",
    "post": "ission"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Linda was happy that she had good ",
    "underlined": "people at work",
    "correct": "colleagues",
    "pre": "col",
    "post": "leagues"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Bernie had never taken that ",
    "underlined": "way",
    "correct": "route",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "oute"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "This is a ",
    "underlined": "true",
    "correct": "factual",
    "pre": "fac",
    "post": "tual"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Our country used to have one ",
    "underlined": "other country under our control",
    "correct": "colony",
    "pre": "col",
    "post": "ony"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Scholars can teach you many things that you didn\u2019t know.",
      "Some people like to live in cities, while others like to live in ruins."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Most people fly on a plane when they go overseas.",
      "You should watch factual movies if you want to laugh."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Many people feel happy when they depart on a trip.",
      "Doctors never persuade people to take medicine."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If you travel overseas, you are still in the same country.",
      "Seeing new things fascinates most people."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Some people like to visit ruins to learn about the past.",
      "Getting something they want often depresses people."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Some students like biology because they learn about rocks.",
      "When people debate about something, they have different ideas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "You should see a scholar if you don\u2019t want to do your homework.",
      "People who talk about sad things can depress you."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Some students debate to get their work done faster.",
      "I tried to persuade my friends to meet me for lunch today."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you study biology, you will learn about different animals.",
      "People fall asleep when a movie fascinates them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If you depart late, you can get to school early.",
      "People who like to know the truth like factual stories."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He wants to win so much that he will ",
    "underlined": "not obey the rules",
    "correct": "cheat",
    "pre": "ch",
    "post": "eat"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I\u2019m going to stand in the ",
    "underlined": "dark area",
    "correct": "shadow",
    "pre": "sha",
    "post": "dow"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The police ",
    "underlined": "believe it\u2019s true",
    "correct": "suspect",
    "pre": "sus",
    "post": "pect"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "If we ",
    "underlined": "do what we are trying to do",
    "correct": "succeed",
    "pre": "suc",
    "post": "ceed"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Please ",
    "underlined": "read aloud",
    "correct": "dictate",
    "pre": "di",
    "post": "ctate"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I am ",
    "underlined": "sure I can do something",
    "correct": "confident",
    "pre": "conf",
    "post": "ident"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "After seeing the evidence, you must ",
    "underlined": "decide",
    "correct": "conclude",
    "pre": "con",
    "post": "clude"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "It was a ",
    "underlined": "good feeling",
    "correct": "delight",
    "pre": "de",
    "post": "light"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "This horse is a ",
    "underlined": "certain",
    "correct": "definite",
    "pre": "de",
    "post": "finite"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "large",
    "correct": "considerable",
    "pre": "con",
    "post": "siderable"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Parents have authority over their children.",
      "Poor people aid rich people by giving them money."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "When you have authority, you cannot do anything.",
      "When people cooperate, they can get more done."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "You should admire people who tell lies.",
      "Learning a new language can frustrate some people."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you aid someone, he or she will usually thank you.",
      "If you cooperate with your friends, you will feel lonely."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "You should frustrate your friends when they help you.",
      "Most students admire teachers who work hard."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "destruction",
      "aid",
      "admire",
      "govern"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "frustrate",
      "admire",
      "plenty",
      "relieve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "disorder",
      "enable",
      "cooperate",
      "attempt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "enable",
      "royal",
      "slave",
      "reputation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "reputation",
      "struggle",
      "stupid",
      "cooperate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you help other people, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "they will admire you",
      "they will struggle with you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "After the fight, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the room was in disorder",
      "the room got a reputation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The people wanted change, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "so they defended themselves",
      "so they elected a new person to govern the country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Because I could not solve the problem, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I became frustrated",
      "there was a division between the animals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She found a mistake on her homework, so __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "she aided it to be fixed",
      "she attempted to correct it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "After returning from the library, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "we could cooperate with our books",
      "we had plenty of books to read"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "After her friends laughed at her, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "she thought that the royal palace looked beautiful",
      "she knew that her last remark was stupid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "You cannot tell me what to do. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I live in the capital city",
      "You don\u2019t have any authority"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Read the directions carefully. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They will cause destruction",
      "They will enable you to complete the project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Before he can feel better, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "he must find a way to relieve the pain",
      "he must become a slave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wanting to hurt someone",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "funeral",
      "violent",
      "rid",
      "enormous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very big",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "fog",
      "declare",
      "giant",
      "mad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to show something",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "resist",
      "extraordinary",
      "ought",
      "reveal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to capture",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "trap",
      "extraordinary",
      "ought",
      "reveal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a way of thinking about a person",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "council",
      "impression",
      "sword",
      "tale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mad",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "big",
      "to capture",
      "amazing",
      "angry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "income",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to free from",
      "the money earned by a person",
      "the right thing to do",
      "a person that lives in a town"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "resist",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to want to hurt someone",
      "to show something",
      "to fight against",
      "large"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sword",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a long, sharp weapon",
      "cloud near the ground or water",
      "tobacco rolled up for smoking",
      "a way to think of a person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tale",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to hold clothes in place",
      "a way to see if someone should go to jail",
      "to say something",
      "a story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Every ",
    "underlined": "person living",
    "correct": "citizen",
    "pre": "cit''",
    "post": "citizen"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "group of people who run the town",
    "correct": "council",
    "pre": "cou",
    "post": "ncil"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "ceremony for the dead person",
    "correct": "funeral",
    "pre": "fun",
    "post": "eral"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The thief wanted to tell his story during the ",
    "underlined": "test to decide if he was guilty",
    "correct": "trial",
    "pre": "t",
    "post": "rial"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I ",
    "underlined": "said",
    "correct": "declared",
    "pre": "de",
    "post": "clared"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The pyramid was ",
    "underlined": "very large",
    "correct": "enormous",
    "pre": "en",
    "post": "ormous"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He ",
    "underlined": "freed",
    "correct": "rid",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "id"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I really ",
    "underlined": "should do the right thing and",
    "correct": "ought",
    "pre": "o",
    "post": "ught"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The rain and thick ",
    "underlined": "clouds on the ground",
    "correct": "fog",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "og"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The wav she trained the dog was ",
    "underlined": "amazing",
    "correct": "extraordinary",
    "pre": "e",
    "post": "xtraordinary"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Jeff did ",
    "underlined": "really well",
    "correct": "super",
    "pre": "su",
    "post": "per"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "idea about tomorrow\u2019s weather",
    "correct": "forecast",
    "pre": "for",
    "post": "ecast"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Look at how the vegetables are all planted in a ",
    "underlined": "line",
    "correct": "row",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "ow"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I would like to see that ",
    "underlined": "interesting display",
    "correct": "exhibit",
    "pre": "exh",
    "post": "ibit"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My brother likes ",
    "underlined": "big animals that lived millions of years ago",
    "correct": "dinosaurs",
    "pre": "din",
    "post": "osaurs"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "If you are not careful, you will get ",
    "underlined": "water all over yourself",
    "correct": "wet",
    "pre": "w",
    "post": "et"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Permission to",
    "underlined": "Permission to",
    "correct": "admission",
    "pre": "ad",
    "post": "mission"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Will the school offer a ",
    "underlined": "study of stars",
    "correct": "astronomy",
    "pre": "a",
    "post": "stronomy"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My uncle always ",
    "underlined": "gets involved",
    "correct": "interferes",
    "pre": "in",
    "post": "terferes"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "head of the school",
    "correct": "principal",
    "pre": "pri",
    "post": "ncipal"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "__ We learned about grammar in astronomy class.",
      "__ Do not interfere when I am working."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "__ It was very kind of him to spite his sister.",
      "__ Which shelf should I put this on?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "__ Do you have a shelf in your yard?",
      "__ In astronomy class, I learned about the Solar System."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "__ He drank all the milk in the fridge to spite me.",
      "__ Mrs. Joyner is a strict principal, but she is actually very nice."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "__ The loud music interferes with my concentration.",
      "__ It is against his principals to be dishonest."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Oil and water do not have a good __________ together.We should go __________ the weather.",
    "options": [
      "chemistry",
      "despite"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "chemistry",
      "despite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I wanted to see the bird __________ at the zoo.My daughter has gained __________ to an Ivy League university.",
    "options": [
      "admission",
      "exhibit"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "exhibit",
      "admission"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I wish I could see a real __________.I learned about a South American country in my __________ book.",
    "options": [
      "geography",
      "dinosaur"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "dinosaur",
      "geography"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Be very __________ with the old dishes.__________ push the dirt in around the flowers.",
    "options": [
      "gentle",
      "lightly"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "gentle",
      "Lightly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I don\u2019t know if I would enjoy __________.My son is a __________.",
    "options": [
      "genius",
      "fame"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fame",
      "genius"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a certain amount",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ingredient",
      "quantity",
      "metal",
      "fault"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make less",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "decrease",
      "oppose",
      "insist",
      "abuse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to watch closely",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "bake",
      "monitor",
      "mess",
      "afford"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a plant seed",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "sue",
      "passive",
      "bean",
      "fund"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "money you owe",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "convert",
      "debt",
      "candle",
      "generous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "debt",
      "fund",
      "bean",
      "abuse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "fault",
      "abuse",
      "monitor",
      "sue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "afford",
      "bake",
      "insist",
      "ingredient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "fault",
      "decrease",
      "quantity",
      "convert"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "debt",
      "monitor",
      "afford",
      "generous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "To make sure the door was built strong, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "it was made out of metal",
      "it was monitored to the floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I was treated unfairly by my company, so __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "we decreased the table",
      "I decided to sue them in court"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I went to the grocery store. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I converted the milk",
      "I got a small quantity of eggs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When your friend borrows money from you, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "he owes you a debt",
      "he opposes you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The man wants to cook noodles. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He will get the ingredients",
      "He will insist the water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I have enough money. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "My fund is too small",
      "I can afford to buy the shirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When the oven was hot enough, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "it baked the potato",
      "it made a mess in the kitchen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "In case the power goes out, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "you should keep candles at home",
      "you will be generous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When the girl became hungry, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "she became passive and decided to do something about it",
      "she cooked some beans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "My homework was not turned in. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I abused it at home",
      "It was all my fault"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "carve",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to know",
      "to stop",
      "to teach",
      "to cut into"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "consult",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to stop",
      "to ask for help",
      "to give",
      "to turn in circles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "anxiety",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "very small",
      "luck",
      "worries",
      "group of fighters"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intense",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "strong",
      "first",
      "bad",
      "mountain top"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "proof",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "luck",
      "facts",
      "a large number",
      "a group of fighters"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tutor",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a group of fighters",
      "someone who gives lessons",
      "to turn in circles",
      "to stop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lend",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to stop",
      "to know",
      "to give",
      "to cut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "initial",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "first",
      "mountain top",
      "very small",
      "strong"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hike",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to walk in the forest",
      "to teach",
      "to turn in circles",
      "to ask for help"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pride",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a group of fighters",
      "able to happen",
      "needing help",
      "being happy with yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I should quit eating candy because it is bad for me.",
      "The tiny tower stretched to the sky."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "We ran far above the mountain peak.",
      "I will need water if I\u2019m going to hike the long trail."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If I want to get better at sports, I should quit playing.",
      "The tiny ant crawled in under the door."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The clouds look like they can touch the mountain peaks.",
      "I have a great deal of pride when I lose a contest."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The boy was filled with pride when he learned how to read.",
      "I hiked downstairs from my room."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "There are __________ problems with her plan.I __________ you that I\u2019ll get a good grade because I studied hard",
    "options": [
      "guarantee",
      "potential"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "potential",
      "guarantee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My mother __________ me her car when I need it.I work as a __________ during the summer to make money.",
    "options": [
      "lends",
      "tutor"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lends",
      "tutors"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My eyes hurt when I looked into the __________ light.There are __________ of people in the world.",
    "options": [
      "billions",
      "intense"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "intense",
      "billions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "To cook noodles, the __________ step is to boil water.She __________ taking care of her plants, so they died.",
    "options": [
      "quit",
      "initial"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "initial",
      "quit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I had a feeling of __________ when I thought the bully would hit me.When the man stopped breathing, his wife knew it was an __________.",
    "options": [
      "emergency",
      "anxiety"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "anxiety",
      "emergency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a part of something",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "greenhouse",
      "secretary",
      "thesis",
      "portion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "easy to see",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "blind",
      "talent",
      "apparent",
      "severe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make something",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "compose",
      "commit",
      "exhaust",
      "ignore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to find an answer",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "ignore",
      "exhaust",
      "calculate",
      "remind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a kind of science",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "physics",
      "thesis",
      "vision",
      "uniform"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the act of seeing",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "dormitory",
      "vision",
      "physics",
      "greenhouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "unable to see",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "severe",
      "apparent",
      "obvious",
      "blind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a building used to grow plants",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "thesis",
      "greenhouse",
      "portion",
      "talent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a school building",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "secretary",
      "talent",
      "dormitory",
      "uniform"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to talk",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "chat",
      "compose",
      "remind",
      "calculate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Frank needs to buy a new ",
    "underlined": "piece of clothing that shows him as part of a group",
    "correct": "uniform",
    "pre": "unif",
    "post": "orm"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "It is ",
    "underlined": "easily seen",
    "correct": "obvious",
    "pre": "obv",
    "post": "ious"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My dad will tell me to remember to feed our dog.",
    "underlined": "",
    "correct": "remind",
    "pre": "rem",
    "post": "ind"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Sitting out in the sun gave David a ",
    "underlined": "very serious",
    "correct": "severe",
    "pre": "se",
    "post": "vere"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I walked back to the ",
    "underlined": "school building where students live",
    "correct": "dormitory",
    "pre": "d",
    "post": "ormitory"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "someone who controls workers",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "absord",
      "boss",
      "generation",
      "crew"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not like anything else",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "flavor",
      "foundation",
      "committee",
      "unique"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make two of something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "layer",
      "dig",
      "double",
      "devote"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to eat something",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "dine",
      "precise",
      "mud",
      "handle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to put something higher",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "donate",
      "elevate",
      "soil",
      "contract"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "foundation",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "special",
      "a group that provides money for research",
      "the part held in the hand",
      "wet dirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "generation",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the same age group",
      "without bumps",
      "to eat",
      "something used to cut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "committee",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a group of workmen",
      "taste of food or drink",
      "to put higher",
      "a group that makes decisions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "donate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to move dirt",
      "an agreement",
      "to give something",
      "a single thickness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "boss",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to give something",
      "someone who controls workers",
      "to give everything",
      "dirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The sponge __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "absorbed all the water",
      "contracted to save money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "They will help. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "They are the crew working on this job",
      "They aren\u2019t in the same generation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The food tastes better now __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "that you added more salt to give it some flavor",
      "that you added some soil to make it grow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She was very special. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "She seldom spent time with the foundation",
      "She had a unique skill that few people have"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Dr. Dion started a __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "boss at work",
      "foundation to help sick children"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "We were able to __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "devote no attention",
      "dig very deep into the soft soil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where will you __________?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "dine at for dinner",
      "donate your table from"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The rock was __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "missing its handle",
      "smooth and flat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "You will get dirty __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "if you elevate your feet",
      "if you play in the mud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are cooking for more than two people, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "layer it with some milk",
      "double the amount of water in the recipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Jennifer ",
    "underlined": "looked for a long time",
    "correct": "stared",
    "pre": "st",
    "post": "ared"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Even though the noise scared me, I ",
    "underlined": "returned to",
    "correct": "recovered",
    "pre": "re",
    "post": "coved"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The man\u2019s speech ",
    "underlined": "went on",
    "correct": "lasted",
    "pre": "la",
    "post": "sted"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I am ",
    "underlined": "quiet",
    "correct": "shy",
    "pre": "s",
    "post": "hy"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My little brother woke up with a really bad ",
    "underlined": "hot temperature",
    "correct": "fever",
    "pre": "f",
    "post": "ever"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "My friend said I took her book, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "but I didn\u2019t, so I denied it",
      "so I relied on what she told me"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When I opened the door, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I was shocked by what I saw",
      "it made a funny gesture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "My teacher __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wanted to take a likeness of the class this year",
      "emphasized that students must follow the classroom rules"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The book was easy for me to read, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "thus I finished it in two days",
      "so I recovered a harder book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The things my sister said __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "seemed really shy",
      "gave me a new perspective"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He woke up feeling sick and with a high __________.The door to her private __________ was unlocked.",
    "options": [
      "chamber",
      "fever"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fewer",
      "chamber"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Many people have a different __________ than me.The painting didn\u2019t have much of a __________ to my dad.",
    "options": [
      "perspective",
      "likeness"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "perspective",
      "likeness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ had to be signed by ten people.My brother was too excited to have a __________ plan.",
    "options": [
      "rational",
      "document"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "document\/ rational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The loud noise __________ me.The monkey __________ at me through the bars.",
    "options": [
      "stared",
      "shocked"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "shocked",
      "stared"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I\u2019m not old enough to drive; __________, it seems kind of scary.I\u2019m scared that I might get the __________ this winter.",
    "options": [
      "moreover",
      "flu"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "moreover",
      "flu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy made a __________ to his friends to follow him.My sister ran in and __________ what I was saying.",
    "options": [
      "interrupted",
      "gesture"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "gesture",
      "interrupted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I trusted the man, so I __________ on his advice.I could not depend on the man; __________, I had to do it all myself.",
    "options": [
      "thus",
      "relied"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "relied",
      "thus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The basketball game __________ longer than three hours.I was sick, but I __________ in time to go on the field trip.",
    "options": [
      "recovered",
      "lasted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lasted",
      "recovered"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl at the store was __________, so she didn\u2019t talk.The man did not __________ that he liked ice cream.",
    "options": [
      "deny",
      "shy"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "shy",
      "deny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She __________ the need for good manners.Did the flowers __________ last night due to the snow?",
    "options": [
      "emphasized",
      "freeze"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "emphasized",
      "freeze"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to create something for the first time",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "aim",
      "signal",
      "mechanic",
      "invent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "most important",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "differ",
      "junior",
      "prime",
      "commute"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to move",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "attach",
      "shift",
      "bet",
      "confirm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cost",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "carriage",
      "expense",
      "height",
      "labor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "typical",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "classic",
      "criticize",
      "formal",
      "sincere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I started the job as ",
    "underlined": "low-level",
    "correct": "junior",
    "pre": "j",
    "post": "unior"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The nurse measured ",
    "underlined": "how tall I am",
    "correct": "height",
    "pre": "h",
    "post": "eigt"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Building the house took many hours of ",
    "underlined": "work",
    "correct": "labor",
    "pre": "l",
    "post": "abor"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Marcus gave a ",
    "underlined": "truthful",
    "correct": "sincere",
    "pre": "s",
    "post": "incere"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "We are going to take a ride in a ",
    "underlined": "horse-pulled vehicle",
    "correct": "carriage",
    "pre": "c",
    "post": "arriage"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is a good idea to bet your money on silly things.",
      "You should go to a mechanic if you have a problem with your car."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Drivers use signals to make their cars go faster.",
      "You should attach a stamp to a letter before you mail it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you and your date differ too much, you might not like each other.",
      "When you confirm the results of the test, you make them better."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is O.K. to wear sandals to a formal party.",
      "Teachers often criticize lazy students."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "People must pay attention to signals when they are driving.",
      "When you visit a mechanic they will sell you a new car."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You should wear nice clothing if you go to a formal event.",
      "Good friends like to criticize each other."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Husbands and wives who differ are often very busy people.",
      "If you commute to work, you have to travel a certain distance."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is a good idea to confirm your plans before you travel.",
      "If you attach a large sign to your door, no one will see it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If your aim is to learn how to swim, you must get in the water.",
      "Everyone commutes in math class."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "People who have an aim to succeed are very lazy.",
      "When you bet money, you might lose it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "investigate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to search for",
      "to meet",
      "to stop",
      "to make someone sure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "element",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "the top of a room",
      "a funny drawing",
      "a tag",
      "a part of something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "odd",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a religious man",
      "wanting to know more",
      "not normal",
      "a happy feeling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "priest",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a private book",
      "a person trained to perform religious duties",
      "food crops",
      "a funny drawing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "label",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "things you do well",
      "a tag that tells about something",
      "your job",
      "a particular part of something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pause",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to search for",
      "to meet",
      "to stop",
      "to make someone sure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "agriculture",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "growing food",
      "believing in something",
      "not normal",
      "wanting to know more"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "diary",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a job",
      "food crops",
      "the top of a room",
      "a private book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "faith",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a happy feeling",
      "things you do well",
      "a tag",
      "belief in something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "curious",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "the business of farming",
      "wanting to know more",
      "a religious man",
      "things you do well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy was full of __________ when his new brother was born.The store was __________. It was only open one day a week.",
    "options": [
      "joy",
      "odd"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "joy",
      "odd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl writes in her __________ every night.The boy __________ in his father was strong.",
    "options": [
      "faith",
      "diary"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "diary",
      "faith"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ in this book make me laugh.I want to get involved in a __________ where I am helping others.",
    "options": [
      "cartoons",
      "profession"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cartoons",
      "profession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I __________ my new neighbors for the first time.She __________ me that she was right.",
    "options": [
      "convinced",
      "greeted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "greeted",
      "convinced"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ on my jacket says \u201cdo not wash.\u201dThe smart child had many __________ when it came to math.",
    "options": [
      "label",
      "abilities"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "labels",
      "abilities"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "agriculture",
      "label",
      "grain",
      "odd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "diary",
      "abilities",
      "monk",
      "priest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "faith",
      "curious",
      "investigate",
      "greet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "delay",
      "ceiling",
      "joy",
      "pause"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "greet",
      "curious",
      "profession",
      "odd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to tell or explain meaning",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "adopt",
      "exclaim",
      "interpret",
      "reject"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person without sense",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "fool",
      "nest",
      "stream",
      "vitamin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "clothes that people wear for a particular occasion",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "motive",
      "neat",
      "costume",
      "tone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to reach or put out",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "beg",
      "extend",
      "forbid",
      "silence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "in a kind way",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "beyond",
      "illustrate",
      "indeed",
      "kindly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When I found the lost cat, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I asked my mom if we could adopt it",
      "I extended my hurt foot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When I visit other countries, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I usually tell them how much better my country is than theirs",
      "someone has to interpret what I say"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Not having enough money __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "can put you beyond the forest",
      "can indeed be a big problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "At the start of class, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "the teacher kindly asked for us to stop talking",
      "the teacher exclaimed the lesson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The woman wanted to go to Africa. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The tone of her voice was angry",
      "Her motive was to help people"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I need to ",
    "underlined": "make cold",
    "correct": "refrigerate",
    "pre": "refri",
    "post": "gerate"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "numbers that tells a fact",
    "correct": "statistics",
    "pre": "stat",
    "post": "istics"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "His father would ",
    "underlined": "agree with and like",
    "correct": "approve",
    "pre": "app",
    "post": "rove"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "It makes me sad that so many people suffer ",
    "underlined": "having no money",
    "correct": "poverty",
    "pre": "pov",
    "post": "erty"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I could not get past the ",
    "underlined": "thing that was in my way",
    "correct": "barrier",
    "pre": "bar",
    "post": "rier"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "She does not have a dog, but she likes to ",
    "underlined": "make believe",
    "correct": "pretend",
    "pre": "pre",
    "post": "tend"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Watering the plants is my ",
    "underlined": "thing I have to do",
    "correct": "duty",
    "pre": "du",
    "post": "ty"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The loud noise made her wake up in ",
    "underlined": "a very short amount of time",
    "correct": "instant",
    "pre": "in",
    "post": "stant"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "To open the lock, ",
    "underlined": "put in",
    "correct": "insert",
    "pre": "i",
    "post": "nsert"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He will have to leave if he does not pay the ",
    "underlined": "money to live here",
    "correct": "rent",
    "pre": "r",
    "post": "ent"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Learning Spanish was a gradual process for me.",
      "The boy retired his mother."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The bottle fell and broke in an instant.",
      "I accomplish sleeping before I go to bed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Four is the approximate number of forty.",
      "The old man retired from his job."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It is not always easy to accomplish hard goals.",
      "The race car won by going at a gradual speed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Peanuts are an instant to grow and eat.",
      "His approximate height is two meters."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "permission",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to not be scared",
      "the act of allowing the doing of something",
      "to not be asleep",
      "something sent into space"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "scale",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "size",
      "below the earth",
      "a chemical",
      "an expensive stone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "courage",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to be alert",
      "the act of allowing the doing of something",
      "to take part in an activity",
      "bravery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "satellite",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to not do something",
      "something sent into space",
      "to take part in an activity",
      "the act of allowing the doing of something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pour",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a chemical in the earth",
      "a tool for looking",
      "to move liquid",
      "to be afraid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "raw",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a tool for looking",
      "natural",
      "a man in space",
      "something in a place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "telescope",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a tube for water",
      "a spirit",
      "a tool for looking",
      "a man in space"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "awake",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to not do something",
      "not asleep",
      "not afraid",
      "the act of allowing the doing of something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gravity",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a chart of numbers",
      "a spirit",
      "to move on top of water",
      "a powerful force"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "presence",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a man in space",
      "a worker in a mine",
      "a spirit",
      "the fact of being present"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The movie had __________ flying in heaven and singing beautiful songs.I watched a TV show about how people trained to become __________.",
    "options": [
      "angels",
      "astronauts"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "angels",
      "astronauts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Russia was the first country to send a __________ into space.The teacher asked all of us to __________ in writing the story.",
    "options": [
      "participate",
      "satellite"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "satellite",
      "participate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My mother gave me __________ to attend the party.The man at the door __________ people permission to enter the building.",
    "options": [
      "grants",
      "permission"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "permission",
      "grants"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We are studying __________ that we use in everyday life.The woman keeps her __________ in a safe place.",
    "options": [
      "jewels",
      "minerals"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "minerals",
      "jewels"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The water __________ broke, and now the street is flooded.Thomas got a __________ from his grandfather on his birthday.",
    "options": [
      "telescope",
      "pipe"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "pipe",
      "telescope"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "repair",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to fix",
      "to start after a break",
      "to slide and fall",
      "to catch a bad person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tissue",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a soft paper",
      "a machine that blows air",
      "a news writer",
      "a container with wheels"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pup",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a place fora car",
      "a prize",
      "a baby dog",
      "a game or race"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "resume",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to slide and fall",
      "to start after a break",
      "to prove",
      "to fix"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stable",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a little bit",
      "a place for a car",
      "type of animal",
      "will not fall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a place to put a car",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "stable",
      "bucket",
      "alarm",
      "garage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to prove someone did a bad thing",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "somewhat",
      "repair",
      "convict",
      "resume"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not close together",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "apart",
      "arrest",
      "slip",
      "qualify"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a type of animal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "tissue",
      "breed",
      "yard",
      "contest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a news writer",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "pup",
      "journalist",
      "award",
      "qualify"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Be careful not to slip on the ice.",
      "I hope my yard is ready to eat."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I made a cake with my stable.",
      "The man robbed the store of over 200 dollars."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The boy carried sand in his bucket.",
      "He used the contest to clean the floor."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The award for winning the game is a new toy.",
      "The boy pulled the car apart by washing it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The mother arrested dinner for her family.",
      "An alarm sounds to warn us of a fire."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The stable tree did not fall in the wind.",
      "She slipped the table after dinner."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "My dog likes to play in the yard.",
      "The man was upset after he robbed himself."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I fell down and got hurt as an award.",
      "I won the contest because I was the fastest runner."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "China and Mexico are far apart.",
      "The alarm washed away the dirt."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The bucket wrote down every word.",
      "If you steal, the police will arrest you."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The airport\u2019s __________ consisted of large curved windows and wide hallways.If you mix water and flour, you will create a sticky __________.",
    "options": [
      "architecture",
      "substance"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "architecture",
      "substance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because they had plastic leaves, the flowers were clearly __________.Though they were made in different years, those cars look __________.",
    "options": [
      "alike\/ artificial"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "artificial",
      "alike"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "They need a large __________ of wood to burn in the winter.The water __________ left several areas with nothing to drink.",
    "options": [
      "shortage",
      "stock"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "stock",
      "shortage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ smell of fresh cookies came from our house.I couldn\u2019t __________ which of the black bags was mine.",
    "options": [
      "distinct",
      "distinguish"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "distinct",
      "distinguish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The cat slowly walked across the steep __________.They laid the body inside the cold dark __________.",
    "options": [
      "roof",
      "tomb"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "roof",
      "tomb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the top of a building",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "dust",
      "roof",
      "tomb",
      "chain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an injury to the body",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "substance",
      "distinct",
      "wound",
      "artificial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a feeling of happiness",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "excitement",
      "inherit",
      "manner",
      "architecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a stored amount",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "shortage",
      "manner",
      "alike",
      "stock"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "someone who steals",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "annoy",
      "excitement",
      "mount",
      "thief"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The lawyer said that Jane would ",
    "underlined": "be given",
    "correct": "inherit",
    "pre": "inhe",
    "post": "rit"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The police thought my brother was a ",
    "underlined": "person who steals",
    "correct": "thief",
    "pre": "thi",
    "post": "ef"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The wind blew the ",
    "underlined": "tiny pieces of dirt",
    "correct": "dust",
    "pre": "d",
    "post": "ust"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Tom used a ",
    "underlined": "series of connected loops",
    "correct": "chain",
    "pre": "ch",
    "post": "ain"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The bandages helped the cut on his arm to ",
    "underlined": "become well after injury",
    "correct": "heal",
    "pre": "h",
    "post": "eal"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The fall left a painful ",
    "underlined": "injury",
    "correct": "wound",
    "pre": "wo",
    "post": "und"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Their excitement continued to ",
    "underlined": "grow stronger",
    "correct": "mount",
    "pre": "m",
    "post": "ount"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My sister likes to ",
    "underlined": "bother",
    "correct": "annoy",
    "pre": "a",
    "post": "nnoy"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "His head is so hard. It feels like it\u2019s made out of ",
    "underlined": "firm",
    "correct": "solid",
    "pre": "s",
    "post": "olid"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "She explained the homework in a calm ",
    "underlined": "way",
    "correct": "manner",
    "pre": "m",
    "post": "anner"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Why do you look so clean?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I was using a journal.",
      "I just took a bath."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Can you touch your toes?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I marvel at my abilities.",
      "No, I can\u2019t bend that far."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Do you remember the movie we saw together?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Yes, I recall it was wonderful.",
      "No, I think it was fiction."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What do you think we need for our classroom?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "We should have a flag in the corner.",
      "Yes, I think it is fantastic."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How do you feel about your new car?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It uses sufficient gas.",
      "I regret buying it."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When you want to learn about history, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "you should read an academic journal",
      "you should read fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "In front of a government building, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "there is usually a flag",
      "there are usually baths"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When people die, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "they have to get surgery",
      "their soul goes to heaven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A lot of people eat too quickly. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "They hardly chew their food",
      "They only drink liquids"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The movie was better than we imagined. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It was sufficient",
      "It was fantastic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "This is an important decision. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I feel like I need to bend forward",
      "I don\u2019t want to have to regret making a mistake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Before you buy a car, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "marvel at it",
      "inspect it carefully"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "After the accident, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Ali was disabled",
      "Ali had a tube"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Memorize this address, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "then you will feel tough",
      "so you will be able to recall it in the future"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "He climbed the mountain __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "and overcame his fear of heights",
      "to get more nutrients"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a group of twelve",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "bin",
      "neat",
      "cash",
      "dozen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to say loudly",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "yell",
      "inspire",
      "admit",
      "mere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "relating to the face",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "bowl",
      "facial",
      "nap",
      "wallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not polite",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "settle",
      "vehicle",
      "rude",
      "occasion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an older person",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "criminal",
      "elder",
      "penalty",
      "fence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "My beans yelled when I dropped them.",
      "I keep all of my money in my wallet."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The rude boy always said \u201cplease\u201d and \u201cthank you.\u201d",
      "The fence around the house needed to be painted."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The criminal was sent to jail.",
      "I can admit to a race because I am fast."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The man built a cabin in the forest.",
      "The cash tasted good tonight."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The penalty for your birthday is a big cake.",
      "The coach kept the footballs in a large bin."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "We were nice to the rude man, but he was mean to us.",
      "The wallet made his dinner taste better."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The strong fence let all of the sheep go into the field.",
      "It was loud at the party, so he had to yell for me to hear him."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "When he does something wrong, he always admits it.",
      "The mean cabin told the boy to go away."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "If you cheat during the game, there will be a penalty.",
      "Criminals are always nice to people."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "She liked to bin her toys.",
      "I do not have enough cash to buy a car."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ for the car is gas.My favorite shirt is made out of __________.",
    "options": [
      "cotton",
      "fuel"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fuel",
      "cotton"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of his job made Steve worry about money.She wanted to __________ that her car was safe, so she locked the door.",
    "options": [
      "loss",
      "insure"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "loss",
      "insure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy found a piece of colorful __________ in the ocean.That group of rocks coming out of the ocean is a __________.",
    "options": [
      "coral",
      "reef"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "coral",
      "reef"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Funny stories always __________ me.I __________ quite a bit when I was in Hawaii last summer.",
    "options": [
      "surfed",
      "amuse"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "amuse",
      "surfed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I was given the __________ of editing his entire manuscript.Don\u2019t forget to __________ the door on your way out.",
    "options": [
      "task",
      "shut"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "task",
      "shut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He ",
    "underlined": "blamed",
    "correct": "accused",
    "pre": "ac",
    "post": "cused"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The man\u2019s bedroom was very ",
    "underlined": "simple",
    "correct": "plain",
    "pre": "pla",
    "post": "in"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The clown likes to ",
    "underlined": "entertain",
    "correct": "amuse",
    "pre": "amu",
    "post": "se"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I need to ",
    "underlined": "change",
    "correct": "adjust",
    "pre": "adj",
    "post": "ust"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "During their free time, the children ",
    "underlined": "did",
    "correct": "engaged",
    "pre": "en",
    "post": "gaged"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "This ",
    "underlined": "cloth",
    "correct": "cotton",
    "pre": "co",
    "post": "tton"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "bad storm over the ocean",
    "correct": "hurricane",
    "pre": "hu",
    "post": "rricane"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Tightly close",
    "underlined": "Tightly close",
    "correct": "Shut",
    "pre": "S",
    "post": "hut"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "He will ",
    "underlined": "hit something and break",
    "correct": "crash",
    "pre": "c",
    "post": "rash"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The army fights in the war ",
    "underlined": "area",
    "correct": "zone",
    "pre": "z",
    "post": "one"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The ",
    "underlined": "magical woman",
    "correct": "witch",
    "pre": "w",
    "post": "itch"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "My sister gave me ",
    "underlined": "words that showed she was sorry",
    "correct": "apology",
    "pre": "apo",
    "post": "logy"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "The man went to ",
    "underlined": "a place where criminals",
    "correct": "jail",
    "pre": "j",
    "post": "ail"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "People say I ",
    "underlined": "look like",
    "correct": "resemble",
    "pre": "re",
    "post": "semble"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Did I ",
    "underlined": "say",
    "correct": "pronounce",
    "pre": "p",
    "post": "ronounce"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "It is important that you read the story carefully __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It will help to expose any mistakes",
      "Then it will capture your dog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Mike and Ike look the same. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They don\u2019t resemble their mother",
      "They must be twin brothers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you want to be understood, __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "you must be bold",
      "you must pronounce your words clearly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Please keep our city clean. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It helps to preserve its beauty",
      "It makes it ordinary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Children need to learn that __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "witches are in their schools",
      "tobacco is bad for their health"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Don\u2019t worry about breaking the glass. __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You don\u2019t need to give an apology",
      "You think you are innocent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The man was caught for stealing the money __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "and went to jail",
      "but did not know the minister"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "It would be wonderful __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "if I had bugs in my bed",
      "if the company hired me"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I don\u2019t have a baseball glove. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Can I borrow a duke",
      "Can you loan me yours"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you do something bad, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "you might feel guilty afterwards",
      "you will be a permanent guest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to take away",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "subtract",
      "weigh",
      "dare",
      "net"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to join",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "tight",
      "branch",
      "whisper",
      "accompany"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a place for travelers to rest",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "seed",
      "inn",
      "net",
      "pot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a way to think about life",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "philosophy",
      "sharp",
      "electronic",
      "sort"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to throw",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "breath",
      "virtual",
      "cast",
      "bridge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "branch",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a part of a tree",
      "the hard part of a fruit",
      "very close to being real",
      "a metal container"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bare",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to cut easily",
      "to use electricity",
      "plain",
      "fixed in place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "whisper",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to join",
      "to say quietly",
      "to be brave",
      "to throw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "net",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a metal container",
      "a way to think about life",
      "a small restaurant",
      "a bag made of thread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tight",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "fixed in place",
      "to cut easily",
      "plain",
      "the air you take in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is easy to seed your dinner.",
      "It\u2019s raining so much that it\u2019s a virtual flood."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The boy whispered as loudly as he could.",
      "I don\u2019t care what sort of food I eat."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Will you accompany me to the party?",
      "The dog made a branch to catch the ball."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The door was bare when we took the paint off of it.",
      "She put the net inside the fish."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The man dared to leap over the big fire.",
      "It is important to weigh your math tests."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The virtual in my house was dirty.",
      "When I tell a secret, I whisper so no one else will hear."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You should save the seed so you can grow another plant.",
      "Sort your hands before dinner."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The boy was accompanied alone to school.",
      "The fish could not get out of the net."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The bird built a nest on the highest branch.",
      "I dare my bed before going to sleep."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "The bare tree was covered in leaves and bark.",
      "You can weigh yourself to see if your diet is working."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I need your help to move the ",
    "underlined": "tables and chairs",
    "correct": "furniture",
    "pre": "fur",
    "post": "niture"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "This problem will test your ",
    "underlined": "ability to understand",
    "correct": "intelligence",
    "pre": "int",
    "post": "elligence"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like to be in dark rooms with ",
    "underlined": "covers",
    "correct": "curtains",
    "pre": "c",
    "post": "urtains"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "Tom and Rob are ",
    "underlined": "the best",
    "correct": "ideal",
    "pre": "i",
    "post": "deal"
  },
  {
    "type": "letter",
    "question": "I need to ",
    "underlined": "get",
    "correct": "obtain",
    "pre": "o",
    "post": "btain"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Many people wear a shell before going out into the rain.",
      "In the past three years, the city has had two floods."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Nowadays, many students like using the Internet to do research.",
      "Many groups have annual meetings every month."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Some dogs have interesting feathers.",
      "You cannot ride a bicycle if it doesn\u2019t have wheels."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Churches don\u2019t let people read religious books.",
      "Birds use their feathers to help them fly."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Many people enjoy watching romantic movies.",
      "If you get good grades, you don\u2019t deserve to graduate."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A crab is an example of an animal that has a shell.",
      "People never go fishing near the shore."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "People who do bad things deserve to be punished.",
      "Mountains and hills are examples of floods."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Horses are more common than cars nowadays.",
      "People who are religious go to church."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "If you are romantic, you probably don\u2019t like movies about love.",
      "There are beaches along the shore of some oceans and lakes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You should see your doctor once a year for an annual checkup.",
      "The wind makes the wheels of a car turn."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "salary",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a system of beliefs",
      "to lend something and get back later",
      "the money one makes at a job",
      "the center of a town"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "former",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "in the past",
      "existing for a short time",
      "to establish something",
      "a system of beliefs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "formula",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to believe without proof",
      "to try to get someone to act",
      "a mathematical rule",
      "money for school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "practical",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "the way it used to be",
      "useful",
      "to complain",
      "a valuable collection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "borrow",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to be wanted",
      "to take for a short time",
      "a system of beliefs",
      "to make a person feel stupid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "assume",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to believe without proof",
      "useful",
      "25 cents",
      "boring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "downtown",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a group of letter or numbers",
      "the money you make at a job",
      "food with a lot of sugar",
      "the center of a city"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dull",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "boring",
      "to believe without proof",
      "to take for a short time",
      "to give but receive back later"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "treasure",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "money for school",
      "to encourage",
      "a valuable collection",
      "the center of a town"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "temporary",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a small amount of money",
      "to establish",
      "existing for a short time",
      "to give but get back later"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "The lawyer is very busy because __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "she has many clients",
      "she makes a good salary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I want to make more money, so __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "I will invest some of my money",
      "I assume that I did"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I didn\u2019t like the book; __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "it was only temporary",
      "it was very dull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "This math problem is hard, __________.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "and I wish I had a formula",
      "so I need a scholarship"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "I don\u2019t need more money. __________.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "I will found a bakery",
      "I have enough cash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make or produce with difficulty",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "prosper",
      "arise",
      "penny",
      "forge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person who works with metal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "iron",
      "blacksmith",
      "charitable",
      "benefactor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to keep something going",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "exceed",
      "sustain",
      "preach",
      "occupy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a small area that is part of a country",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ladder",
      "province",
      "encounter",
      "compensate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thinking oneself not to be too important",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "humble",
      "satisfaction",
      "chimney",
      "modest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "benefactor",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "giver",
      "an area",
      "money",
      "too much"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "compensate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "where smoke goes",
      "to shape metal",
      "a tool used to climb",
      "to pay someone in return"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "occupy",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to be rich",
      "to happen",
      "to see someone you know",
      "to be in a place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "iron",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a baby",
      "a type of metal",
      "a good feeling",
      "a person who makes things with metal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "exceed",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to keep something going",
      "to not talk about yourself too much",
      "to be kind to others",
      "to go past a certain limit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a form of money?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A province",
      "A penny",
      "A blacksmith",
      "A ladder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you meet a boy on the street, you ______ him.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "exceed",
      "occupy",
      "encounter",
      "sustain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a good feeling?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Modest",
      "Humble",
      "Satisfaction",
      "Charitable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which one is part of a house?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Forge",
      "Compensate",
      "Arise",
      "Chimney"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word relates to the word religion?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Iron",
      "Preach",
      "Benefactor",
      "Prosper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means to happen?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Sustain",
      "Arise",
      "Province",
      "Prosper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following do people use to reach high places?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A chimney",
      "A blacksmith",
      "A benefactor",
      "A ladder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are smart with your money, then what will happen to you?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "You will occupy a jail cell",
      "You will forge a strong relationship",
      "You will prosper",
      "You will become humble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone gives money to others, we could say that they are ______ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "charitable",
      "modest",
      "prosper",
      "exceed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following describes someone who thinks they are no better than others?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Benefactor",
      "Satisfaction",
      "Humble",
      "Compensate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a strong feeling of not liking someone or something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "deceive",
      "repay",
      "offense",
      "hatred"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not as good as",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "inferior",
      "hatred",
      "satisfactory",
      "venture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to get something",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "overlook",
      "discourage",
      "lodge",
      "acquire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to go to a dangerous place",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wheat",
      "venture",
      "newcomer",
      "caretaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a plant that makes grain",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "fake",
      "wheat",
      "shepherd",
      "hut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "satisfactory",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to pretend",
      "to care for",
      "good enough",
      "project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "newcomer",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "not comfortable",
      "someone new to a place",
      "not as good as",
      "a glass lamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "repay",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to give back",
      "to not pay attention to",
      "a house for hunting",
      "a bad thing that someone does"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fake",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to fail to notice",
      "not real",
      "to get",
      "to protect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "discouraged",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "high place",
      "to dislike a lot",
      "not real",
      "less excited"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "discourage",
      "lodge",
      "venture",
      "hut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "shepherd",
      "caretaker",
      "repay",
      "wheat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "offense",
      "fake",
      "hatred",
      "deceive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "acquire",
      "awkward",
      "newcomer",
      "ridiculous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "overlook",
      "inferior",
      "neglect",
      "satisfactory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl didn\u2019t tike the __________, so she played a joke on them. She put __________ bugs in their drinks.",
    "options": [
      "fake",
      "newcomers"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "newcomers",
      "fake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Dave hoped to __________ a new house. The __________ where he lived was too old.",
    "options": [
      "acquire",
      "lodge"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "acquire",
      "lodge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She was eager to __________ the boy that had helped her repair her bike. While others had simply __________ her, he was happy to help.",
    "options": [
      "repay",
      "neglected"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "repay",
      "neglected"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Going to jail __________ the man from any __________ in the future.",
    "options": [
      "offenses",
      "discouraged"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "discouraged",
      "offenses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In the middle of the storm, the __________ looked for his lost sheep by __________ up the mountain.",
    "options": [
      "shepherd",
      "venturing"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "shepherd",
      "venturing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My little brother tried to __________ us by dressing in Dad\u2019s clothes, but he just looked __________.",
    "options": [
      "deceive",
      "ridiculous"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "deceive",
      "ridiculous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The farmer built his __________ close to the __________ field so he could constantly watch it.",
    "options": [
      "wheat",
      "hut"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hut",
      "wheat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After the __________ started a small fire in the kitchen, he felt very __________ .",
    "options": [
      "awkward",
      "caretaker"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "caretaker",
      "awkward"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Most shoppers tend to __________ any products that they think are __________ to similar things.",
    "options": [
      "overlook",
      "inferior"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "overlook",
      "inferior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She had a __________ for food with tomatoes, but everything else on the menu was __________.",
    "options": [
      "hatred",
      "satisfactory"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hatred",
      "satisfactory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not strongly put in place",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "kid",
      "loose",
      "disgrace",
      "sensation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thankful",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "decent",
      "irritate",
      "grateful",
      "offend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a job or task",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "sled",
      "chore",
      "alley",
      "ax"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "someone you love or admire",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "valentine",
      "pine",
      "bunch",
      "elbow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make angry",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "offend",
      "scar",
      "persist",
      "overnight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bunch",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a group of things",
      "a tool",
      "a narrow road",
      "wood from a tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "elbow",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a picture",
      "a mark on the skin",
      "a part of the arm",
      "a vehicle for snow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "irritate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to keep trying",
      "to annoy",
      "not being serious",
      "full of thanks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "disgrace",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "shame",
      "to make angry",
      "during the night",
      "not strongly attached"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "decent",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to make fun",
      "a feeling from the senses",
      "a job or task",
      "good or correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overnight",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "happening during the night",
      "to make fun of someone",
      "not held in place",
      "a feeling one gets from their senses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ax",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a tall tree",
      "a tool used for cutting",
      "a part of the arm",
      "a feeling of shame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tease",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a group of things",
      "to make a joke",
      "when something is enough",
      "to make fun of someone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pine",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a job one has to do",
      "a tall tree",
      "a mark left on the skin",
      "a vehicle used in the snow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sensation",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "someone one loves or admires",
      "to make someone angry or mad",
      "a feeling",
      "a scar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man bought a big __________. He needed it to cut down a(n) __________ tree in his yard.",
    "options": [
      "ax",
      "pine"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ax",
      "pine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The bully likes to __________ the smaller children. He does not know that his actions __________ them.",
    "options": [
      "offend",
      "tease"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tease",
      "offend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The door to the shed is __________. It will be windy tomorrow, so I must work __________ to fix it so it does not blow away.",
    "options": [
      "overnight",
      "loose"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "loose",
      "overnight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of cutting the grass was difficult. However, the boy was __________ when he was paid for his hard work.",
    "options": [
      "chore",
      "grateful"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "chore",
      "grateful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After the snow storm, the __________ was covered with snow and ice. It was fun to ride our __________ down the path.",
    "options": [
      "alley",
      "sled"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "alley",
      "sled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She hurt her __________ and had to go to the doctor. There is a large __________ where the cut healed.",
    "options": [
      "elbow",
      "scar"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "elbow",
      "scar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She must put all of the leaves into a __________. It will not be easy, but she must __________ to get the job done.",
    "options": [
      "persist",
      "bunch"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bunch",
      "persist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy always __________ his friend about things that aren\u2019t true. But he will __________ his friend if he continues this action.",
    "options": [
      "kids",
      "irritate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "kids",
      "irritate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He thought that until he got a __________ haircut, Elena would never be his __________.",
    "options": [
      "valentine",
      "decent"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "decent",
      "valentine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The runner felt __________ when he lost the race. He had a terrible __________ in his stomach.",
    "options": [
      "sensation",
      "disgrace"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "disgrace",
      "sensation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "far away",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "compact",
      "leisure",
      "distant",
      "passion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a sweet thing to eat",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "dessert",
      "wool",
      "mankind",
      "bloom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a small magical creature",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "pulse",
      "pillow",
      "grace",
      "fairy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an event that covers the sun",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "whistle",
      "decay",
      "eclipse",
      "curl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make someone feel less tired",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "spice",
      "refresh",
      "dip",
      "sneeze"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "whistle",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a flavor",
      "to make noise with one\u2019s lips",
      "people",
      "a flower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "compact",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "far",
      "not at work",
      "small",
      "to help tired people"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wool",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "sheep\u2019s hair",
      "magic creature",
      "something to eat",
      "strong feeling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "grace",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to chase after",
      "to get old and rot",
      "a nice way to move",
      "in the shape of a circle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dip",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to blow out air",
      "something soft for your head",
      "to put in and out",
      "one of the things on your feet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spice",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a flavor added to food or drink",
      "something with a round shape",
      "to make one feel less tired",
      "a sweet thing to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "leisure",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "time when you do not have to work",
      "to become naturally destroyed",
      "the hair of sheep",
      "a feeling of wanting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "curl",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to get old and fall apart",
      "something with a curve",
      "something small",
      "to go after"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pillow",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "something you sleep on",
      "the quality of moving well",
      "an event that covers the sun",
      "far away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pulse",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "not at work",
      "a magic creature",
      "the beat of one\u2019s heart",
      "to go away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Some scientists think that in the __________ future, we are going to use all of our fuel. One way to use less fuel is to drive a __________ car.",
    "options": [
      "distant",
      "compact"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "distant",
      "compact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Early members of __________ walked slowly and strangely. However, people learned how to move with __________ over the years.",
    "options": [
      "pulse",
      "eclipse"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "eclipse",
      "pulse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Early members of __________ walked slowly and strangely. However, people learned how to move with __________ over the years.",
    "options": [
      "mankind",
      "grace"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mankind",
      "grace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My favorite __________ is cinnamon. I put it in all of my favorite __________.",
    "options": [
      "desserts",
      "spice"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "spice",
      "desserts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In the fall, the flowers do not __________. I clean them up when they start to __________.",
    "options": [
      "bloom",
      "decay"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bloom",
      "decay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She __________ a song while she took a shower to __________ herself.",
    "options": [
      "refresh",
      "whistled"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "whistled",
      "refresh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When my father was a boy, he learned all about a sheep\u2019s __________. For example, he learned that it forms __________.",
    "options": [
      "wool",
      "curls"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "wool",
      "curls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Jennifer likes to paint in her __________ time. The most recent picture she painted was of a __________.",
    "options": [
      "fairy",
      "leisure"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "leisure",
      "fairy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Kelly __________ her feet into the pool but decided not to get in because she was __________ a lot. She was afraid she might get others sick if she got in.",
    "options": [
      "sneezing",
      "dipped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "dipped",
      "sneezing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The baby has a __________ for soft things. One of the things that he loves the most is his __________.",
    "options": [
      "pillow",
      "passion"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "passion",
      "pillow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Mary __________ the creature that came into her yard and __________ her dog.",
    "options": [
      "scared",
      "cursed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cursed",
      "scared"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like to walk in the __________. I always think about the __________ that are under the ground there.",
    "options": [
      "skeletons",
      "cemetery"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cemetery",
      "skeletons"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My mother bought me a __________ new coat. My favorite part is the warm __________.",
    "options": [
      "fancy",
      "hood"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fancy",
      "hood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When my friend stayed at my house, we sat with a __________. Instead of sleeping, we sat and told __________ for an hour!",
    "options": [
      "riddles",
      "flashlight"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "flashlight",
      "riddles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Judy wanted to find a __________ that was scary. Finally, she decided to dress like a __________ witch.",
    "options": [
      "disguise",
      "wicked"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "disguise",
      "wicked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We planted a vegetable garden to help __________ our family. But many of the plants __________ before we could eat them.",
    "options": [
      "rotted",
      "nourish"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "nourish",
      "rotted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The poor family was __________ after all of their food __________.",
    "options": [
      "spoiled",
      "starving"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "starving",
      "spoiled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Tim loves being an __________ of that town. __________ after he moved there, he made many friends.",
    "options": [
      "inhabitant",
      "shortly"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "inhabitant",
      "shortly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I entered a contest that was in my favorite __________. Imagine the __________ when I won!",
    "options": [
      "publication",
      "thrill"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "publication",
      "thrill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Christie __________ me with her city\u2019s library. Since then, I have read every book they have about __________.",
    "options": [
      "acquainted",
      "pirates"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "acquainted",
      "pirates"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes an evil person?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Shortly",
      "Curse",
      "Fancy",
      "Wicked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which one is a feeling?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A thrill",
      "A hood",
      "A flashlight",
      "An inhabitant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which one can you wear?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A cemetery",
      "A disguise",
      "A publication",
      "A riddle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is most related to death?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Spoil",
      "Acquaint",
      "Starve",
      "Nourish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is most commonly related to the ocean?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Rot",
      "Scare",
      "Skeleton",
      "Pirate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mom says we need to hurry because the game will start ",
    "correct": "shortly"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It\u2019s a good idea to ",
    "correct": "acquaint"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My little brother bothered me all day by asking me to solve his ",
    "correct": "riddles"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A reporter at that ",
    "correct": "publication"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I am an ",
    "correct": "inhabitant"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was crying because he was ",
    "correct": "scared"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I want to buy that ",
    "correct": "fancy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I need a ",
    "correct": "flashlight"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The children were afraid that the witch would ",
    "correct": "curse"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "hood"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ lived in one of the poorest __________ in the country.",
    "options": [
      "districts",
      "senator"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "senator",
      "districts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When he __________ his fist on the top of his __________, it made a funny sound.",
    "options": [
      "skull",
      "tapped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tapped",
      "skull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "If you want to find a __________, try looking __________ rocks or pieces of wood.",
    "options": [
      "underneath",
      "worm"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "worm",
      "underneath"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She __________ her children by watching a humorous __________ with them after school.",
    "options": [
      "consoled",
      "broadcast"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "consoled",
      "broadcast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She felt __________ sorrow after her husband was __________ for his crime.",
    "options": [
      "execute",
      "tremendous"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tremendous",
      "executed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He decided to listen to the news __________ because he could no longer __________ the boredom of being home alone.",
    "options": [
      "endure",
      "bulletin"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bulletin",
      "endure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The soup was very thick. He had to __________ the spoon with both hands in order to __________ it.",
    "options": [
      "grasp",
      "stir"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "grasp",
      "stir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The television news __________ us of the storm. We put the car in the __________ of the house where it would be protected.",
    "options": [
      "alerted",
      "rear"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "alerted",
      "rear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She looked at all the tools in the __________ but could not find anything to use to __________ the meat.",
    "options": [
      "chop",
      "drawer"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "drawer",
      "chop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Many toys had been piled beneath the carpet in the __________. The __________ I got from hitting my head on the door was painful.",
    "options": [
      "bump",
      "closet"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "closet",
      "bump"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The mother ",
    "correct": "consoled"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Every Sunday, the family watched a ",
    "correct": "broadcast"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I couldn\u2019t find my coat in the ",
    "correct": "closet"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "John left his paper ",
    "correct": "underneath"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "senator"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "In order to get over the wall, the cat had to make a ",
    "correct": "tremendous"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Harold slowed the car down as he drove over the ",
    "correct": "bump"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There is very little rain in my ",
    "correct": "district"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Because he committed such a horrible crime, he was ",
    "correct": "executed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The cook ",
    "correct": "chopped"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes a news program?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Grasp",
      "Bulletin",
      "Tap",
      "Alert"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which one do you put things into?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A drawer",
      "A bump",
      "A district",
      "A worm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following describes something in the back?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Endure",
      "Skull",
      "Rear",
      "Tremendous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following does an alarm do for people?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Alert them",
      "Console them",
      "Execute them",
      "Tap them"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means to go through something difficult?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Chop",
      "Broadcast",
      "Stir",
      "Endure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a doctor for animals",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ambitious",
      "veterinarian",
      "mayor",
      "mutual"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to leave something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "rub",
      "bark",
      "abandon",
      "restore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very smart",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "loyal",
      "enthusiastic",
      "deaf",
      "brilliant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a safe place",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "refuge",
      "horizon",
      "bay",
      "expedition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the bottom part of a face",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "complaint",
      "chin",
      "senses",
      "overweight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mutual",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "fat",
      "having the same relationship with each other",
      "smart",
      "hard working"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "complaint",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a trip",
      "a statement of unhappiness",
      "a safe place",
      "where the land curves in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bark",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a part of the face",
      "a doctor for animals",
      "a sound made by a dog",
      "the bottom of the sky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enthusiastic",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "unable to hear",
      "to leave behind",
      "to agree to do the job",
      "wanting to do something very much"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mayor",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a town leader",
      "to press back and forth",
      "to put back",
      "the ability to see and touch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rub",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to move your hand over",
      "the leader of a town",
      "to show displeasure",
      "a small inlet of water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "loyal",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to put back to the way before",
      "weighing too much",
      "not able to hear",
      "to always help"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "horizon",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "very smart",
      "to want to be successful",
      "where the sky and earth meet",
      "hard working"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "restore",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to change to the way it used to be",
      "to leave behind",
      "to agree to do the job",
      "unable to hear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "senses",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "having similar ideas",
      "to press back and forth",
      "how one sees, hears, and smell",
      "a far-away journey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where could you put a boat?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "On the horizon",
      "In a refuge",
      "In the bay",
      "In an expedition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would happen if you ate too much?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You might become overweight.",
      "You would be brilliant.",
      "You could become a veterinarian.",
      "You might be loyal."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What helps you smell things?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "The mayor",
      "Your complaints",
      "Being deaf",
      "Your senses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following can you feel about a holiday?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Mutual",
      "Ambitious",
      "Enthusiastic",
      "Abandon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What do you do to improve an old house?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Restore it",
      "Bark at it",
      "Rub it",
      "Point your chin at it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean to be deaf?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "You can\u2019t smell.",
      "You are dead.",
      "You can\u2019t hear.",
      "You can\u2019t feel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these people goes on expeditions as part of their job?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "An airplane pilot",
      "A school teacher",
      "A police officer",
      "An engineer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following words is most likely to be related to the horizon?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Computer",
      "School",
      "Newspaper",
      "Sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means to be rich and successful?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Mayor",
      "Ambitious",
      "Overweight",
      "Loyal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means having the same feelings as someone else?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Ambitious",
      "Enthusiastic",
      "Overweight",
      "Mutual"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because it was their __________, my father bought my mother a gift. It was an __________ coat.",
    "options": [
      "anniversary",
      "elegant"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "anniversary",
      "elegant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "It takes a lot of __________ to design new airplanes. You have to know how to make them go __________ in the easiest way.",
    "options": [
      "arithmetic",
      "upwards"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "arithmetic",
      "upwards"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "You should be __________ of yourself! You know you\u2019re not supposed to eat on the __________!",
    "options": [
      "couch",
      "ashamed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ashamed",
      "couch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When the wind blew, the door __________ open. And since it was raining, water __________ into the room.",
    "options": [
      "burst",
      "dripped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "burst",
      "dripped"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My brother is a __________, so he knows about construction. However, he doesn\u2019t know how to __________.",
    "options": [
      "sew",
      "carpenter"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "carpenter",
      "sew"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I heard a news story about something in the __________. I guess they found __________ under the ground.",
    "options": [
      "coal",
      "highlands"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "highlands",
      "coal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Archeologist found __________ made from __________ in Africa.",
    "options": [
      "ivory",
      "needle"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "needle",
      "ivory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "People who work at the __________ do many things to stay safe. For example, they do not have __________ hanging from their clothing because they can get caught in the machinery.",
    "options": [
      "threads",
      "mill"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mill",
      "threads"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Bruce worked hard to __________ the wood floors. Afterwards, he wiped the floor with a soft __________.",
    "options": [
      "fabric",
      "polish"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "polish",
      "fabric"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "On Saturday, my dad made me clean out the __________. I also had to __________ the bushes.",
    "options": [
      "shed\/ trim"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "shed",
      "trim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "How good are you at ",
    "correct": "arithmetic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There were some ",
    "correct": "thread"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I wanted to get a ",
    "correct": "trim"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "fabric"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Smoke from the fire rose ",
    "correct": "upwards"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Sometimes the dog goes inside ",
    "correct": "shed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I live in the ",
    "correct": "highlands"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The old ",
    "correct": "mill"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I used to ",
    "correct": "sew"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The silver was ",
    "correct": "polished"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What kind of material does a carpenter work with?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Plastic",
      "Iron",
      "Brick",
      "Wood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these things could drip?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A dog",
      "Water",
      "A ball",
      "Dirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What could you make with a needle?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A shirt",
      "A car",
      "A computer",
      "A chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean if your water pipes burst?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "They are new.",
      "They\u2019ve been cleaned.",
      "They are frozen.",
      "They\u2019ve exploded."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is the same color as ivory?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A needle",
      "A tooth",
      "Coal",
      "Wood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "someone who helps you",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "bully",
      "ally",
      "bounce",
      "quarrel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to move your head up and down",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "wrestle",
      "strain",
      "nod",
      "defeat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to move on your hands and knees",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "crawl",
      "boast",
      "torture",
      "mercy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to move something up and away after hitting it",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sore",
      "sting",
      "defeat",
      "bounce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to cause difficulty or pain",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "rival",
      "ail",
      "whistle",
      "carbohydrate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "boast",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to go on your hands",
      "to be mean to people",
      "to move you head",
      "to talk about yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dominant",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to be hurt",
      "a friend",
      "stronger",
      "a fight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "defeat",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to feel tired",
      "to try hard",
      "to beat",
      "a face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mercy",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "someone on the other side",
      "to push to the ground",
      "to not give punishment",
      "to feel terrible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "carbohydrate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to win",
      "to move off of something",
      "to cause an injury",
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "quarrel",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "an argument",
      "a face of a clock",
      "to move your head",
      "to talk about yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "strain",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to try very hard",
      "a friend",
      "stronger",
      "to move something up and away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rival",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to move the head up and down",
      "to try hard",
      "food",
      "one who keeps another from getting something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wrestle",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "someone on the other side",
      "to push to the ground",
      "to be hurt",
      "to feel terrible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sore",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "not giving another punishment",
      "to be hurt",
      "to cause an injury",
      "to move on the floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Carol is always ",
    "correct": "boasting"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "lerry is a ",
    "correct": "bully"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Foods like bread and rice",
    "correct": "carbohydrate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We were all sad after our team was ",
    "correct": "defeated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I was ",
    "correct": "stinging"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Look at the numbers on the ",
    "correct": "dial"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "If you can\u2019t speak, then ",
    "correct": "nod"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "rival"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I ",
    "correct": "ailed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Sitting through his long, boring speech was a ",
    "correct": "torture"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not having any hair",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "bald",
      "urgent",
      "absence",
      "nowhere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a good feeling when something bad goes away",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "divorce",
      "pat",
      "roar",
      "relief"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to put something in your mouth and get flavor from it",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wrinkle",
      "suck",
      "rhyme",
      "nap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to act like someone else",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "suck",
      "aloud",
      "creep",
      "imitate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to go away suddenly",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "blanket",
      "kidnap",
      "vanish",
      "reproduce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is it called when you don\u2019t have something?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A nap",
      "An absence",
      "A divorce",
      "A pat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "This is another name for a baby.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Vanish",
      "Suck",
      "Creep",
      "Infant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What could you use to carry wood?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A wagon",
      "An infant",
      "A wrinkle",
      "A blanket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following actions is a crime?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "To rhyme",
      "To kidnap",
      "To reproduce",
      "To pat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the following an example of: \"The cat and bat sat in a hat\"?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Bald",
      "Urgent",
      "Aloud",
      "Rhyme"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following could be urgent?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A soccer game",
      "An emergency phone call",
      "A trip to the park",
      "A birthday party"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What happens when a couple gets divorced?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They vanish.",
      "They\u2019re not married anymore.",
      "Their pets are taken away.",
      "They copy others."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you creep?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Angrily",
      "Loudly",
      "Quickly",
      "Slowly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would you pat?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A fish",
      "A sock",
      "A dog",
      "A table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What could come from nowhere?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "An idea",
      "A day",
      "A house",
      "A new year"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I asked my mom __________ where she was going. She told me she was going __________.",
    "options": [
      "aloud",
      "nowhere"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "aloud",
      "nowhere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ has perfect skin without any scars or __________.",
    "options": [
      "infant",
      "wrinkles"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "infant",
      "wrinkles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After my parents got __________, I was sad about my dad\u2019s __________ around the house.",
    "options": [
      "absence",
      "divorced"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "divorced",
      "absence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My boss asked me to __________ the image for her customers. She said it was very __________.",
    "options": [
      "urgent",
      "reproduce"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "reproduce",
      "urgent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After I fell, I __________ on my finger where I cut it. Then my mom __________ me on the back and told me to get up.",
    "options": [
      "sucked",
      "patted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sucked",
      "patted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ man on television entertained viewers by saying __________.",
    "options": [
      "bald",
      "rhymes"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bald",
      "rhymes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Manuel\u2019s mom thought he had __________, but in reality he had just __________ under his bed.",
    "options": [
      "crept",
      "vanished"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "vanished",
      "crept"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I was scared when my big sister left me in the __________. I was afraid someone would __________ me.",
    "options": [
      "wagon",
      "kidnap"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "wagon",
      "kidnap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "It was such a __________ to be finished with the long exam. I was so tired afterward that I needed to take a __________.",
    "options": [
      "nap",
      "relief"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "relief",
      "nap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Nellie wrapped a __________ around her and made funny sounds. She was __________ a ghost.",
    "options": [
      "imitating",
      "blanket"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "blanket",
      "imitating"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to speak openly",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "abnormal",
      "compass",
      "recite",
      "pursuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "capable of causing death",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wilderness",
      "fatal",
      "impatient",
      "blossom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a group of living things",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "ecosystem",
      "manuscript",
      "dwarf",
      "bamboo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the ability to wait without getting upset",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "proverb",
      "marsh",
      "patience",
      "abnormal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a very short character in stories",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "leaf",
      "dialect",
      "recite",
      "dwarf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "manuscript",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "grass with thin branches",
      "an area not settled by people",
      "being able to wait",
      "an old book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "proverb",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a short saying",
      "a device used to tell direction",
      "a small area of water",
      "to say something aloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pursuit",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a chase",
      "not normal",
      "a book",
      "speaking"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dialect",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "can cause death",
      "a different way of speaking",
      "a flat green thing",
      "a creature from stories"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "marsh",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "flowers",
      "wet land",
      "lies",
      "living things"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would you call some place where no one lives?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Fatal",
      "Abnormal",
      "Wilderness",
      "Dishonest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you most likely find a fish?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "In a pond",
      "On a leaf",
      "In the wilderness",
      "On some bamboo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "People use flowers to ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "be a dwarf",
      "make perfume",
      "recite a song",
      "read a manuscript"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would someone sailing in the ocean use to know which way they were going?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "An ecosystem",
      "Patience",
      "A dialect",
      "A compass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a part of a plant?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A blossom",
      "A marsh",
      "A proverb",
      "A pursuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Frogs are an important part of the __________, especially around a(n) __________.",
    "options": [
      "ecosystem",
      "pond"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ecosystem",
      "pond"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When he __________ the poem in front the class, they could not understand him I because he spoke with a different __________.",
    "options": [
      "dialect",
      "recited"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "recited",
      "dialect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "They had never seen anything as __________ as this creature. It looked and dressed like a man, but the __________ was short and had a long nose.",
    "options": [
      "abnormal",
      "dwarf"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "abnormal",
      "dwarf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ was so old that the words were hard to read. Though she tried to I read it, she soon became __________ and put the old book away.",
    "options": [
      "impatient",
      "manuscript"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "manuscript",
      "impatient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Many __________ try to teach lessons about human qualities such as honesty and __________.",
    "options": [
      "patience",
      "proverbs"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "proverbs",
      "patience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ through the __________ was very difficult because the ground was too wet to stand on.",
    "options": [
      "marsh",
      "pursuit"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "pursuit",
      "marsh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She crushed the __________ and mixed it with some water so she could make the __________.",
    "options": [
      "blossom",
      "perfume"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "blossom",
      "perfume"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The label on the bottle was __________. It said that the powder didn\u2019t hurt children when it was actually __________ for them to consume.",
    "options": [
      "dishonest",
      "fatal"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "dishonest",
      "fatal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ that grow on the __________ are thick and hard to chew.",
    "options": [
      "bamboo",
      "leaves"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "leaves",
      "bamboo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because it is easy to lose your way in the __________, it\u2019s a good idea to bring a __________ with you.",
    "options": [
      "compass",
      "wilderness"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "wilderness",
      "compass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "anticipate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to win",
      "to wait for",
      "to blow up",
      "to go everywhere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "kit",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "something that makes you sick",
      "set of things needed to do something",
      "a round container",
      "to disappear in liquid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "steel",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a large bar",
      "a small towel",
      "shiny metal",
      "a smell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "contrary",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "careful",
      "not fancy",
      "fast",
      "opposite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "toss",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to throw",
      "small amount",
      "to be careful",
      "to lock down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "triumph",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to win",
      "a round container",
      "to lock something in place",
      "careful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "scatter",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "something that makes you sick",
      "metal",
      "to expect something",
      "to go in many places"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "casual",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a large bar",
      "the opposite",
      "relaxed or simple",
      "smoke"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rag",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "careful",
      "a small towel",
      "on purpose",
      "to disappear in water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "beam",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to throw",
      "small amount",
      "to smell",
      "a heavy metal bar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a round container",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "scent",
      "kit",
      "beam",
      "barrel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "on purpose",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "deliberate",
      "casual",
      "swift",
      "contrary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something that makes you sick",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "puff",
      "rag",
      "germs",
      "triumph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to lock something in place",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "anticipate",
      "fasten",
      "scatter",
      "explode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to mix in a liquid and disappear",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "caution",
      "toss",
      "dissolve",
      "steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When the house burned, a ",
    "correct": "beam"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Joshua smiled in ",
    "correct": "triumph"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She walked on the ice with ",
    "correct": "caution"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It was scary when the car ",
    "correct": "exploded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I used a ",
    "correct": "rag"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The basketball player was ",
    "correct": "swift"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "You can wear ",
    "correct": "casual"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I really like the ",
    "correct": "scent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My cat made her food ",
    "correct": "scatter"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When we lit the fire, a ",
    "correct": "puff"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We cannot go on our __________ because there are too many passengers on the small __________.",
    "options": [
      "voyage",
      "vessel"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "voyage",
      "vessel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The ship entered the __________, and boxes of supplies were put __________.",
    "options": [
      "aboard",
      "port"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "port",
      "aboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The criminal\u2019s shirt was soaked with __________ because he had been running from the __________.",
    "options": [
      "sheriff",
      "sweat"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sweat",
      "sheriff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ flew his private jet across the world to visit a new __________ that was said to bring people luck.",
    "options": [
      "millionaire",
      "fountain"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "millionaire",
      "fountain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Churches __________ many people that want a safe, quiet place to __________.",
    "options": [
      "worship",
      "harbor"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "harbor",
      "worship"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Criminals __________ a prison, and the guards __________ the rules.",
    "options": [
      "enforce",
      "inhabit"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "inhabit",
      "enforce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The criminal pulled the __________ of the gun, but it had no __________.",
    "options": [
      "bullets",
      "trigger"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "trigger",
      "bullets"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "To __________ the new soldiers, the officer had them __________ together for an hour.",
    "options": [
      "unify",
      "march"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "unify",
      "march"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I\u2019m going to __________ my friends when I show up to the costume party dressed as a __________.",
    "options": [
      "startle",
      "devil"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "startle",
      "devil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy will be quite __________ if you let his kite __________ away.",
    "options": [
      "bitter",
      "drift"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bitter",
      "drift"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I will go on a ",
    "correct": "voyage"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I was on a plane ",
    "correct": "aboard"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "trigger"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "sheriff"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There is a beautiful ",
    "correct": "fountain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My brother likes to hide in the closet and ",
    "correct": "startle"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The president wants to ",
    "correct": "unify"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We sailed the boat into the ",
    "correct": "harbor"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I hope a bear doesn\u2019t ",
    "correct": "inhabit"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "devil"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following can afford very expensive things?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A sheriff",
      "A trigger",
      "A millionaire",
      "A devil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would a person feel if they were upset about a situation?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Bitter",
      "Aboard",
      "Startled",
      "Unified"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where can many sailors be found?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "With a bullet",
      "On a vessel",
      "In a fountain",
      "In a sweat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a toy boat do on water?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Worship",
      "Drift",
      "Inhabit",
      "Enforce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What do people do in the army?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Harbor",
      "Voyage",
      "March",
      "Port"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hardworking",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "diligent",
      "massive",
      "horrible",
      "impolite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to lose control because of stress",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "bleed",
      "kneel",
      "panic",
      "bond"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person learning a job",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "emperor",
      "apprentice",
      "chef",
      "thread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "someone in control of a large area of land",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "priority",
      "luxury",
      "assure",
      "emperor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to angrily tell someone that they did something wrong",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "scold",
      "bandage",
      "crown",
      "robe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The dinner plates with designs made of gold were a ",
    "correct": "luxury"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The king wore a ",
    "correct": "crown"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Joan is a ",
    "correct": "chef"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "George started to ",
    "correct": "bleed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The book was so ",
    "correct": "horrible"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It is ",
    "correct": "impolite"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Everyone is supposed to ",
    "correct": "kneel"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her new boat is ",
    "correct": "massive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He wanted to ",
    "correct": "bond"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "fiber"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Why would someone need a bandage?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They have overeaten.",
      "They have hurt themselves.",
      "They are sweaty.",
      "They are sleepy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone panics, what might they do?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Remain calm",
      "Begin telling jokes",
      "Take a quick nap to save energy",
      "Scream and lose control"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you probably not see someone wearing a robe?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "At the office",
      "In a hospital",
      "At home",
      "In a king and queen\u2019s castle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a good way to bond with a person?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "To find something you both like",
      "To argue often",
      "To tell rumors about them",
      "To fight with them"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which answer below would not be considered an important priority?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Paying your bills",
      "Having at least three meals a day",
      "Drinking plenty of liquids",
      "Having ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes an apprentice?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "An experienced chef",
      "A woman learning to drive",
      "A married man",
      "A girl learning a new job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What will usually happen if someone is diligent?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Success",
      "Sadness",
      "Failure",
      "Laughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you kneel, what does that make you become?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Taller",
      "Older",
      "Smaller",
      "Younger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are assuring someone of something, what are you doing?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Making them feel less worried",
      "Relieving a high fever",
      "Dreaming with them",
      "Playing with them"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Besides a departure time, airplane tickets will also have what other kind of time?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A fun time",
      "A sleep time",
      "A movie time",
      "An arrival time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "theft",
      "nut",
      "cereal",
      "routine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "roast",
      "pharaoh",
      "stove",
      "pardon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "assembly",
      "affair",
      "bless",
      "exploit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "exploit",
      "famine",
      "merry",
      "cheerful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "scheme",
      "slim",
      "ripe",
      "harvest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The sun has a larger ",
    "correct": "diameter"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "theft"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her ",
    "correct": "scheme"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The woman wanted the religious man to ",
    "correct": "bless"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "During the ",
    "correct": "famine"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The oil company ",
    "correct": "exploited"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Since he is very ",
    "correct": "slim"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My thing that I do everyday",
    "correct": "routine"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Would you repeat what you just said to",
    "correct": "Pardon"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "In history class, the students learned about the ",
    "correct": "pharaohs"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After picking the __________ fruit, the cook __________ it in the oven.",
    "options": [
      "ripe",
      "roasted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ripe",
      "roasted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy didn\u2019t hear what the police said, so he asked, \u201c __________ me. Did they | say that there had been a __________ in his home?\u201d",
    "options": [
      "pardon",
      "theft"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "Pardon",
      "theft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "During the __________, only the __________ had enough food to eat.",
    "options": [
      "famine",
      "pharaoh"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "famine",
      "pharaoh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He wasn\u2019t allowed to use the __________, so he made himself a bowl of __________ instead.",
    "options": [
      "cereal",
      "stove"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "stove",
      "cereal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After eating much of the food from the __________, she was no longer very __________.",
    "options": [
      "slim",
      "harvest"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "harvest",
      "slim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "You can tell the size of the food inside a __________ if you measure the __________ of its shell.",
    "options": [
      "diameter",
      "nut"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "nut",
      "diameter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The party was such a happy __________; everyone seemed so __________.",
    "options": [
      "affair",
      "merry"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "affair",
      "merry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Her daily __________ included visiting her grandmother and asking God to __________ her so she would stay healthy.",
    "options": [
      "routine",
      "bless"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "routine",
      "bless"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The king had a plan to __________ the people, but the people had an __________ to stop him.",
    "options": [
      "assembly",
      "exploit"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "exploit",
      "assembly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She was __________ because everything about her __________ had worked.",
    "options": [
      "cheerful",
      "scheme"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cheerful",
      "scheme"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the condition of being away from other people",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "presume",
      "privacy",
      "slice",
      "jury"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to say something nice to someone",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "compliment",
      "sensible",
      "hinder",
      "swell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an object with medicine inside",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "straw",
      "pill",
      "aptitude",
      "adolescent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fairness to others",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "sorrow",
      "justice",
      "liberty",
      "punishment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a store that sells medicine",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "pharmacy",
      "compliment",
      "literary",
      "justice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a group of people that decides whether someone is guilty or not?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A jury",
      "A punishment",
      "A pill",
      "An adolescent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are going to someone\u2019s wedding, what will others think?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "That you are out for justice",
      "That they\u2019ll presume you know the couple",
      "That you are tidy",
      "hat you work in a pharmacy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Ifyou have the ability to do something, then you have ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "aptitude",
      "swell",
      "privacy",
      "hinder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A ______ person reads a lot of books.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "literary",
      "liberty",
      "pill",
      "journalism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone exercises regularly, what kind of person can we say they are?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "One who has aptitude",
      "A sensible person",
      "One who likes to give compliments",
      "A person who enjoys a slice of pizza"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teacher preferred working with children instead of ",
    "correct": "adolescents"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It was hard for the students not to feel ",
    "correct": "sorrow"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The newspaper was known for its excellent ",
    "correct": "journalism"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The pregnant woman\u2019s stomach started to ",
    "correct": "swell"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The wall ",
    "correct": "hindered"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Henry\u2019s ",
    "correct": "punishment"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Everybody in the group received three ",
    "correct": "slices"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I asked my father if we had any ",
    "correct": "straws"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The children enjoyed their ",
    "correct": "liberty"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The doctor\u2019s office was ",
    "correct": "tidy"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following mean that something is not important?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Superstition",
      "Dismiss",
      "Vibrate",
      "Miserable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the power that causes things to happen?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Affection",
      "To originate",
      "To wander",
      "Fate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the hot liquid from a volcano called?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Shallow",
      "Ash",
      "Slope",
      "Lava"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that a volcano does?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Fate",
      "Erupt",
      "Remainder",
      "Sympathy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is it called to have belief in something magical?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Superstition",
      "Vibrate",
      "Agency",
      "Confine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "John was ",
    "correct": "miserable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Manny found a job with a local news ",
    "correct": "agency"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The river in front of her house is ",
    "correct": "shallow"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like to ",
    "correct": "confine"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The house burned down, and there was only ",
    "correct": "ash"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She has to ",
    "correct": "navigate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My plan to become a farmer ",
    "correct": "originated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He has ",
    "correct": "affection"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The people left the town when the ground started ",
    "correct": "vibrating"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I had ",
    "correct": "sympathy"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The__________ __________ from Europe and was brought to North America.",
    "options": [
      "originated",
      "superstition"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "superstition",
      "originated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ quickly __________ his idea as being too unrealistic to be of any use.",
    "options": [
      "agency",
      "dismissed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "agency",
      "dismissed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Their house is built on a __________. There is great concern that __________ from a nearby volcano will destroy the house easily.",
    "options": [
      "slope",
      "lava"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "slope",
      "lava"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When he learned of his __________, he was frightened. It made his entire body __________ uncontrollably.",
    "options": [
      "vibrate",
      "fate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fate",
      "vibrated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Please __________ your __________ or someone who really needs it.",
    "options": [
      "sympathy",
      "confine"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "confine",
      "sympathy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A gray cloud of __________ __________ from the tailpipe of the car that had not been started in three years.",
    "options": [
      "ash",
      "erupted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ash",
      "erupted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I felt __________ all evening. Perhaps I caught a virus when I had to __________ the missing sheep from the heavy rainstorm.",
    "options": [
      "retrieve",
      "miserable"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "miserable",
      "retrieve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I have great __________ for those who do exciting things. When I was young, I would often __________ the countryside just for fun.",
    "options": [
      "wander",
      "affection"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "affection",
      "wander"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We sent the youngsters home while the __________ of the group crossed the __________ but fast moving stream.",
    "options": [
      "remainder",
      "shallow"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "remainder",
      "shallow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "It was a difficult trip, but we managed to __________ our way through the wilderness in a trip that __________ five days.",
    "options": [
      "spanned",
      "navigate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "navigate",
      "spanned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to give up control",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "revolution",
      "flame",
      "yield",
      "independence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to make a loud, deep sound",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "boom",
      "spear",
      "cliff",
      "blaze"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the highest point",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "knight",
      "retreat",
      "steep",
      "summit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a flat wall of rock",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "lightning",
      "cliff",
      "armor",
      "withdraw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "someone who disagrees with those in charge",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "thunder",
      "invasion",
      "rebel",
      "troop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "flame",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a small piece of fire",
      "the total amount",
      "a long stick",
      "a loud sound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spear",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "metal worn to protect",
      "a brave soldier",
      "a sharp weapon",
      "to give up control"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "withdraw",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to leave a place",
      "a group of soldiers",
      "to burn brightly",
      "to stab with a point"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lightning",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a mountain",
      "to run away",
      "a high flat rock",
      "what you see during a storm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "knight",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a king",
      "a skilled soldier",
      "a strange event",
      "a group attack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "withdraw",
      "armor",
      "steep",
      "retreat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "blaze",
      "flame",
      "summit",
      "independence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "2,3",
    "options": [
      "cliff",
      "spear",
      "rebel",
      "revolution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "yield",
      "knight",
      "warrior",
      "boom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "thunder",
      "troop",
      "lightning",
      "steep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Miguel did not want to ",
    "correct": "yield"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "With his ",
    "correct": "spear"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "During the storm we heard ",
    "correct": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The army ",
    "correct": "retreated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "troops"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "armor"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We walked carefully down ",
    "correct": "steep"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A feeling of ",
    "correct": "independence"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The soldiers managed to hold off the ",
    "correct": "invasion"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We heard a ",
    "correct": "boom"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to deal with a difficult situation",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "revenge",
      "confront",
      "supper",
      "object"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a part of a flower",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "horror",
      "mist",
      "bench",
      "stem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "soft and easy to chew",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "tender",
      "retreat",
      "steep",
      "summit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "feeling of being afraid",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "incident",
      "pregnant",
      "horror",
      "spare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to breathe air",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "sigh",
      "daisy",
      "shame",
      "orphan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bench",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "quiet",
      "a seat",
      "no parents",
      "meal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "plot",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to plan",
      "a flower",
      "to get even",
      "soft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "supper",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a hard situation",
      "breathe",
      "meal",
      "flower part"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dispute",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "an argument",
      "a shock",
      "flat rock",
      "a baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "incident",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "water",
      "to feel bad",
      "extra",
      "a bad event"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If a child loses their parents, what do they become?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A daisy",
      "An orphan",
      "A spare",
      "An object"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would you call someone who can spare time to help you?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "greedy",
      "mean",
      "kind",
      "arrogant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that would fill you with shame?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Buying new shoes",
      "Stealing from your grandparents",
      "Eating cake",
      "Buying some books"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would put a person in a rage?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Getting a new job",
      "A bright sunny day",
      "Meeting friends",
      "Someone stealing their car"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you sneak, what are you doing?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Loudly talking",
      "Trying not to be seen",
      "Trying not to be heard",
      "Happily singing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She went to the lawn and cut a __________ from the garden. It smelled good and was covered in __________.",
    "options": [
      "mist",
      "daisy"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "daisy",
      "mist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The employees had a long __________ with the owner over their low pay. Eventually, one worker __________ the owner and was finally able to solve the problem.",
    "options": [
      "dispute",
      "confronted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "dispute",
      "confronted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She looked across the schoolyard, hoping to find an empty __________ where she could rest. Since they were all full, she __________ and sat on the ground instead.",
    "options": [
      "bench",
      "sighed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bench",
      "sighed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of the car accident made him too scared to drive. It wasn\u2019t until three years after the __________ that he got into a car again.",
    "options": [
      "incident",
      "horror"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "horror",
      "incident"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ woman couldn\u2019t go to work anymore, so she had a lot of to __________ with her hobbies.",
    "options": [
      "pregnant",
      "spare"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "pregnant",
      "spare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He wasn\u2019t usually a person who tried to get __________. However, when he learned that his classmates had __________ against him, he changed his position.",
    "options": [
      "revenge",
      "plotted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "revenge",
      "plotted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A dog got into the garden and ate all the flowers, leaving behind only the __________. When the owner found out, he felt __________.",
    "options": [
      "stems",
      "rage"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "stems",
      "rage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Mr. Holloway cooked hamburgers and vegetables for __________ yesterday. Everything was cooked very well. The meat was juicy and the vegetables were __________.",
    "options": [
      "tender",
      "supper"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "supper",
      "tender"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ didn\u2019t have anybody to take care of him. He often had to __________ into empty houses during the winter just to keep warm.",
    "options": [
      "sneak",
      "orphan"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "orphan",
      "sneak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A thief had taken several __________ from the museum. After a few days, however, he felt a sense of __________ and returned everything.",
    "options": [
      "shame",
      "objects"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "objects",
      "shame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a part of one\u2019s personality",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "trait",
      "profound",
      "necessity",
      "magnificent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to press together",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "vital",
      "squeeze",
      "terrific",
      "trait"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to jump a long distance",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "squeeze",
      "seize",
      "howl",
      "leap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "frozen rain",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "hail",
      "dissatisfied",
      "outcome",
      "dawn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the condition of being with little or no problem",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "dawn",
      "beneath",
      "ease",
      "pile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The princess looked ",
    "correct": "magnificent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It is a ",
    "correct": "necessity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The tribe honored their ",
    "correct": "supreme"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The runner was pleased with the ",
    "correct": "outcome"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The answer to this problem is ",
    "correct": "evident"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My father will be ",
    "correct": "dissatisfied"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The police ",
    "correct": "seize"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The early news program comes on TV at ",
    "correct": "dawn"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We covered the trap with a ",
    "correct": "pile"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The lion protected her ",
    "correct": "cub"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you complete a task with no problem, then it was done with what?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Necessity",
      "Dawn",
      "Ease",
      "Leap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is the one that a police officer would seize?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A mechanic",
      "A criminal",
      "A cold",
      "A teacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you describe something magnificent?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Very lovely",
      "Small and dirty",
      "Having a bad smell",
      "Extremely smart"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A leap is most sim ilarto which of the following?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Sprint",
      "Jump",
      "Squat",
      "Climb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these would be considered profound?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A puddle on the ground",
      "A blank sheet of paper",
      "New shoes",
      "A great idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you squeeze someone, it may mean what?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "You like them.",
      "You are hungry.",
      "You are very tired.",
      "You want to go home."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are beneath your friend, then where is he?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "He\u2019s above me.",
      "He\u2019s below me.",
      "He\u2019s beside me.",
      "He\u2019s nowhere to be found."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What kind of animal will usually howl?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A duck",
      "A parrot",
      "An ostrich",
      "A wolf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is the most vital for human survival?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Food",
      "Water",
      "A heart",
      "Money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that would make you feel terrific?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Making a friend happy",
      "Being late for class",
      "Pushing someone down",
      "Breaking your finger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stroke",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to surprise",
      "to move a hand",
      "a light",
      "to speak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sacrifice",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to give up",
      "to allow",
      "to cry",
      "to say"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "joint",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "very sad",
      "a large meal",
      "a short story",
      "where two bones meet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "emphasis",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "family",
      "a song",
      "a doctor",
      "special attention"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hollow",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "natural",
      "cannot move",
      "to connect",
      "empty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She avoided walking in ",
    "correct": "dim"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Since she\u2019s lived in hot places all her life, she\u2019s ",
    "correct": "accustomed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The holes in the old pipes let water ",
    "correct": "leak"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her back felt ",
    "correct": "stiff"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was happy to go home and see ",
    "correct": "clan"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "astonished"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The school served a ",
    "correct": "feast"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The only thing that I could see in the dark night was my flashlight ",
    "correct": "glowing"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It was ",
    "correct": "tragic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her ",
    "correct": "instincts"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ was about a young boy with magic powers. At first nobody believed him, but everyone was __________ when he made a cat disappear.",
    "options": [
      "fable",
      "astonished"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fable",
      "astonished"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After hearing the bad news, she __________ her fist on the table in anger. Things would go wrong, her __________ told her.",
    "options": [
      "instincts",
      "banged"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "banged",
      "instincts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Though the food was good, he felt sick after the __________. He just wasn\u2019t __________ to eating so much at one time.",
    "options": [
      "accustomed",
      "feast"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "feast",
      "accustomed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ tretched out my arm, looking at my elbow. He wanted to make sure that my pain wasn\u2019t a problem with the __________.",
    "options": [
      "joint",
      "physician"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "physician",
      "joint"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The university placed a special __________ on student safety. They wanted to __________ that they were interested in protecting students.",
    "options": [
      "affirm",
      "emphasis"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "emphasis",
      "affirm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He wanted to find out where his sister went after school, so he hid in a __________ tree in the schoolyard. However, when he came out, he felt __________ all over.",
    "options": [
      "stiff",
      "hollow"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hollow",
      "stiff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The entire __________ was excited about her wedding. While they drove to the church, they sang happy __________.",
    "options": [
      "clan",
      "tunes"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "clan",
      "tunes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In the __________ light, it was hard to find the earring she\u2019d dropped on the floor. She __________ he ground until she finally felt it.",
    "options": [
      "dim",
      "stroked"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "dim",
      "stroked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy suffered from a __________ illness. Still, his family made __________ to make sure he was always comfortable.",
    "options": [
      "tragic",
      "sacrifices"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tragic",
      "sacrifices"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He shut the door to make sure that no light could __________ into the room. However, he could still see the moon __________ outside of his window.",
    "options": [
      "leak",
      "glowing"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "leak\/  glowing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to have enough room",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "accommodate",
      "circus",
      "tame",
      "steer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to change the color of something",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "tempt",
      "dye",
      "stripe",
      "dose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A category of being either a boy or a girl",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "wipe",
      "extent",
      "informal",
      "gender"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the title of a newspaper story",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "pose",
      "headline",
      "ranch",
      "inquire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to pay someone to do something",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "portrait",
      "commission",
      "peer",
      "messenger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inquire",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to pay someone for something",
      "to ask about something",
      "to make someone want something",
      "not wild"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "steer",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a picture of someone",
      "to stay in one position",
      "a traveling show",
      "to control the direction of a car"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stripe",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a line",
      "a person who carries news",
      "an amount of medicine",
      "describes being either a boy or a girl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "extent",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to have room for",
      "how much",
      "to change color",
      "a place with many animals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "coincide",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to happen at the same time",
      "not official",
      "to watch carefully",
      "the title of a news story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The patient __________ if the doctor could help his shoulder pain. The doctor gave him a __________ of medication that would relieve the pain.",
    "options": [
      "inquired",
      "dose"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "inquired",
      "dose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The photographer __________ through the camera, but the picture didn\u2019t seem right. So he asked the people to __________ differently.",
    "options": [
      "pose",
      "peered"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "peered",
      "pose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Her grandfather gave her a __________ that was painted when he was a boy. Her grandfather\u2019s family had __________ a famous artist to do it.",
    "options": [
      "portrait",
      "commissioned"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "portrait",
      "commissioned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The day of the wedding __________ with an important baseball game. As a result, the hotels couldn\u2019t __________ he extra guests.",
    "options": [
      "accommodate",
      "coincided"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "coincided",
      "accommodate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The performers at the __________ had clothing that was __________ funny colors.",
    "options": [
      "circus",
      "dyed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "circus",
      "dyed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "They didn\u2019t understand the __________ of the damage until they saw the __________ that said that thousands of people had lost their homes in the storm.",
    "options": [
      "headline",
      "extent"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "extent",
      "headline"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ carried the notes in a bag that had a long green __________ on the side.",
    "options": [
      "messenger",
      "stripe"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "messenger",
      "stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The owner of the __________ had an __________ meeting with his employees to talk to them about the recent problems.",
    "options": [
      "ranch",
      "informal"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ranch",
      "informal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I couldn\u2019t tell the __________ of the person __________ the car because it was dark outside.",
    "options": [
      "steering",
      "gender"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "gender",
      "steering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The trainer __________ the __________ tiger with a treat, but the animal remained in his place.",
    "options": [
      "tame",
      "tempted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tempted",
      "tame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where are the Aborigines originally from?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Australia",
      "Asia",
      "South America",
      "Europe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone confesses, what do they do?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Go away",
      "Make up a story",
      "Tell the truth",
      "Go back home"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who often shaves their faces?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Women",
      "Babies",
      "Men"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the animals below is very fierce?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A mouse",
      "A lion",
      "A rabbit",
      "A horse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What do you need ifyou want to gamble?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A kitchen",
      "Money",
      "A book",
      "Special boots"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean if you\u2019ll try anything to make a change?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "You are fierce.",
      "You will rob.",
      "You are desperate.",
      "You are terrified."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a person with a lot of opportunities have?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Cottages",
      "Purses",
      "Prospects",
      "Lawns"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What should a person be like if they are handling something dangerous?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Cautious",
      "Mow",
      "Wizard",
      "Confess"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might happen to someone who doesn\u2019t follow the rules of a library?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They may be sent to see an Aborigine.",
      "They may be banned from the place.",
      "They may have to mow the grass.",
      "They may only be allowed to enter during the daytime."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What happens to a cloth that is washed too many times?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It's colors begin to fade.",
      "It's gambled.",
      "It's outlawed.",
      "It's seldom seen."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ lived in a large __________ hat was faraway from the rest of the population.",
    "options": [
      "cottage",
      "Aborigine"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "Aborigine",
      "cottage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The old __________ sat in his hideout trying to figure out what to do. He was out of __________ and thought he should just turn himself in to the sheriff.",
    "options": [
      "prospects",
      "outlaw"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "outlaw",
      "prospects"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The popular __________ was tired of not having any privacy. So he __________ his long beard and dyed his hair so no one would recognize him.",
    "options": [
      "wizard",
      "shaved"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "wizard",
      "shaved"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Be __________ when you __________ with large amounts of money.",
    "options": [
      "gamble",
      "cautious"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cautious",
      "gamble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We decided to __________ all __________ fires because they could spread easily.",
    "options": [
      "daytime",
      "ban"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ban",
      "daytime"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Mr. Beck\u2019s once proud __________ has been overgrown and __________ since he moved away.",
    "options": [
      "lawn",
      "faded"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lawn",
      "faded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ thief stole the woman __________ from the table.",
    "options": [
      "desperate",
      "purse"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "desperate",
      "purse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I had to __________ the lawn in the old field yesterday. As I did, I uncovered a small den of __________ raccoons.",
    "options": [
      "mow",
      "fierce"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mow",
      "fierce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I was __________ by the thought of going to jail. So I knew that the right thing to do would be to __________ my crime to the authorities.",
    "options": [
      "terrified",
      "confess"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "terrified",
      "confess"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My grandfather __________ lets anyone to use his favorite fishing __________. But since it was my birthday, he let me use it.",
    "options": [
      "seldom",
      "rod"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "seldom",
      "rod"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a group of animals, such as cows",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "graze",
      "a herd",
      "a bundle",
      "a poster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to escape from trouble or danger",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "flee",
      "graze",
      "pave",
      "initiate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "somebody who thinks that good things will happen",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a widow",
      "a phantom",
      "a parade",
      "an optimist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "able to be moved or carried easily",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "greed",
      "parade",
      "portable",
      "nerve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a small road",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a bulb",
      "a symphony",
      "a scratch",
      "a lane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "baggage",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a group of animals",
      "an object used during a trip",
      "a glass object",
      "a celebration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nerve",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "happiness",
      "sadness",
      "anger",
      "bravery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "initiate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to run away",
      "to start",
      "to hit",
      "to cut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "graze",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to eat",
      "to want more than you need",
      "to carry",
      "to make nice sounds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "phantom",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "an animal",
      "a person who sees the good side of situation",
      "a ghost",
      "a person whose husband has died"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The band was almost ready to perform the __________. After a few moments, they __________ the thirty-minute piece.",
    "options": [
      "initiated",
      "symphony"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "symphony",
      "initiated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The large field was full of grass where the animals could __________. The farmer knew his __________ could be glad to live there.",
    "options": [
      "graze",
      "cattle"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "graze",
      "cattle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Andy didn\u2019t have the __________ to tell his teacher that he had made a mistake. However, Kristin, an __________, thought the teacher wouldn\u2019t get angry.",
    "options": [
      "optimist",
      "nerve"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "nerve",
      "optimist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man wondered if the __________ near his house would ever be __________.",
    "options": [
      "lane",
      "paved"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lane",
      "paved"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A __________ of goats followed the rancher into the barn. He opened a __________ of food and fed them.",
    "options": [
      "bundle",
      "herd"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "herd",
      "bundle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ told the hungry children to leave her house. She had more than enough food, but her __________ kept her from sharing.",
    "options": [
      "greed",
      "widow"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "widow",
      "greed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My whole class was invited to walk in the __________. We carried large __________ that had our school\u2019s name on them.",
    "options": [
      "parade",
      "posters"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "parade",
      "posters"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The woman bought a __________ lamp that she could take with her on trips. After a year, however, she had to buy a new __________ for the lamp.",
    "options": [
      "bulb",
      "portable"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "portable",
      "bulb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "There was a loud noise, then a large __________ came into the room. The children screamed and __________ immediately.",
    "options": [
      "fled",
      "phantom"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "phantom",
      "fled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He bought new __________ before the trip, but after the first time he used them, they were __________ and looked old.",
    "options": [
      "baggage",
      "scratched"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "baggage",
      "scratched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "relates to the cold places on Earth",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "polar",
      "marine",
      "frost",
      "underlying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a small part of something",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "fraction",
      "merit",
      "ray",
      "dynasty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something that appears real but is not",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "resign",
      "circulate",
      "derive",
      "illusion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to get from another source",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "frost",
      "illusion",
      "derive",
      "invade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to die in the water from lack of air",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "via",
      "drown",
      "suicide",
      "underlying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "invade",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to come from",
      "to kill oneself",
      "to take over another country",
      "to happen because of something else"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dynasty",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "thin layer of ice",
      "a group of rulers from the same family",
      "a person that knows about the sea",
      "very cold"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "merit",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a low ranking officer",
      "a good quality",
      "a part of a whole",
      "a hidden problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "resign",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to quit",
      "to die underwater",
      "to shake",
      "to move from place to place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ray",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a way to get through",
      "something that seems to be something else",
      "a group of soldiers at sea",
      "a line of light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "tremble",
      "circulate",
      "ray",
      "frost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "dynasty",
      "marine",
      "navy",
      "merit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "lieutenant",
      "derive",
      "polar",
      "invade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,1",
    "options": [
      "consequent",
      "underlying",
      "fraction",
      "resign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,3",
    "options": [
      "illusion",
      "suicide",
      "via",
      "drown"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We only require that you donate a ",
    "correct": "fraction"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The massive ",
    "correct": "dynasty"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "ray"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "illusion"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Josie arrived ",
    "correct": "via"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The scent of her perfume ",
    "correct": "circulated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After hearing about the new policy, Mitch was so upset that he ",
    "correct": "resigned"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "frost"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The kitten ",
    "correct": "trembled"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I was a ",
    "correct": "lieutenant"
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "collapse",
      "alter",
      "wire",
      "crush"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "disgusting",
      "envy",
      "jealous",
      "wipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,3",
    "options": [
      "ginger",
      "autumn",
      "receipt",
      "flour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "0,2",
    "options": [
      "fuse",
      "curve",
      "fireworks",
      "drain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better",
    "correct": "1,2",
    "options": [
      "aside",
      "paste",
      "blend",
      "embrace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The mixture was a funny color and looked ",
    "correct": "disgusting"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After the house ",
    "correct": "collapsed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When the boy spilled his milk, his mother ",
    "correct": "wiped"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The bird ",
    "correct": "curved"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The mother ",
    "correct": "embraced"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The farmer\u2019s food was usually ready in the ",
    "correct": "autumn"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "wire"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She ",
    "correct": "altered"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "drain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I asked the taxi driver to give me a ",
    "correct": "receipt"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The roof of the old house hadn\u2019t been __________ since it was built. Since it wasn\u2019t cared for, it eventually __________.",
    "options": [
      "collapsed",
      "altered"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "collapsed",
      "altered"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The recipe says to use two tablespoons of fresh __________. Then __________ all of the ingredients together and put it over the meat.",
    "options": [
      "blend",
      "ginger"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ginger",
      "blend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Last __________, my neighbor\u2019s parents gave him a toy rocket to put together. I __________ him because I\u2019ve always wanted one for myself.",
    "options": [
      "envied",
      "autumn"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "autumn",
      "envied"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The family stood __________ as the father tried to fix the car. He was sure that he just needed to fix the __________ on it.",
    "options": [
      "aside",
      "wires"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "aside",
      "wires"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "On my way home, I accidentally __________ the carton of eggs. The store let me exchange them since I had my __________.",
    "options": [
      "crushed",
      "receipt"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "crushed",
      "receipt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "At the end of the festival, there were supposed to be __________. However, they didn\u2019t work because something had damaged the __________.",
    "options": [
      "fuse",
      "fireworks"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fireworks",
      "fuse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Annie bought a type of paint that was a thick __________. It was easy to use, and when she was done, she __________ it up with an old cloth.",
    "options": [
      "paste",
      "wiped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "paste",
      "wiped"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The player hit the ball and it __________ through the field without anybody touching it. As a result, the team won the game and __________ each other in happiness.",
    "options": [
      "curved",
      "embraced"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "curved",
      "embraced"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl wasn\u2019t __________ of her brother\u2019s new friend. All they did was talk about __________ things like frogs and snakes.",
    "options": [
      "disgusting",
      "jealous"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "jealous",
      "disgusting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Megan didn\u2019t use enough __________ when making pancakes. As a result, she poured the mixture down the __________ and tried again.",
    "options": [
      "flour",
      "drain"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "flour",
      "drain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something you keep flowers in",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "vase",
      "stack",
      "tin",
      "spectacle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to say something is better than it really is",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "exaggerate",
      "drag",
      "heritage",
      "insult"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a rich and important person",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ambassador",
      "noble",
      "necklace",
      "prejudice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "having light, yellow-colored hair",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "suspicious",
      "blonde",
      "rumor",
      "conquer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not trusting of someone",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "suspicious",
      "meanwhile",
      "acknowledge",
      "precious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "heritage",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "features of a society",
      "to put into something else",
      "a government worker",
      "a rich and powerful person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spectacle",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "an amazing sight",
      "to take something",
      "something that is wrong",
      "a piece of jewelry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "drag",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to attack",
      "very important",
      "not trusting",
      "to pull something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sin",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "something wrong for religious reasons",
      "the traditions of a country",
      "a place to keep flowers",
      "an official working in a foreign country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tin",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a color of hair",
      "to say mean things",
      "a cheap metal",
      "to control a country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The police waited for the criminals. ",
    "correct": "Meanwhile"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "ambassador"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "necklace"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I ",
    "correct": "acknowledge"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Don\u2019t ",
    "correct": "insult"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Alexander the Great ",
    "correct": "conquered"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She admired the ",
    "correct": "precious"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Would you please ",
    "correct": "stack"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "You shouldn\u2019t spread ",
    "correct": "rumors"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some visitors to foreign countries experience ",
    "correct": "prejudice"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very cold",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "arctic",
      "grocer",
      "canal",
      "tide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person who sells things",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "dairy",
      "merchant",
      "stubborn",
      "congress"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something very bad",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "chemist",
      "chill",
      "tragedy",
      "tide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to go down",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "hesitate",
      "descend",
      "institution",
      "splash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to run",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "postpone",
      "suburb",
      "poke",
      "jog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hesitate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "an organization",
      "to feel pain",
      "to wait for a moment",
      "to make something happen later"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "canal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to go down",
      "a path for water",
      "things made from milk",
      "a small city"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "chill",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a group of leaders",
      "a feeling of cold",
      "a person who sells food",
      "to run"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stubborn",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a very bad thing",
      "a person who sells things",
      "when water hits something",
      "not changing your mind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "poke",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to make something later",
      "the level of the sea",
      "to push with your finger",
      "a scientist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The party was planned for tonight, but it was ",
    "correct": "postponed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I was recently elected to ",
    "correct": "congress"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My grandfather was a ",
    "correct": "merchant"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The hospital is an important ",
    "correct": "institution"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "chemist"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "dairy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Don\u2019t ",
    "correct": "splash"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She lives in the ",
    "correct": "suburb"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "tide"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It ",
    "correct": "ache"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to show in a picture",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "portray",
      "trace",
      "gaze",
      "rotate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something that causes an event",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "souvenir",
      "certificate",
      "circumstance",
      "criticism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a feeling of sadness",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "frown",
      "grief",
      "bomb",
      "glance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a box for burying dead people",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "groom",
      "license",
      "coffin",
      "cope"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a device for making small things look bigger",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "submarine",
      "microscope",
      "devastate",
      "nuclear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "certificate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a document for permission",
      "something bought to remind of a place",
      "between two sizes",
      "a document that claims a fact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cope",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to deal with a difficult situation",
      "to look at something quickly",
      "to completely destroy something",
      "to turn around in a circle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "trace",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to look at for a long time",
      "to follow over with the eyes",
      "to show in a picture",
      "to express dislike or sadness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "groom",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a boat that can go under water",
      "a box used to bury dead people",
      "a man about to be married",
      "something that causes an event"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bomb",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to go between two places",
      "the act of finding fault with someone",
      "an object that explodes",
      "a feeling of sadness because of death"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The engineer __________ a line with his finger to where he thought the police officers would find the __________.",
    "options": [
      "traced",
      "bomb"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "traced",
      "bomb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The politician said that there were many __________ that lead to the US using a __________ weapon on Japan.",
    "options": [
      "nuclear",
      "circumstances"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "circumstances",
      "nuclear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I was so busy that I could only __________ at my daughter\u2019s __________ of achievement. I will take a better look at it when I get home.",
    "options": [
      "glance",
      "certificate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "glance",
      "certificate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The entire family was filled with __________ as their father\u2019s __________ was slowly lowered into the ground.",
    "options": [
      "coffin",
      "grief"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "grief",
      "coffin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I was completely __________ when I heard the news of her accident. I hope that her husband can __________ with the situation.",
    "options": [
      "cope",
      "devastated"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "devastated",
      "cope"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Maria __________ her __________ so that all of her classmates could get a good view of it.",
    "options": [
      "rotated",
      "souvenir"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rotated",
      "souvenir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After receiving a great deal of __________ about her idea, Katie __________ but was determined not to quit.",
    "options": [
      "frowned",
      "criticism"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "criticism",
      "frowned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Tony __________ at the pictures of the new forms of bacteria that were discovered. Curious, he viewed samples of them through a powerful __________.",
    "options": [
      "gazed",
      "microscope"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "gazed",
      "microscope"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Eric did not have a __________ to operate the sophisticated __________.",
    "options": [
      "submarine",
      "license"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "license",
      "submarine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Lisa __________ her new __________ as the perfect husband. But we all knew that he had many faults.",
    "options": [
      "groom",
      "portrayed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "portrayed",
      "groom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "clothes that need to be washed",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "spine",
      "appliance",
      "laundry",
      "cupboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "easy to break",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "emerge",
      "delicate",
      "basin",
      "pursue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a brush with a long handle used for cleaning floors",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "handicap",
      "broom",
      "strip",
      "hook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to promise something",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "swear",
      "hop",
      "utilize",
      "swing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not wanting to do something",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sleeve",
      "stain",
      "caterpillar",
      "reluctant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pursue",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a bone in the middle of the back",
      "a bowl for washing things",
      "to come out of something",
      "to chase after something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "appliance",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a piece of equipment used in the home",
      "a section of cloth used to cover a floor",
      "a wooden box used for storing things",
      "a dirty mark that is difficult to clean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "utilize",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to jump a short distance",
      "an insect that looks like a worm",
      "to move something back and forth",
      "to use something for a specific purpose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "handicap",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a curved metal for holding things",
      "something that is easy to break",
      "a promise to do something",
      "a condition that limits abilities"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "swing",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to move something back and forth",
      "a curved piece of metal",
      "a brush with a long handle",
      "clothes that need to be washed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some animals, such as insects, do not have a ",
    "correct": "spine"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "John filled the ",
    "correct": "basin"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She was hungry so she looked for a snack in the ",
    "correct": "cupboard"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The rabbit ",
    "correct": "hopped"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The swimmer ",
    "correct": "emerged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mary put her flowers in a pot and then hung it from a ",
    "correct": "hook"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "caterpillar"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "William used a ",
    "correct": "strip"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The baseball player rolled up the ",
    "correct": "sleeves"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We tried using soap and hot water but couldn\u2019t get the ",
    "correct": "stain"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The population growth in the city was incredibly __________. It is quite surprising that people settled there at such a fast __________.",
    "options": [
      "rapid",
      "rate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rapid",
      "rate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Many __________ laws make it illegal for business to compete in unfair ways. However, the specific laws in different countries __________ greatly.",
    "options": [
      "contemporary",
      "vary"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "contemporary",
      "vary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because it is quite __________ on the island, various kinds of plants grow well there. However, some of these plants are __________ to humans.",
    "options": [
      "humid",
      "toxic"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "humid",
      "toxic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The cheese has a smooth __________. However, some people find it hard to eat because of its powerful __________.",
    "options": [
      "texture",
      "aroma"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "texture",
      "aroma"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A __________ of people suggested that nearby cities could fight the invaders if they cooperated with each other. As a result, everyone __________ their efforts and defeated the invaders.",
    "options": [
      "cluster",
      "combined"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cluster",
      "combined"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The artist uses __________ differences of color in her landscapes. This has an overall calming and __________ effect on the viewer.",
    "options": [
      "soothing",
      "subtle"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "subtle",
      "soothing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A huge garden was __________ in the middle of the city. However, a species of rare plants gave off an unpleasant __________.",
    "options": [
      "cultivated",
      "odor"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cultivated",
      "odor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "During a four or five course meal, one should drink something to clean the __________ between courses. The perfect __________ for this is, of course, water.",
    "options": [
      "beverage",
      "palate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "palate",
      "beverage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I can explain the basic story in a simple, __________ way. A boy is given a __________ message, and he begins an exciting adventure.",
    "options": [
      "condensed",
      "divine"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "condensed",
      "divine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "This island of Oahu is not a natural __________ like Maui. However, tourists still have plenty to enjoy on Oahu, from visits to pineapple __________ to traditional celebrations.",
    "options": [
      "plantations",
      "paradise"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "paradise",
      "plantations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A soothing cup of tea __________.",
    "correct": "is good for a sore throat",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The odor of the cheese __________.",
    "correct": "was too strong to be enjoyable",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The pot\u2019s texture  __________.",
    "correct": "feels so smooth",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The chemical is toxic  __________.",
    "correct": "to insects and small animals",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The contemporary fiction class __________.",
    "correct": "includes work from the 21st century",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The rate at which these flowers grew __________.",
    "correct": "was surprisingly fast",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My mother cultivates  __________.",
    "correct": "several species of flowers as a hobby",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The plantation had __________.",
    "correct": "twenty workers who grew cotton",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The thick and humid forest __________.",
    "correct": "covered almost a third of the country",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "That cluster of stars in the sky makes __________.",
    "correct": "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull",
    "options": [
      "was surprisingly fast",
      "includes work from the 21st century",
      "feels so smooth",
      "covered almost a third of the country",
      "was too strong to be enjoyable",
      "several species of flowers as a hobby",
      "to insects and small animals",
      "twenty workers who grew cotton",
      "is good for a sore throat",
      "the shoulder of Taurus the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The scientists wanted to find a cure for the sickness, __________.",
    "correct": "so they combined the chemicals",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He offered to share his water, __________.",
    "correct": "but I wanted my own beverage",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I prefer mocha to coffee __________.",
    "correct": "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Many new jobs were created, __________.",
    "correct": "so economic growth was rapid",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The report was ten pages long, __________.",
    "correct": "but the condensed version was shorter",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The doctor asked him to open his mouth, __________.",
    "correct": "and she looked at his palate",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She walked in the door, __________.",
    "correct": "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Because the island is so warm and beautiful, __________.",
    "correct": "people call it a paradise",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Because patients\u2019 bodies are so different, __________.",
    "correct": "the effects of the medicine will vary",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "It didn\u2019t rain all summer, __________.",
    "correct": "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
    "options": [
      "so economic growth was rapid",
      "and Jim thought it was a divine message",
      "people call it a paradise",
      "the effects of the medicine will vary",
      "and she looked at his palate",
      "and she smelled the aroma of cookies",
      "so they combined the chemicals",
      "because it has a subtle taste of chocolate",
      "but I wanted my own beverage",
      "but the condensed version was shorter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thorn",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a sharp part on a plant",
      "a captain on a ship",
      "someone who serves food",
      "a piece of wood that moves a boat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "arc",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a thin rop",
      "a part of your mind",
      "a circle in a rope",
      "a curved shape"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "raft",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a waiter",
      "an undesirable event",
      "on fire",
      "a floating platform"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hay",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "oil",
      "dry grass",
      "a piece of wood in the ground",
      "a fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "character",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "where something is bought",
      "personality",
      "difficulties",
      "skin and muscle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a piece of wood in the ground",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "admiral",
      "flesh",
      "stake",
      "loop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "frightened",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wrecked",
      "horrified",
      "fiery",
      "sour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a curved shape",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "arc",
      "hay",
      "kerosene",
      "string"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "part of your mind that stops you from doing bad things",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "character",
      "conscience",
      "accident",
      "steward"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something you use to move a boat",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "thorn",
      "raft",
      "grapefruit",
      "paddle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Tom was promoted, and now he is an ",
    "correct": "admiral"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some people thought that the meal was too ",
    "correct": "sour"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The oil in lamps and stoves",
    "correct": "Kerosene"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Why did you steal the woman\u2019s bag? Don\u2019t you have a ",
    "correct": "conscience"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Can you buy three ",
    "correct": "grapefruits"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I hope that the ",
    "correct": "steward"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After lightning struck the tree, the forest turned into a ",
    "correct": "fiery"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Use this ",
    "correct": "string"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I cleaned the rabbit\u2019s cage and left some ",
    "correct": "hay"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I threw the ball through the ",
    "correct": "hoop"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I had the __________ of going with them or staying home. I felt like an __________ for the choice I made.",
    "options": [
      "idiot",
      "option"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "option",
      "idiot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because he liked to __________ the kitten by pouring water on it, the boy\u2019s mother __________ him for his cruel behavior.",
    "options": [
      "admonished",
      "torment"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "torment",
      "admonished"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "It was difficult to __________ the dog\u2019s location because its cries __________ off of the hills.",
    "options": [
      "echoed",
      "pinpoint"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "pinpoint",
      "echoed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My sister likes to __________ about how my mother and father think her behavior is __________.",
    "options": [
      "brag",
      "perfect"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "brag",
      "perfect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When you __________ the machine on, you need to __________ because the machine is dangerous.",
    "options": [
      "beware",
      "switch"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "switch",
      "beware"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "All of the accidents at the swimming pool led to the __________ closing of it and the end of a favorite summer __________.",
    "options": [
      "eventual",
      "pastime"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "eventual",
      "pastime"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The king wanted people to think that his power was __________. He would put people in jail if they __________ with him.",
    "options": [
      "disagreed",
      "awesome"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "awesome",
      "disagreed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Even though the little girl was trying to sneak up on her parents, her __________ steps made her parents __________ of her.",
    "options": [
      "audible",
      "conscious"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "audible \/conscious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "An __________ tree fell across the road, forcing the travelers to take a more __________ route through the countryside.",
    "options": [
      "immense",
      "indirect"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "immense",
      "indirect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The police could not find a single clue to the crime, which gave a __________ as to how __________ the thief had been.",
    "options": [
      "hint",
      "thorough"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hint",
      "thorough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "You should beware  __________.",
    "correct": "of the hole in the bridge",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My favorite pastime  __________.",
    "correct": "is listening to music",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The doctor did a thorough check __________.",
    "correct": "of the sick man\u00e2\u0080\u0099s health",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The two friends disagreed __________.",
    "correct": "about which game was better",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She switched the bag __________.",
    "correct": "from her left hand to her right",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "His proud sister brags __________.",
    "correct": "about how good she is at sports",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "An immense pile of garbage __________.",
    "correct": "was the reason for the bad smell",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The indirect route __________.",
    "correct": "took an hour more to drive",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The awesome storm caused __________.",
    "correct": "fear that his home would be damaged",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She admonished the student __________.",
    "correct": "for talking during the test",
    "options": [
      "about which game was better",
      "of the hole in the bridge",
      "for talking during the test",
      "was the reason for the bad smell",
      "about how good she is at sports",
      "of the sick man\u2019s health",
      "took an hour more to drive",
      "fear that his home would be damaged",
      "from her left hand to her right",
      "is listening to music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He couldn\u2019t sleep at night __________.",
    "correct": "because bad dreams tormented him",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "We knew he broke his leg when he fell __________.",
    "correct": "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He had to choose the blue car __________.",
    "correct": "because there weren\u00e2\u0080\u0099t any other options",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The hiker always carried a compass and map, __________.",
    "correct": "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She didn\u2019t eat good food and didn\u2019t exercise, __________.",
    "correct": "and it led to her eventual illness",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The students had to answer all the questions correctly __________.",
    "correct": "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The captain did not see the ship approaching behind him, __________.",
    "correct": "but he was conscious of the other boats",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She thought someone was calling to her from the other cliff, __________.",
    "correct": "but it was just the echo of her voice",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He knew his friends were having a surprise party for him __________.",
    "correct": "because they gave him so many hints",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "If you can\u2019t tie your own shoes by the time you\u2019re twelve years old __________.",
    "correct": "then people might think you\u00e2\u0080\u0099re an idiot",
    "options": [
      "and it led to her eventual illness",
      "because they gave him so many hints",
      "if they wanted to get a perfect grade",
      "but he was conscious of the other boats",
      "because bad dreams tormented him",
      "then people might think you\u2019re an idiot",
      "but it was just the echo of her voice",
      "because there weren\u2019t any other options",
      "so he could pinpoint his location in the wild",
      "because the sound of the bone breaking was audible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a sad movie cause people to do?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "To weep",
      "To except",
      "To perish",
      "To disapprove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would a bird build a home?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "On a rim",
      "In a pit",
      "On a roost",
      "On a flight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word best describes a wet towel?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Immoral",
      "Damp",
      "Trivial",
      "Fond"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean to fly?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "To soar",
      "To moan",
      "To be oblivious",
      "To be typical"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word would best describe a smooth, wet stone?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Ivy",
      "Utterly",
      "Slippery",
      "Immoral"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word describes something that would have a rim?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A thought",
      "A cup",
      "A person",
      "A smell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word describes something that has a beak?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A bird",
      "A boat",
      "A car",
      "A lion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is typical about fish?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "They can swim.",
      "One type can sing.",
      "They can live on land.",
      "Some can live for close to 50 years."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these people would most likely be moaning?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A doctor",
      "A happy boy",
      "A wife",
      "A hurt woman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which person has been proven to have committed an immoral act?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A teacher",
      "A criminal",
      "A judge",
      "A fireman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "All of the people in the movie will __________ if they remain __________ of the monster.",
    "options": [
      "oblivious",
      "perish"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "perish",
      "oblivious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When the owl wants to make a __________ , it is __________ of using an empty barn.",
    "options": [
      "roost",
      "fond"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "roost",
      "fond"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He grabbed the can by its __________ , then tossed it far down into the __________.",
    "options": [
      "pit",
      "rim"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rim",
      "pit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The eagle __________ into the clouds when it goes on a long __________.",
    "options": [
      "flight",
      "soars"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "soars",
      "flight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Every time the sick woman would __________ in pain, her daughter would __________.",
    "options": [
      "moan",
      "weep"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "moan",
      "weep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "It is not __________ for a policeman to do __________ things like stealing.",
    "options": [
      "immoral",
      "typical"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "typical",
      "immoral"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": " Every part of the bird was beautiful, __________ for its short, ugly __________.",
    "options": [
      "beak",
      "except"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "except",
      "beak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because his assistant is teaching them __________ plays, the coach will __________ of the time wasted.",
    "options": [
      "trivial",
      "disapprove"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "trivial",
      "disapprove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Because it __________ covered the fence, the gardener had to remove all of the __________.",
    "options": [
      "utterly",
      "ivy"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "utterly",
      "ivy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The ground became dangerous and __________ because everyone placed their __________ towels there.",
    "options": [
      "slippery",
      "damp"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "slippery",
      "damp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "If you know how to __________ a computer, you can get access to __________.",
    "options": [
      "cyberspace",
      "operate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "operate",
      "cyberspace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A __________ study shows that __________ hunger is a very big problem.",
    "options": [
      "recent",
      "global"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "recent",
      "global"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My mom is completely __________ about computers. She thinks that email and chat rooms are __________ ways to spend one\u2019s time.",
    "options": [
      "weird",
      "ignorant"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ignorant",
      "weird"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Joe has the ability to write great __________. His writing is so good that he never has to __________ his work.",
    "options": [
      "essays",
      "edit"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "essays",
      "edit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The report is due at the end of the __________. You should look in the __________ to see if this book will help you with the report.",
    "options": [
      "semester",
      "index"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "semester",
      "index"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Our teacher __________ while she was giving us a __________ about health!",
    "options": [
      "fainted",
      "lecture"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fainted",
      "lecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Jennifer\u2019s notes are very neat! They are __________, and she has __________ the most important parts with a green pen.",
    "options": [
      "highlighted",
      "typewritten"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "typewritten",
      "highlighted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I made a __________ to go to the __________ more often to improve my health.",
    "options": [
      "gymnasium",
      "resolution"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "resolution",
      "gymnasium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of the story is that you should think __________ before saying anything that might hurt someone.",
    "options": [
      "moral",
      "awhile"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "moral",
      "awhile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We __________ the company, and our suggestions are written in this __________ document.",
    "options": [
      "evaluated",
      "private"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "evaluated",
      "private"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The team evaluated __________.",
    "correct": "the success of the project",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The moral of the story is __________.",
    "correct": "to be nicer to people",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The global economic problems __________.",
    "correct": "are getting worse",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Joe operates __________.",
    "correct": "this large machine",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "We went to a lecture __________.",
    "correct": "about birds",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The friends you meet in cyberspace __________.",
    "correct": "aren\u00e2\u0080\u0099t as important as real friends",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The weird kid at school __________.",
    "correct": "ate soup with a knife",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "You should highlight these words __________.",
    "correct": "with a yellow pen",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I made a resolution __________.",
    "correct": "to eat less chocolate",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The end of the first semester __________.",
    "correct": "is halfway through the school year",
    "options": [
      "are getting worse",
      "aren\u2019t as important as real friends",
      "about birds",
      "is halfway through the school year",
      "to be nicer to people",
      "to eat less chocolate",
      "the success of the project",
      "with a yellow pen",
      "this large machine",
      "ate soup with a knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I wanted to get fit __________.",
    "correct": "so I went to the gymnasium",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Geology is my favorite subject, __________.",
    "correct": "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My paper was full of mistakes, __________.",
    "correct": "but he helped me edit it",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My brother couldn\u2019t help me with my math homework __________.",
    "correct": "because he\u00e2\u0080\u0099s ignorant about math",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "In the first aid class, we learned what to do __________.",
    "correct": "if someone faints",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I wanted to find some information about volcanoes, __________.",
    "correct": "so I looked under \u00e2\u0080\u009cV\u00e2\u0080\u009d in the index",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "That copy of the text book is too old, __________.",
    "correct": "so you should find a more recent one",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I need a computer __________.",
    "correct": "because my essay has to be typewritten",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I\u2019ll get some tea if __________.",
    "correct": "you wait here awhile",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "You mustn\u2019t tell anyone this information; __________.",
    "correct": "it\u00e2\u0080\u0099s private",
    "options": [
      "it\u2019s private",
      "so I looked under \u201cV\u201d in the index",
      "but he helped me edit it",
      "you wait here awhile",
      "so I went to the gymnasium",
      "so you should find a more recent one",
      "so I wrote an essay about rocks",
      "because my essay has to be typewritten",
      "if someone faints",
      "because he\u2019s ignorant about math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a set of clothes",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "spirit",
      "suit",
      "recipe",
      "rail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "common people",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "folk",
      "pleasure",
      "absolute",
      "attentive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to get smaller",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "melt",
      "pop",
      "shrink",
      "envision"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a large cloth worn on the back",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "patch",
      "cape",
      "spark",
      "role"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "happening at the same rate everywhere",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "evenly",
      "alas",
      "soaks",
      "pudding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "melt",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to get smaller",
      "to turn to liquid",
      "to make wet",
      "to imagine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spark",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a flash of fire",
      "a set of clothes",
      "a sweet dessert",
      "a set of instructions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rail",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a horizontal bar",
      "a common person",
      "a normal purpose",
      "a different part of a surface"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "absolute",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "said when bad things happen",
      "careful",
      "happening at the same rate",
      "total and complete"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pleasure",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to make a noise",
      "to get smaller",
      "a feeling of happiness",
      "personality"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Mom made chocolate pudding __________.",
    "correct": "for dessert last night",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He is very attentive __________.",
    "correct": "during science class",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "People wore capes more often __________.",
    "correct": "two hundred years ago",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "His strong spirit __________.",
    "correct": "could not be hurt from mean comments",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I can\u2019t envision you __________.",
    "correct": "as a politician",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "It was a pleasure __________.",
    "correct": "to meet you",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "His role at work is __________.",
    "correct": "to manage the team of employees",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The cat is sitting on the rail __________.",
    "correct": "of the fence",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "For this recipe, I will need __________.",
    "correct": "flour, eggs and sugar",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "There were sparks flying __________.",
    "correct": "out of the computer",
    "options": [
      "of the fence",
      "two hundred years ago",
      "during science class",
      "to manage the team of employees",
      "flour, eggs and sugar",
      "as a politician",
      "for dessert last night",
      "out of the computer",
      "to meet you",
      "could not be hurt from mean comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "If you wash this silk shirt in hot water, __________.",
    "correct": "it will shrink",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Tony didn\u2019t practice the presentation, __________.",
    "correct": "so it was an absolute disaster",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I studied hard for the test, __________.",
    "correct": "but alas, I still didn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t do very well",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Dan was very unlucky __________.",
    "correct": "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Christmas is an important holiday __________.",
    "correct": "when folks meet with their families",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "If you put the butter near the fire, __________.",
    "correct": "it will melt",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "This pan was so dirty __________.",
    "correct": "that I had to soak it overnight",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "To protect the kingdom, __________.",
    "correct": "the soldiers spread out evenly",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I knew the television had broken __________.",
    "correct": "when I heard the pop",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "At work, we have to dress well, __________.",
    "correct": "so I usually wear a suit",
    "options": [
      "the soldiers spread out evenly",
      "because he fell in a patch of rocks",
      "so it was an absolute disaster",
      "it will melt",
      "it will shrink",
      "when folks meet with their families",
      "so I usually wear a suit",
      "that I had to soak it overnight",
      "when I heard the pop",
      "but alas, I still didn\u2019t do very well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to work to correct a problem between two people",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "oblige",
      "intervene",
      "conceal",
      "volunteer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "allowed by the law",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "legal",
      "offense",
      "memorable",
      "gratitude"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to find a solution",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "proclaim",
      "sentence",
      "resolve",
      "rally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an object that helps people remember a place",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "witness",
      "landmark",
      "account",
      "resource"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "something a person does that can be punished by law",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "architect",
      "deed",
      "habitat",
      "crime"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "memorable",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "natural",
      "thankful",
      "special",
      "public"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "witness",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a designer of buildings",
      "an important person",
      "someone who obeys the law",
      "a person who sees a crime"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "deed",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "money and materials",
      "proof of ownership",
      "a natural home",
      "an action that breaks the law"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sentence",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a punishment for a crime",
      "an object that helps people",
      "something against the law",
      "a large public meeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "proclaim",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to hide something",
      "to offer to help",
      "to say in public",
      "to stop a problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is most likely a habitat?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A pond",
      "A bridge",
      "A broom",
      "A picture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When something is concealed, what is it called?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Loud",
      "Colorful",
      "Hidden",
      "Quick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that an architect makes?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A law",
      "A house",
      "A cake",
      "A dress"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT legal?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Swimming",
      "Singing",
      "Crying",
      "Stealing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is someone who feels gratitude most likely to say?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "\u201cHello.\u201d",
      "\u201cI\u2019m sorry.\u201d",
      "\u201cGo away.\u201d",
      "\u201cThankyou.\u201d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The government has enough ",
    "correct": "resources"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The town had a ",
    "correct": "rally"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The necklace was ",
    "correct": "memorable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His ",
    "correct": "offense"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She had iust enough money in her ",
    "correct": "account"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Children are ",
    "correct": "obliged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My uncle ",
    "correct": "proclaimed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Four students ",
    "correct": "volunteered"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A bear\u2019s ",
    "correct": "habitat"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was filled with ",
    "correct": "gratitude"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Mr. Holloway was sent to __________ the old coach, who was known for his wild __________ during games.",
    "options": [
      "conduct",
      "replace"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "replace",
      "conduct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Decisions made in courts are often __________ by the personal views of the judge. In some cases, the decisions help change __________.",
    "options": [
      "influenced",
      "laws"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "influenced",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I __________ the pencil and squeezed it until it __________.",
    "options": [
      "gripped",
      "snapped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "gripped",
      "snapped"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My father __________ a check in the letter he sent me. He always offered to help even if I didn\u2019t ask for any help __________.",
    "options": [
      "whatsoever",
      "enclosed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "enclosed",
      "whatsoever"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The soldier dreaded the __________ battle. He __________ thought about what might happen to him.",
    "options": [
      "constantly",
      "impending"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "impending",
      "constantly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I saw several __________ in the ice. This __________ to happen when the weather becomes warmer.",
    "options": [
      "tends",
      "cracks"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cracks",
      "tends"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Sheila took the __________ from her purse and pressed a couple of buttons. It took her awhile to figure out how to turn it to silent __________.",
    "options": [
      "device",
      "mode"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "device",
      "mode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She ran from room to room quickly, but __________ suddenly. She couldn\u2019t have __________ to the room without a key.",
    "options": [
      "halt",
      "access"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "halted",
      "access"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The student had a __________ reason for leaving the classroom when his teacher was gone. He tried to explain his __________ of what happened while she was gone.",
    "options": [
      "valid",
      "version"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "valid",
      "version"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The thief __________ while the police questioned him. They didn\u2019t feel sorry for the __________ crimminal.",
    "options": [
      "sly",
      "perspired"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "perspired",
      "sly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Scientists have a device that helps __________.",
    "correct": "them tell how old an object is",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The driver gripped the wheel __________.",
    "correct": "as she turned around the corner",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I always perspire more often __________.",
    "correct": "in the summer",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The concert halted __________.",
    "correct": "when the electricity went out",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The sly boy took a cookie while __________.",
    "correct": "his mother wasn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t watching him",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My father replaced the old __________.",
    "correct": "light bulb with a new one",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He had a valid reason __________.",
    "correct": "to miss school today",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I snapped the toy __________.",
    "correct": "by holding it too tightly",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The teacher tends to give the best grades to __________.",
    "correct": "students who do all of their homework",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I got no joy whatsoever from getting __________.",
    "correct": "my brother in trouble",
    "options": [
      "as she turned around the corner",
      "when the electricity went out",
      "by holding it too tightly",
      "light bulb with a new one",
      "in the summer",
      "them tell how old an object is",
      "to miss school today",
      "students who do all of their homework",
      "my brother in trouble",
      "his mother wasn\u2019t watching him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He didn\u2019t understand, __________.",
    "correct": "so they told him a different version",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He was told to behave, __________.",
    "correct": "so his conduct was excellent",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Joe was such a bad person __________.",
    "correct": "that he broke every law",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "To keep the jewels safe, __________.",
    "correct": "it was enclosed in glass",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Be careful __________.",
    "correct": "because he can influence people to do anything",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Mark tried the code, __________.",
    "correct": "but he wasn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t given access to the room",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She practices the violin during the day, __________.",
    "correct": "so the constant music wouldn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t annoy the neighbors",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He studied hard __________.",
    "correct": "because the impeding test was so important",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She turned her phone off, __________.",
    "correct": "so the mode wouldn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t disturb anyone",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He replaced the glass __________.",
    "correct": "because there were cracks in it",
    "options": [
      "but he wasn\u2019t given access to the room",
      "because he can influence people to do anything",
      "because the impeding test was so important",
      "so the constant music wouldn\u2019t annoy the neighbors",
      "that he broke every law",
      "it was enclosed in glass",
      "because there were cracks in it",
      "so they told him a different version",
      "so his conduct was excellent",
      "so the mode wouldn\u2019t disturb anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a gentle wind",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "breeze",
      "appetite",
      "subject",
      "display"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "money for a job",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "rumor",
      "forgive",
      "wage",
      "whereas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "big and beautiful",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "feeble",
      "majestic",
      "efficient",
      "outraged"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "full of energy",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "lively",
      "nor",
      "pessimistic",
      "alongside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "used to show how two things are different",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "alongside",
      "smash",
      "defy",
      "whereas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pessimistic",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to show something",
      "believing that something bad will happen",
      "full of energy",
      "large and beautiful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "slap",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to hit someone",
      "to break something",
      "to be beside",
      "to be small or weak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rumor",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to pay",
      "to become windy",
      "to be a sign",
      "an unproven story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outraged",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "angry",
      "connecting two ideas",
      "showing contrast",
      "believing something bad will happen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "defy",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hunger",
      "to stop being angry",
      "helping someone",
      "to go against"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "lim walks to school ",
    "correct": "alongside"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I needed Jamie to ",
    "correct": "assist"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "rumor"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I spend all my ",
    "correct": "wages"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The chair ",
    "correct": "smashed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Bob is ",
    "correct": "feeble"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My new car is ",
    "correct": "efficient"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My favorite ",
    "correct": "subject"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She was ",
    "correct": "outraged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I ",
    "correct": "forgave"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following connects two negative ideas?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A breeze",
      "Nor",
      "Defy",
      "An outrage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a positive way to describe someone?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Forgive",
      "Pessimistic",
      "Lively",
      "Feeble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What can you study in school?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A breeze",
      "A subject",
      "A wage",
      "An outrage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What controls how much you eat?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Your appetite",
      "Your subject",
      "Your herald",
      "An efficient mouth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are showing something, what are you doing?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Assist",
      "Displaying it",
      "Slapped",
      "Smashed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a formal inspection",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "review",
      "diagram",
      "plea",
      "longing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to accept the truth",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "isolate",
      "classify",
      "construct",
      "concede"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an idea about how something is",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "decade",
      "ferry",
      "concept",
      "particle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "knowing a lot about the world",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "upright",
      "sophisticated",
      "handy",
      "surrender"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "important",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "refrain",
      "numerous",
      "worthwhile",
      "animate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "particle",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a small piece of something",
      "a drawing",
      "a formal inspection",
      "a strong feeling of want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "decade",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "an idea about something",
      "a period often years",
      "a type of boat",
      "a thing that has life"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "upright",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "important",
      "to not do something",
      "standing straight",
      "a request"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "isolate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to separate",
      "to group together by type",
      "to give up",
      "to accept the truth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "handy",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to make something",
      "common",
      "plentiful",
      "useful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Scientists thought that the tiny __________ was not a living thing, so they were very surprised to find that it was indeed __________.",
    "options": [
      "animate",
      "particle"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "particle",
      "animate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My uncle, the carpenter, keeps __________ tools in his truck. However, he keeps the most __________ ones on his tool belt at all times.",
    "options": [
      "handy",
      "numerous"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "numerous",
      "handy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "One way that scientists __________ the different species of early humans is by how they walked. Homo Erectus, for example, walked __________.",
    "options": [
      "classify",
      "upright"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "classify",
      "upright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After sitting in the cell for just one hour, the prisoner felt a __________ to be free. He made a __________ to the officers to release him immediately.",
    "options": [
      "longing",
      "plea"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "longing",
      "plea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Learning how to speak another language is a __________ skill to have in the world of international business. It also can make one into a more __________ person.",
    "options": [
      "sophisticated",
      "worthwhile"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "worthwhile",
      "sophisticated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Jack had a great __________ for a new system, but his boss needs to conduct a thorough __________ to see if it will work.",
    "options": [
      "review",
      "concept"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "concept",
      "review"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "William used a piece of white paper to __________ the different plants in the garden. That made it easier for him to draw a __________ of the leaves of each type of plant.",
    "options": [
      "diagram",
      "isolate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "isolate",
      "diagram"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The great pyramids of Egypt were not __________ overnight. In fact, it took many ___________ to complete them.",
    "options": [
      "constructed",
      "decades"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "constructed",
      "decades"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "As he drove his car onto the __________, John felt sad. He wanted to travel by airplane, but after looking at ticket prices, he had to __________ that air travel was just too expensive.",
    "options": [
      "concede",
      "ferry"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ferry",
      "concede"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In maintaining good health, it is important to __________ from eating unhealthy foods. But that doesn\u2019t mean you must __________ all of the foods that you enjoy.",
    "options": [
      "refrain",
      "surrender"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "refrain",
      "surrender"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to provide the things that someone needs to do something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "sort",
      "enchant",
      "equip",
      "lure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a safe place",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "genre",
      "shelter",
      "defense",
      "culture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "holding a weapon",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "authoritative",
      "vain",
      "diverse",
      "armed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pieces of information",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "details",
      "impacts",
      "applause",
      "supplies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a group working together",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ceremony",
      "alliance",
      "exception",
      "obstacle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Please ",
    "correct": "sort"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Everybody was ",
    "correct": "enchanted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The performer heard great ",
    "correct": "applause"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Tim takes a long time to get ready because he is so ",
    "correct": "vain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Ocean life is ",
    "correct": "diverse"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "What is your favorite ",
    "correct": "genre"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "ceremony"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The city\u2019s only ",
    "correct": "defense"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Ben went through many ",
    "correct": "obstacles"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Most girls like to play with dolls, but Samantha is the ",
    "correct": "exception"
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I\u2019m going to try to lure my friends __________.",
    "correct": "into coming to the museum with me",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Sort the pieces __________.",
    "correct": "into three equal groups",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The biggest obstacle Mary faced __________.",
    "correct": "was not being able to read very well",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The genre of abstract art __________.",
    "correct": "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The awards ceremony is __________.",
    "correct": "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Mexican culture is __________.",
    "correct": "known for its interesting folk art",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The best defense against skin cancer __________.",
    "correct": "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The students were equipped __________.",
    "correct": "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "An armed man ran into __________.",
    "correct": "the jewelry store and stole diamonds",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The vain woman could __________.",
    "correct": "talk about herself for hours and hours",
    "options": [
      "was popularized by artists like Picasso and Dali",
      "is to wear a lot of sunscreen",
      "with pencils, scissors, and a lot of glue",
      "known for its interesting folk art",
      "into coming to the museum with me",
      "tonight at the Royal Crown Hotel",
      "talk about herself for hours and hours",
      "into three equal groups",
      "was not being able to read very well",
      "the jewelry store and stole diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "It started raining really hard, __________.",
    "correct": "so we ran inside for shelter",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He saw that the children were cold, __________.",
    "correct": "so he supplied them with blankets",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Police officers work very hard, __________.",
    "correct": "and officer Jones is no exception",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Everyone always trusts Seth __________.",
    "correct": "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Mother Teresa was a very well-known person, __________.",
    "correct": "and her work impacted many lives",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He only likes one type of music, __________.",
    "correct": "but I like a diverse selection",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "James tried to write the report last night, __________.",
    "correct": "but it had so many details that he couldn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t finish",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I don\u2019t really like Jennifer, __________.",
    "correct": "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Bob and Eric both want to beat James at the game, __________.",
    "correct": "so they will form an alliance",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The performer did a great job, __________.",
    "correct": "and the crowd gave him great applause",
    "options": [
      "and officer Jones is no exception",
      "and her work impacted many lives",
      "but everyone else is enchanted by her",
      "but I like a diverse selection",
      "so we ran inside for shelter",
      "so they will form an alliance",
      "and the crowd gave him great applause",
      "so he supplied them with blankets",
      "but it had so many details that he couldn\u2019t finish",
      "because he sounds authoritative when he speaks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "It was bad that the man had a lot of __________ because he used it to cause __________.",
    "options": [
      "muscle",
      "violence"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "muscles",
      "violence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He had a __________ to win the race, but he had to quit when he got a bad pain in his __________.",
    "options": [
      "belly",
      "bid"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bid",
      "belly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy was always __________ because his classmates were mean and treated him with __________.",
    "options": [
      "disrespect",
      "timid"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "timid",
      "disrespect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy had a lot of __________ before his trip to Europe. He had never been to a different __________ before.",
    "options": [
      "continent",
      "enthusiasm"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "enthusiasm",
      "continent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The movie will start soon. In the __________, help me to __________ these heavy boards against the wall.",
    "options": [
      "lean",
      "meantime"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "meantime",
      "lean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ that the man wanted to drive on was blocked, so he found an __________ route.",
    "options": [
      "alternative",
      "avenue"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "avenue",
      "alternative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The police officer had to __________ the woman from a bad __________ she had with another woman.",
    "options": [
      "conflict",
      "rescue"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rescue",
      "conflict"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl walked along the rough beach. The rocky __________ was __________ on her feet.",
    "options": [
      "harsh",
      "terrain"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "terrain",
      "harsh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boys were up to their usual __________ and were throwing balls of paper at each other in __________.",
    "options": [
      "mischief",
      "succession"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mischief",
      "succession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I turned on the fan so that it would __________ air on me. The __________ of cool air felt wonderful.",
    "options": [
      "current",
      "blow"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "blow",
      "current"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Australia is an island that is also the smallest ",
    "correct": "continent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "terrain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The pitcher threw the balls to home plate in ",
    "correct": "succession"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The student left for school early. She had to walk down an ",
    "correct": "avenue"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Brian was tired. He needed to ",
    "correct": "lean"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The student decided that the answer was A and not the ",
    "correct": "alternative"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The river\u2019s fast ",
    "correct": "current"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He talked about US history, and the pupils wrote notes in the ",
    "correct": "meantime"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The dog continued barking. The loud noise was ",
    "correct": "harsh"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boys used ",
    "correct": "violence"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word best describes a student who is very happy and excited?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Enthusiasm",
      "Violence",
      "Current",
      "Alternative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following describes a scared person best?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Timid",
      "Disrespect",
      "Muscle",
      "Succession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that can be soft and round?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Something in the meantime",
      "An avenue",
      "A person\u2019s belly",
      "A continent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word best describes behavior meant to trick or cause trouble?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Mischief",
      "Conflict",
      "Terrain",
      "Harsh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the action of the wind?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "It bids.",
      "It rescues.",
      "It blows.",
      "It leans."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "irritable",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to please",
      "to get angry easily",
      "having a routine",
      "healthy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "zoom",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to move quickly",
      "dangerous",
      "healthy",
      "to attract"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "subconscious",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "not aware",
      "handwritten",
      "bad dream",
      "pleasing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "charm",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to please",
      "to make a noise",
      "to exercise",
      "to influence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "brew",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to make coffee",
      "to move slowly",
      "to have a routine",
      "to attract"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mary asked for the singer\u2019s ",
    "correct": "autograph"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He isn\u2019t allowed to watch scary movies because they give him ",
    "correct": "nightmares"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Push everything to one side to ",
    "correct": "maximize"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He borrowed a ",
    "correct": "van"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Ellen wanted to get to the gym and try a new ",
    "correct": "workout"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Harriet doesn\u2019t like talking to Jesse when he\u2019s ",
    "correct": "irritable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The cars honked their ",
    "correct": "horn"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "If you don\u2019t start trying harder, you will ",
    "correct": "lag"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The sign ",
    "correct": "warns"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mother cooks me a ",
    "correct": "nutritious"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "This is a good source of protein?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Vegetables",
      "Tea",
      "Beef",
      "Sugar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Stuff can be best described as what?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Sports equipment",
      "A collection of unnamed things",
      "A computer",
      "Socks and shoes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the most nutritious snack below?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "An apple",
      "French fries",
      "A candy bar",
      "Ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something you might put your signature on?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A business letter",
      "A birthday cake",
      "Your hand",
      "The water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you lag behind your friends, you ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "are slower than them",
      "are heavier than them",
      "wait for them",
      "don\u2019t care about them"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What are things that happen and will happen in a person\u2019s life?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Their workout",
      "Their destiny",
      "Their stuff",
      "Their autograph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is similar to a small truck?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A van",
      "A horn",
      "A charm",
      "A lag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a small drop of water called?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Bead",
      "Signature",
      "Protein",
      "Nutritious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean to have influence over something?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "To charm",
      "To maximize",
      "To brew",
      "To affect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What are fire alarms meant to do?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Make people irritable",
      "Give children nightmares",
      "Warn people",
      "Zoom past people"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ruin",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to damage",
      "to hate",
      "to fly",
      "to cook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "brick",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a fast car",
      "a hard piece of clay",
      "a best friend",
      "a favorite kind of toy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sprinkle",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to scatter",
      "to create",
      "to mend",
      "to agree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "injure",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to run",
      "to fall",
      "to hurt",
      "to roast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "slight",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "growing",
      "minor",
      "quick",
      "risky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would a man show others an emotion?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "By flushing it",
      "By injuring it",
      "By ruining it",
      "By expressing it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following says that two former enemies become friends again?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "To reconcile",
      "To shatter",
      "To utter",
      "To sparkle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you describe a girl who can stretch her leg behind her head?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A little bit stale",
      "Very flexible",
      "More than slight",
      "Ready to crumble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these would you use to make bread?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A brick",
      "Some dough",
      "A fist",
      "A lump"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word describes something usually found on windows?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Mixture",
      "Crumble",
      "Slight",
      "Shutters"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Before the project, the clay was one big __________. But when he was finished, he made a perfectly square __________.",
    "options": [
      "brick",
      "lump"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lump",
      "brick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Five minutes ago, the two senators were __________ insults at each other, but now they have __________ because they both agree with the new law.",
    "options": [
      "reconciled",
      "uttering"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "uttering",
      "reconciled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In the middle of the night, she got out of bed and opened the __________. She gazed at the sky where the stars __________ like tiny fires.",
    "options": [
      "shutters",
      "sparkled"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "shutters \/sparkled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The rice was not eaten soon enough, so it tasted __________. It made me feel sick and my face became __________.",
    "options": [
      "flushed",
      "stale"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "stale",
      "flushed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The cook picked up the block of cheese and __________ it into little pieces. Then he mixed them with the __________ before placing it in the oven.",
    "options": [
      "crumbled",
      "dough"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "crumbled",
      "dough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When he started to __________ the flour into the bowl, he slipped and dropped it. The bowl hit the ground and __________.",
    "options": [
      "sift",
      "shattered"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sift",
      "shattered"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He hit the punching bag with his __________. Since the bag was __________, it did not break.",
    "options": [
      "fist",
      "flexible"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fist",
      "flexible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of ice cream and chocolate tastes good, but it will be even better if you __________ sugar on the top of it.",
    "options": [
      "sprinkle",
      "mixture"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mixture",
      "sprinkle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The doctor __________ a lot of concern for my hurt ankle, but I told him the pain was only __________.",
    "options": [
      "slight",
      "expressed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "expressed",
      "slight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The ship was __________ when it crashed into the island. Even though it was greatly damaged, none of the passengers were __________.",
    "options": [
      "ruined",
      "injured"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "ruined",
      "injured"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After weeks of hard work, the scientists must __________ the results of their __________.",
    "options": [
      "research",
      "await"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "await",
      "research"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After the death of her __________ pet, the woman felt nothing but __________ for many weeks.",
    "options": [
      "misery",
      "beloved"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "beloved",
      "misery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The store had a __________ of canned vegetables, but the man __________ that they didn\u2019t have his favorite brand.",
    "options": [
      "complained",
      "variety"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "variety",
      "complained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The new schedule __________ passengers who thought the train was __________ at 8 a.m.",
    "options": [
      "due",
      "confused"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "confused",
      "due"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The island was a great place to __________ a hotel since the __________ was warm throughout the year.",
    "options": [
      "climate",
      "establish"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "establish",
      "climate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "__________ he had a lot of bad luck in the past, he refused to let __________ events stop him from moving forward.",
    "options": [
      "although",
      "prior"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "Although",
      "prior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ was turned up to the highest temperature, but it couldn\u2019t heat the __________ room.",
    "options": [
      "furnace",
      "entire"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "furnace \/entire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In the __________ of a terrible war, the young boys had to __________ quickly.",
    "options": [
      "mature",
      "midst"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "midst",
      "mature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "To make sure the dog\u2019s __________ was long enough, Bob took out a ruler and __________ it.",
    "options": [
      "measured",
      "leash"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "leash",
      "measured"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She insisted that they __________ her mother\u2019s favorite perfume before they __________ her.",
    "options": [
      "buried",
      "apply"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "apply",
      "buried"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Although he didn\u2019t know how to dance, __________.",
    "correct": "he went to the party anyway",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A furnace keeps __________.",
    "correct": "a room warm during the winter",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Florida\u2019s warm climate makes __________.",
    "correct": "many travelers want to vacation there",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He wanted to establish __________.",
    "correct": "a school for blind children",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The train was due to arrive at __________.",
    "correct": "around seven in the morning",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A lot of research is needed __________.",
    "correct": "before new medicines can be created",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Shoppers have a variety of __________.",
    "correct": "food to choose from at the store",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "In the midst of the game __________.",
    "correct": "the team\u00e2\u0080\u0099s best player had to be replaced",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A leash keeps __________.",
    "correct": "a dog from running away",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Her beloved sister __________.",
    "correct": "always calmed her",
    "options": [
      "he went to the party anyway",
      "before new medicines can be created",
      "a school for blind children",
      "a room warm during the winter",
      "a dog from running away",
      "many travelers want to vacation there",
      "always calmed her",
      "the team\u2019s best player had to be replaced",
      "around seven in the morning",
      "food to choose from at the store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "To determine if the new drug was safe, __________.",
    "correct": "scientists measured all the effects",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "His newest book did not sell well, __________.",
    "correct": "but his prior works were very successful",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He wanted to finish the race, __________.",
    "correct": "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He lost his map, __________.",
    "correct": "so he became confused",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The soup was cold, __________.",
    "correct": "so the diners complained to the waiter",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Sue was very silly as a child, __________.",
    "correct": "but she became more serious as she matured",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "No one could find the treasure __________.",
    "correct": "because the pirate had buried it",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He said he would write to her, __________.",
    "correct": "so she patiently awaited his letters",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She wanted to look older, __________.",
    "correct": "so she applied makeup to her face",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "They were thirsty, __________.",
    "correct": "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
    "options": [
      "scientists measured all the effects",
      "but his prior works were very successful",
      "because the pirate had buried it",
      "so she applied makeup to her face",
      "but the pain in his ankle gave him too much misery",
      "so she patiently awaited his letters",
      "so they drank the entire bowl of punch",
      "so the diners complained to the waiter",
      "but she became more serious as she matured",
      "so he became confused"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Greg had the __________ of falling in a pool, though he didn\u2019t know how to swim. The experience left him with __________ feelings about swimming pools.",
    "options": [
      "negative",
      "misfortune"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "misfortune",
      "negative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After one day, the __________ on her lip began to go away. In a week, it had disappeared __________.",
    "options": [
      "bruise",
      "altogether"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bruise",
      "altogether"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "For the __________ of fairness, we tried to divide the pizza equally. One pizza was enough to give three slices __________ person.",
    "options": [
      "per",
      "sake"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sake",
      "per"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A woman __________ with the child to behave in the store. The child, however, continued to be __________.",
    "options": [
      "disobedient",
      "pleaded"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "pleaded",
      "disobedient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "They walked past a large river, which the guide said was the __________ of a waterfall. They finally __________ the waterfall when they reached the bottom of the hill.",
    "options": [
      "source",
      "glimpsed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "source",
      "glimpsed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The girl wanted to make her plastic __________ look pretty, so she __________ cloth around it.",
    "options": [
      "stitched",
      "hoop"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hoop",
      "stitched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The family was __________ tightly. For example, on Saturdays, it was their __________ to go to the park together.",
    "options": [
      "custom",
      "bind"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bound",
      "custom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ teacher was angry to see the students passing notes. She took the note from the students and __________ it into pieces.",
    "options": [
      "stern",
      "ripped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "stern",
      "ripped"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy lost his balance and fell with a __________. When he got up, he noticed that he\u2019d __________ his elbow.",
    "options": [
      "thump",
      "scraped"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "thump",
      "scraped"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The coach didn\u2019t __________ the loss for his team. So, after the game, he was __________.",
    "options": [
      "vehement",
      "foresee"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "foresee",
      "vehement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Kelly had the misfortune of breaking __________.",
    "correct": "her arm before the competition",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The disobedient dog ran away __________.",
    "correct": "from its owner at the park",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She felt bound to her friends because she had __________.",
    "correct": "known them fora long time",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The weatherman didn\u2019t foresee any __________.",
    "correct": "bad weather this weekend",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The family had a custom of __________.",
    "correct": "eating dinner early on Sundays",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She glimpsed at his painting __________.",
    "correct": "before it was completed",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Charlie ripped the paper in half and __________.",
    "correct": "gave one piece to his friend",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Jasmine pleaded with her teacher __________.",
    "correct": "to give her a better grade",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Leslie scraped the ice __________.",
    "correct": "off the window",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "George was vehement about being allowed __________.",
    "correct": "to use the computer",
    "options": [
      "gave one piece to his friend",
      "bad weather this weekend",
      "from its owner at the park",
      "off the window",
      "to give her a better grade",
      "known them fora long time",
      "to use the computer",
      "eating dinner early on Sundays",
      "her arm before the competition",
      "before it was completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "There was a tear in my shirt, __________.",
    "correct": "so my mom stitched it back together",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She dropped the scissors on the carpet, __________.",
    "correct": "so there was a slight thump",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "His parents were strict, __________.",
    "correct": "because stern rules built character",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The website was good, __________.",
    "correct": "but the sources were unreliable",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The fight was horrifying, __________.",
    "correct": "it filled him with negative dreams",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I enjoy soda, __________.",
    "correct": "but only 2 cans per week",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He went to school despite being sick __________.",
    "correct": "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "They used a different system __________.",
    "correct": "that was altogether different from mine",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He liked showing off, __________.",
    "correct": "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He fell down the stairs, __________.",
    "correct": "so he had bruises on his arm",
    "options": [
      "so he tried jumping through the hoop",
      "because the sake of his grade depended on it",
      "but only 2 cans per week",
      "so my mom stitched it back together",
      "so he had bruises on his arm",
      "that was altogether different from mine",
      "it filled him with negative dreams",
      "because stern rules built character",
      "so there was a slight thump",
      "but the sources were unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The box had a __________ that was very easy to open. It was a __________ place to store the young girl\u2019s toys.",
    "options": [
      "convenient",
      "lid"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "lid",
      "convenient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "When it started raining, I __________ my newspaper in half. Then I carried it over my head to __________ myself from the rain.",
    "options": [
      "shield",
      "folded"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "folded",
      "shield"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She wasn\u2019t used to spending time in an __________ setting. After only a few days, she was glad to __________ the city.",
    "options": [
      "exit",
      "urban"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "urban",
      "exit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ soldier spent three weeks alone in the forest. When he returned to __________, he was stronger than ever.",
    "options": [
      "mighty",
      "civilization"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mighty",
      "civilization"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The branches of the trees __________ as the wind blew. The wind was stronger than usual because of the __________ weather.",
    "options": [
      "stormy",
      "swayed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "swayed",
      "stormy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boys __________ to the middle of the lake. At that point, they couldn\u2019t go any further because the __________ grew too thickly.",
    "options": [
      "reeds",
      "waded"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "waded",
      "reeds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ of geese chose not to land in the field because it was still wet with __________.",
    "options": [
      "dew",
      "flock"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "flock",
      "dew"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Some plants contain __________ that can be eliminated by cooking. The cooking process results in a __________ change to the plant\u2019s chemical makeup.",
    "options": [
      "poison",
      "drastic"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "poison",
      "drastic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "There was little light inside the __________ where the bears lived. Outside, there was little plant life, just a few __________ and some small weeds.",
    "options": [
      "den",
      "mushrooms"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "den",
      "mushrooms"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ animals of the island knew how to protect themselves from bad weather. When a storm __________, they immediately ran for cover.",
    "options": [
      "native",
      "loomed"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "native",
      "loomed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The plant is filled with ",
    "correct": "poison"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The man asked for extra ",
    "correct": "mushrooms"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My socks got wet when I walked in the ",
    "correct": "dew"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Madagascar has an interesting group of ",
    "correct": "native"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boy put on a scarf to ",
    "correct": "shield"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Alyssa found a small ",
    "correct": "den"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The man ",
    "correct": "folded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The farmer traded his ",
    "correct": "flock"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I was not strong enough to lift the ",
    "correct": "lid"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After the movie was over, the audience ",
    "correct": "exit"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What word below best describes a superhero?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Mushrooms",
      "Dew",
      "Mighty",
      "Reeds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Something that is easy to do is described as what?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Drastic",
      "Convenient",
      "Poison",
      "Urban"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is an activity done in the water?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Sway",
      "Fold",
      "Exit",
      "Wade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which covers a box?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A den",
      "A lid",
      "A civilization",
      "A flock"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word fits best? Koalas are ______ to Australia.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "loom",
      "shield",
      "stormy",
      "native"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "an underground room",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "accent",
      "basement",
      "a technique",
      "errand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to think about something",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "complicate",
      "reserve",
      "ponder",
      "slam"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "the written words of a play or film",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "script",
      "blank",
      "barber",
      "gloves"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a group that sings",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "hermits",
      "leather",
      "choir",
      "staircases"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "in a fair way",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "comic",
      "decline",
      "searching",
      "justly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "slam",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to close loudly",
      "to be careful",
      "to close the eyes",
      "to save"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "decline",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to look for",
      "to say no",
      "to be right",
      "fair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hermit",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "clothing for you hands",
      "something that is funny",
      "a trip to do something",
      "a person who is alone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "leather",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a distinct way of speaking",
      "material used to make clothing",
      "an underground room",
      "a piece of clothing for the hands"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "barber",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a singing group",
      "a person who cuts hair",
      "a set of stairs",
      "phrases that form a play"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The writer\u2019s comic stories __________.",
    "correct": "always make me laugh",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Donna usually ran errands __________.",
    "correct": "right before coming home from work",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I tried to reserve __________.",
    "correct": "some seats for this week\u00e2\u0080\u0099s show",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She wanted to join the choir __________.",
    "correct": "after hearing them sing in church",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A beautiful staircase __________.",
    "correct": "led up to the second floor",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The speaker\u2019s strong accent __________.",
    "correct": "made him hard to understand",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Roger pondered a long time __________.",
    "correct": "before buying a new car",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The hermit __________.",
    "correct": "slept in small cave",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I remembered to make sure I had my gloves __________.",
    "correct": "just before I left the house",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The large basement __________.",
    "correct": "makes a great playroom",
    "options": [
      "after hearing them sing in church",
      "made him hard to understand",
      "before buying a new car",
      "some seats for this week\u2019s show",
      "always make me laugh",
      "makes a great playroom",
      "led up to the second floor",
      "slept in small cave",
      "just before I left the house",
      "right before coming home from work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I put some medicine in my eyes, __________.",
    "correct": "so I had to keep blinking them",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The boy\u2019s mom yelled at him for getting mud on the couch, __________.",
    "correct": "so he cleaned the leather couch",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He asked Sara to see the scary movie, __________.",
    "correct": "but she declined",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He spent the period daydreaming. So when he turned in his test, __________.",
    "correct": "it was completely blank",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The new play was great __________.",
    "correct": "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I didn\u2019t pay attention in class, __________.",
    "correct": "so the homework was very complicated",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My hair was a mess, __________.",
    "correct": "so I went to see the barber",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He couldn\u2019t stand the sound of the music, __________.",
    "correct": "so he left the room and slammed the door",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Dean and Anne finished the race at the same time, __________.",
    "correct": "so both were justly give medals",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He lost his glasses, __________.",
    "correct": "so he had to search for them for an hour",
    "options": [
      "because Tony spent a lot of time on the script",
      "so he cleaned the leather couch",
      "so I went to see the barber",
      "so both were justly give medals",
      "but she declined",
      "so the homework was very complicated",
      "it was completely blank",
      "so he had to search for them for an hour",
      "so I had to keep blinking them",
      "so he left the room and slammed the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cargo",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "space",
      "items",
      "air",
      "list"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "retain",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to keep",
      "to join",
      "to do",
      "to press a switch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vivid",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to not work",
      "bright",
      "end",
      "vegetable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "raisin",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "division",
      "grape",
      "air",
      "writer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "idle",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "doing nothing",
      "affected",
      "plate",
      "to have food come up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Scientists do not completely understand the ",
    "correct": "atmosphere"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The police officer ",
    "correct": "stated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teacher asked the students to read three ",
    "correct": "chapters"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Carolyn ",
    "correct": "notified"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His mother brought his food to him on a ",
    "correct": "tray"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Gina was ",
    "correct": "afflicted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Islands like Bali, Hawaii, Brunei, ",
    "correct": "etc."
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The flight attendant asked me to keep my bag out of the ",
    "correct": "aisle"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The computer\u2019s ",
    "correct": "breakdown"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "author"
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Connect your seat belt  __________.",
    "correct": "before you begin driving",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Patty was afflicted by __________.",
    "correct": "a disease that made her tired",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The cargo was lost when the door __________.",
    "correct": "was accidentally opened",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The school will notify your __________.",
    "correct": "parents if you are late",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The author of the book __________.",
    "correct": "has written many others as well",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Flip the switch __________.",
    "correct": "when the image comes into view",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "After the breakdown, __________.",
    "correct": "she had to get a new car",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Katie said her peas were __________.",
    "correct": "too sour to eat",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Vanessa had raisins __________.",
    "correct": "as a snack before dinner",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The last chapter of the book __________.",
    "correct": "was the most interesting",
    "options": [
      "as a snack before dinner",
      "she had to get a new car",
      "a disease that made her tired",
      "has written many others as well",
      "when the image comes into view",
      "before you begin driving",
      "was accidentally opened",
      "was the most interesting",
      "parents if you are late",
      "too sour to eat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "There were many items that the customer ordered, __________.",
    "correct": "so she put them on the tray",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The manager was unhappy __________.",
    "correct": "because no one stated the truth",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The meat had gone bad __________.",
    "correct": "and it made many people vomit",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Jay was rushed to the hospital, __________.",
    "correct": "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Her blouse was so colorful when she bought it, __________.",
    "correct": "but the vivid colors faded after a week",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Judy danced beautifully, __________.",
    "correct": "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He tried to keep busy, __________.",
    "correct": "but he always found himself being idle",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Sammy tried to get through to the bathroom, __________.",
    "correct": "but the aisle was crowded",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He sold most of his clothes, __________.",
    "correct": "but he retained his favorite shirt",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Sarah became quite ill __________.",
    "correct": "because the atmosphere was polluted",
    "options": [
      "but he retained his favorite shirt",
      "but her unfortunate mistake hurt her",
      "and it made many people vomit",
      "but he always found himself being idle",
      "so she put them on the tray",
      "because the atmosphere was polluted",
      "because no one stated the truth",
      "so his aunt, dad, mom, etc met him there",
      "but the aisle was crowded",
      "but the vivid colors faded after a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to clean with a broom",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "sweep",
      "betray",
      "pray",
      "choke"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to say your opinion",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "comment",
      "cross",
      "cease",
      "distrust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to bring into existence",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sole",
      "dent",
      "tuck",
      "found"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a piece of jewelry",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "civil",
      "bracelet",
      "mass",
      "fort"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a loud explosion",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "treachery",
      "blast",
      "rife",
      "lining"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The lucky man was the ",
    "correct": "sole"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She was so worried about her mother\u2019s health that she went to church to ",
    "correct": "pray"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He ",
    "correct": "choked"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The rain ",
    "correct": "ceased"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There is a ",
    "correct": "mass"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I hit the wall with my car, and now there is a small ",
    "correct": "dent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I ",
    "correct": "distrust"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The conditions in some parts of Africa are very poor, and disease is ",
    "correct": "rife"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The man ",
    "correct": "betrayed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019m going to ",
    "correct": "cross"
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ threw a lot of smoke into the air, and it made me __________.",
    "options": [
      "blast",
      "choke"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "blast",
      "choke"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The army built a __________ to defend themselves from their former ally\u2019s __________.",
    "options": [
      "treachery",
      "fort"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fort",
      "treachery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "My jobs at home are to __________ the floor and __________ the sheets neatly under the bed.",
    "options": [
      "sweep",
      "tuck"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sweep",
      "tuck"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The homeless man\u2019s __________ possession was a jacket with a warm __________.",
    "options": [
      "lining",
      "sole"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sole",
      "lining"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I __________ those girls because they __________ their friends by telling their secrets.",
    "options": [
      "distrust",
      "betray"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "distrust",
      "betray"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He __________ his business after the fighting from the war __________.",
    "options": [
      "ceased",
      "founded"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "founded",
      "ceased"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man on the news __________ on the recent __________ struggles of the people.",
    "options": [
      "commented",
      "civil"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "commented",
      "civil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Fiona stepped on my __________ and made a __________ in it.",
    "options": [
      "bracelet",
      "dent"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "bracelet",
      "dent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I watched the __________ of people __________ the bridge to see the Queen.",
    "options": [
      "cross",
      "mass"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mass",
      "cross"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The country was __________ with enemies, so I __________ that our people would be safe.",
    "options": [
      "prayed",
      "rife"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rife",
      "pray"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The reward for finding the lost dog was a very large ",
    "correct": "sum"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When his arm got crushed, it damaged a ",
    "correct": "vein"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "To which chart does this collection of data ",
    "correct": "relate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "This book ",
    "correct": "chronicles"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Since that pot is made out of ",
    "correct": "copper"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The nation had a party because their country had existed for a ",
    "correct": "millennium"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her ",
    "correct": "background"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "venom"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I wouldn\u2019t believe him. He\u2019s not very ",
    "correct": "trustworthy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The owners of the hotel decided to ",
    "correct": "update"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What do you need if you want to catch a fish?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Copper",
      "Venom",
      "Bait",
      "Disease"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means to be raised to a higher position?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Chronicle",
      "Update",
      "Infect",
      "Promote"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which would most likely be found in a library?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Literature",
      "A teller",
      "A vein",
      "Regligion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Sometimes, uncomfortable clothes will make you do this?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Itch",
      "Trustworthy",
      "Relate",
      "Background"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the combination of two numbers?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A sum",
      "A millennium",
      "Folklore",
      "A myth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The bank teller  __________.",
    "correct": "deposited Paul\u00e2\u0080\u0099s money into his account",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Many religions  __________.",
    "correct": "believe that there is a god",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The nation\u2019s folklore  __________.",
    "correct": "is rich with tradition",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The factory\u2019s new worker had a background __________.",
    "correct": "in engineering",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Those veins pump blood __________.",
    "correct": "to all necessary places in the body",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The snake\u2019s poisonous venom  __________.",
    "correct": "caused the boy to collapse",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The newspaper story chronicled the action __________.",
    "correct": "of the heroic crime-fighter",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "One of that culture\u2019s myths explains that the ocean __________.",
    "correct": "was once a small pond",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The total sum for staying three nights at the hotel __________!",
    "correct": "was over $300",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Her arm started to itch __________.",
    "correct": "from all of the insect bites",
    "options": [
      "caused the boy to collapse",
      "to all necessary places in the body",
      "was once a small pond",
      "was over $300",
      "in engineering",
      "deposited Paul\u2019s money into his account",
      "from all of the insect bites",
      "of the heroic crime-fighter",
      "believe that there is a god",
      "is rich with tradition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "If you don\u2019t stay away from school today, __________.",
    "correct": "then you might infect the other students",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Because the calendar didn\u2019t list the new holidays, __________.",
    "correct": "it had to be updated",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The hunters put some food in the trap, __________.",
    "correct": "but no animals wanted the bait",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She learned to speak the country\u2019s language, __________.",
    "correct": "so she could read their literature",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The police thought the two crimes might be connected, __________.",
    "correct": "but it turned out that they didn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t relate to each other",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The pipes were safe for carrying water __________.",
    "correct": "because they were made from copper",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He had done great work for the company for three years, __________.",
    "correct": "so his boss promoted him",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She never shared her friends\u2019 secrets with anyone, __________.",
    "correct": "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "If you think a lot can happen in a hundred years, __________.",
    "correct": "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He had a bad cough and a headache, __________.",
    "correct": "so he thought he\u00e2\u0080\u0099d caught a disease",
    "options": [
      "because they were made from copper",
      "but no animals wanted the bait",
      "so everyone knew she was trustworthy",
      "it had to be updated",
      "then you might infect the other students",
      "so she could read their literature",
      "so he thought he\u2019d caught a disease",
      "so his boss promoted him",
      "but it turned out that they didn\u2019t relate to each other",
      "then imagine how much might happen in a millennium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The other children were __________ him about how funny his new shoes looked, and it didn\u2019t take long for him to develop a bad __________.",
    "options": [
      "mocking",
      "temper"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "mocking",
      "temper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ realized that they could copy more books if they stopped arguing and worked in __________.",
    "options": [
      "scribes",
      "unity"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "scribes",
      "unity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The young man __________ in the cold without getting a ride for such a long time. When a car finally picked him up, the soft seat and warm air was very __________.",
    "options": [
      "cozy",
      "hitchhiked"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hitchhiked",
      "cozy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ they received was not only money but also several, __________ such as food and clothing.",
    "options": [
      "charity",
      "goods"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "charity",
      "goods"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The senators __________ the warning from the countries\u2019 leaders and decided to stay __________ in the war.",
    "options": [
      "heeded",
      "neutral"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "heeded",
      "neutral"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The ancient __________ that we studied in class today was very important because it spread __________ and trade throughout the world.",
    "options": [
      "commerce",
      "empire"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "empire",
      "commerce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The king\u2019s two sons had to fight to see who would become the next king. Whoever was the __________ would get to sit upon his father\u2019s __________.",
    "options": [
      "throne",
      "victor"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "victor",
      "throne"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The cold and dirt had __________ the poor man\u2019s clothing to almost nothing, and the mayor felt __________ or him and took him home to his house.",
    "options": [
      "pity",
      "reduced"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "reduced",
      "pity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The businessmen __________ the students because they didn\u2019t agree with his opinions concerning the __________.",
    "options": [
      "economy",
      "persecuted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "persecuted",
      "economy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The men had __________ the small lake of all its fish and were __________ to going without fish for many years.",
    "options": [
      "condemned",
      "depleted"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "depleted",
      "condemned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Appliances are ",
    "correct": "goods"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After making five cakes, all the sugar in the house was ",
    "correct": "depleted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "During the holidays, offering ",
    "correct": "charity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Because my views were different, I was ",
    "correct": "persecuted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "victors"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When his car ran out of gas, he ",
    "correct": "hitchhiked"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Though it might seem like fun at the time, it\u2019s not nice to ",
    "correct": "mock"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The warm weather ",
    "correct": "reduced"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "unity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "empire"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who is someone who would NOT sit on a throne?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A king",
      "A queen",
      "A chef",
      "An emperor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "All of the following describe something that\u2019s cozy EXCEPT ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "relaxing",
      "large",
      "comfortable",
      "warm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that you might heed?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Food",
      "Money",
      "Fun",
      "Advice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone can\u2019t control their temper, then they are likely to easily become ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "upset",
      "proud",
      "happy",
      "sleepy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is something a scribe would use?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Goods",
      "An oven",
      "A pen",
      "Nails"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A professor at a university is probably ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a majority",
      "an intellectual",
      "a controversy",
      "a factor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If every member of a family has a disease, the disease is ______.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "accurate",
      "identical",
      "vast",
      "genetic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would a farmer do if bugs were eating his plants?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Use a pesticide",
      "Find a mammal",
      "Raise offspring",
      "Become a vegetarian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that scientists do?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Analyze chemicals",
      "Multiply books",
      "Reinforce messages",
      "Regulate businesses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word is related to the term \u201couter space\u201d?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Stricken",
      "Evolve",
      "Genome",
      "Asteroid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What happens when something evolves?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "It studies more.",
      "It disagrees.",
      "It changes.",
      "It gets stronger."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these is a mammal?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A chicken",
      "A snake",
      "A spider",
      "A monkey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would a vegetarian eat?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Steak",
      "Sausage",
      "Chicken",
      "Corn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If something is accurate, it is ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "long",
      "false",
      "correct",
      "mysterious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these is usually considered vast?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The sky",
      "A bedroom",
      "A pool",
      "The newspaper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The cheaper blouse is nearly identical  __________.",
    "correct": "to the one I found in that expensive store",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The zoo is full of mammals  __________.",
    "correct": "that come from all over the world",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The computer has evolved from __________.",
    "correct": "a big machine to a tiny one",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My teacher said that asteroids __________.",
    "correct": "are made of rock, ice and metal",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Many pesticides that are used on __________.",
    "correct": "crops cause illnesses in humans",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The woman reinforced her statement __________.",
    "correct": "with an example from a scientific study",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The doctor analyzes the daily report __________.",
    "correct": "about each patient",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The vast space of the room was __________.",
    "correct": "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "My report on animal genomes __________.",
    "correct": "will be printed in a science textbook",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The accident left her stricken __________.",
    "correct": "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
    "options": [
      "will be printed in a science textbook",
      "about each patient",
      "with two broken legs and an injured arm",
      "that come from all over the world",
      "with an example from a scientific study",
      "a big machine to a tiny one",
      "to the one I found in that expensive store",
      "are made of rock, ice and metal",
      "big enough to fit at least 5,000 people",
      "crops cause illnesses in humans"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A small group of kids wanted pizza, __________.",
    "correct": "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I don\u2019t read gossip magazines __________.",
    "correct": "since the news isn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t accurate",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The people in this department can\u2019t be trusted, __________.",
    "correct": "so we must regulate their actions",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "There are many things to consider about the car, __________.",
    "correct": "but the most important factor is its price",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The sisters both had the strange disease, __________.",
    "correct": "so dad thought it was genetic",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "James thought he made the right choice, __________.",
    "correct": "but it caused a lot of controversy",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Pam served steak and potatoes to Ben, __________.",
    "correct": "but she didn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t know he was a vegetarian",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Alice is a short woman, __________.",
    "correct": "but her offspring are very tall",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I thought it would take weeks for them to grow, __________.",
    "correct": "but the flowers multiplied fast",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Daniel loves sports and parties, __________.",
    "correct": "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
    "options": [
      "but the flowers multiplied fast",
      "but the majority wanted hamburgers",
      "so dad thought it was genetic",
      "but she didn\u2019t know he was a vegetarian",
      "since the news isn\u2019t accurate",
      "but the most important factor is its price",
      "but her offspring are very tall",
      "but his brother is more of an intellectual",
      "but it caused a lot of controversy",
      "so we must regulate their actions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means to make a noise?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Grasp",
      "Plush",
      "Growl",
      "Stagger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following eats other animals?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Core",
      "Predator",
      "Cunning",
      "Saucer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a balance between two things?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Equilibrium",
      "Foster",
      "Compassion",
      "Sane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means not too much?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Dizzy",
      "Withhold",
      "Tense",
      "Moderation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What word means the same as agreement?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Cherish",
      "Stumble",
      "Snatch",
      "Consent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "withhold",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to think normally",
      "to be together",
      "to not give",
      "to express happiness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "snatch",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to leave",
      "to throw",
      "to give",
      "to take"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cherish",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to break into pieces",
      "to love something important",
      "to agree with",
      "to give something away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stagger",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to turn off",
      "to run into someone",
      "to take something away",
      "to trip and almost fall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "saucer",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a small dish",
      "to stop being angry",
      "helping someone",
      "to go against"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I __________ going to the movies, but in __________ because it can be expensive.",
    "options": [
      "cherish",
      "moderation"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cherish",
      "moderation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The lion began to __________, and the deer knew there was a __________ to be afraid of.",
    "options": [
      "growl",
      "predator"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "growl",
      "predator"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man was __________, so he felt __________ for the starving child in need.",
    "options": [
      "compassion",
      "sane"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "sane",
      "compassion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The boy moved to __________ the cup from his sister and knocked over the __________.",
    "options": [
      "saucer",
      "snatch"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "snatch",
      "saucer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Deep in the __________ of the tree, there are minerals that __________ new growth.",
    "options": [
      "core",
      "foster"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "core",
      "foster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ criminal started to __________ up the gemstone so no one would know it was the same stone.",
    "options": [
      "cunning",
      "grind"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "cunning",
      "grind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After he __________ down the hill, he felt __________.",
    "options": [
      "dizzy",
      "tumbled"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tumbled",
      "dizzy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The woman decided to __________ her permission and did not give __________ to her daughter\u2019s request.",
    "options": [
      "consent",
      "withhold"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "withhold",
      "consent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The man felt __________ after his horse started to __________ because he thought that the horse might fall.",
    "options": [
      "stumble",
      "tense"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tense",
      "stumble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I felt like I had no __________. As a result, I started to __________ as I walked.",
    "options": [
      "equilibrium",
      "stagger"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "equilibrium",
      "stagger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "being the right thing to do",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "jealousy",
      "migrate",
      "ethical",
      "secluded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a wet area of land",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "swamp",
      "institute",
      "celebrity",
      "species"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "able to make decisions quickly",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hardy",
      "rural",
      "extinct",
      "decisive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "respected by many people",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "nurture",
      "traverse",
      "esteemed",
      "overhead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a rule of behavior",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "zoology",
      "aircraft",
      "concrete",
      "principle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nurture",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to travel",
      "respected",
      "to care for",
      "to die"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "secluded",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "respected",
      "correct",
      "alone",
      "to make decisions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "species",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "stones",
      "an animal",
      "wet land",
      "a place to study"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "jealousy",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "knowing right and wrong",
      "the act of wanting another person\u2019s things",
      "famous",
      "studying animals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overhead",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "moving",
      "above",
      "able to fly",
      "able to cope"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How come we cannot see dinosaurs today?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They are celebrities.",
      "They are extinct.",
      "It isn\u2019t ethical.",
      "They have all traversed the desert."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What should I do if I want to learn about animals?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Go to a swamp",
      "Study zoology",
      "Nurture babies",
      "Be decisive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these does NOT describe the countryside?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is very rural.",
      "There are not a lot of buildings.",
      "Birds often fly overhead.",
      "There is a lot of concrete."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you want to camp in the mountains, you need to ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "have principles",
      "be hardy",
      "feel jealousy",
      "travel in an aircraft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Brids ______ to warmer parts of the country during the winter.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "esteem",
      "insitute",
      "species",
      "migrate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "You need to be __________ if you want to __________ the mountains.",
    "options": [
      "hardy",
      "traverse"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "hardy",
      "traverse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A(n) __________ is going to give a talk at the __________ of Drama.",
    "options": [
      "institute",
      "celebrity"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "celebrity",
      "institute"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Many people __________ by ship or __________.",
    "options": [
      "aircraft",
      "migrate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "migrate",
      "aircraft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She felt a lot of __________ because her sister was highly __________.",
    "options": [
      "esteemed",
      "jealousy"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "jealousy",
      "esteemed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "They found the remains of __________ animals in the __________.",
    "options": [
      "swamp",
      "extinct"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "extinct",
      "swamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "You can see many different bird __________ in this __________ location.",
    "options": [
      "secluded",
      "species"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "species",
      "secluded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He made a quick, __________ choice, but he was worried if it was the __________ thing to fire him over the holidays.",
    "options": [
      "ethical",
      "decisive"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "decisive",
      "ethical"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "He chose to study __________ because he has always liked to __________ animals.",
    "options": [
      "zoology",
      "nurture"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "zoology",
      "nurture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "vI like to be in __________ areas where there are no planes flying __________.",
    "options": [
      "overhead",
      "rural"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "rural",
      "overhead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like the __________ of covering the garden in __________.",
    "options": [
      "concrete",
      "principle"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "principle",
      "concrete"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a dangerous animal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "barley",
      "beast",
      "an assumption",
      "cure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to trouble or annoy someone",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "extinguish",
      "harass",
      "discriminate",
      "integrate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a dead body",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "colonel",
      "flint",
      "corpse",
      "embassy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "very small",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "miniature",
      "contagious",
      "deformed",
      "promptly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a bad situation",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "technician",
      "crisis",
      "nutrition",
      "tropics"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "assumption",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a grain",
      "a military officer",
      "a belief without proof",
      "a bad situation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "integrate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to be on time",
      "to become ill",
      "to put out a fire",
      "to socialize with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "flint",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a dead body",
      "an unusual shape",
      "a hard stone",
      "a building in another country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nutrition",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "trouble",
      "the process of how food is used for health",
      "ending an illness",
      "a dangerous animal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tropics",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "areas close to the Equator",
      "small things",
      "scientists",
      "bad treatment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Barley is often __________.",
    "correct": "fed to animals",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The colonel won a medal __________.",
    "correct": "for his work in the war",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Our new neighbors have integrated well __________.",
    "correct": "with the people in the village",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The corpse was examined __________.",
    "correct": "to determine the cause of death",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "An employer should not discriminate __________.",
    "correct": "among people at work",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The embassy will tell you __________.",
    "correct": "how you can get a visa",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The financial crisis __________.",
    "correct": "was caused by poor bank management",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I was able to extinguish the __________.",
    "correct": "entire fire by myself",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Flint weapons were used __________.",
    "correct": "by people living ten thousand years ago",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "A lot of miniature electronic machines __________.",
    "correct": "are manufactured in Japan",
    "options": [
      "to determine the cause of death",
      "are manufactured in Japan",
      "how you can get a visa",
      "by people living ten thousand years ago",
      "fed to animals",
      "was caused by poor bank management",
      "entire fire by myself",
      "for his work in the war",
      "with the people in the village",
      "among people at work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Tom left the house early __________.",
    "correct": "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The children wanted some chocolate, __________.",
    "correct": "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The book was very fun to read __________.",
    "correct": "because all the beasts could talk",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I phoned the police, __________.",
    "correct": "and they arrived very promptly",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Pam isn\u2019t at work today __________.",
    "correct": "because the illness is contagious",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I want to cut down the tree in the garden __________.",
    "correct": "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "James studied chemistry at university, __________.",
    "correct": "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Mike was released from the hospital __________.",
    "correct": "because the doctors cured his illness",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "If you want to be healthy, __________.",
    "correct": "you need to pay attention to your nutrition",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "You may need to have some vaccinations __________.",
    "correct": "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
    "options": [
      "if you go on vacation in the tropics",
      "because the doctors cured his illness",
      "because the illness is contagious",
      "because all the beasts could talk",
      "and they arrived very promptly",
      "because it is deformed and looks ugly",
      "so they harassed their father until he bought some",
      "on the assumption that the traffic would be bad",
      "and now he works as a technician in a laboratory",
      "you need to pay attention to your nutrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to give something away",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "deposit",
      "distribute",
      "comprehensive",
      "conserve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "extremely important",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "cumulative",
      "federal",
      "crucial",
      "wooded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "where something begins",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "birthplace",
      "formation",
      "rainforest",
      "equator"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a person\u2019s goal",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "strategy",
      "capacity",
      "objective",
      "frequency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "unusual and unfamiliar",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "oxygen",
      "exotic",
      "comparative",
      "beneficial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "strategy",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a plan",
      "a goal",
      "a line",
      "a forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "beneficial",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "filled with trees",
      "good for you",
      "unusual or exciting",
      "containing many details"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "formation",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "how something is made",
      "the number of things inside something",
      "where someone is born",
      "how often something happens"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "federal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "made from added parts",
      "coming from the government",
      "very important",
      "based on something else"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "conserve",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to protect",
      "to give",
      "to put into",
      "to breathe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I like going to the park because it\u2019s ",
    "correct": "wooded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Sam ",
    "correct": "distributed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The letter came from a ",
    "correct": "federal"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The business\u2019s ",
    "correct": "objective"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My mother grows ",
    "correct": "exotic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He needed ",
    "correct": "oxygen"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "This book about the history of India is ",
    "correct": "comprehensive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019m going to visit a small town in Ecuador that is near the ",
    "correct": "equator"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The number of shoes that Jane and Beth have is ",
    "correct": "comparative"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Eddie didn\u2019t want to eat it, but he knew the broccoli would be ",
    "correct": "beneficial"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word has about the same meaning as capacity?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "open",
      "expand",
      "reduce",
      "maximum amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these can be cumulative?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Snow",
      "A plate",
      "A radio",
      "Air"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something you would deposit into a closet?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A television",
      "Jackets",
      "Money",
      "Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something you probably wounldn\u2019t encounter in a rainforest?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Many trees",
      "Monkeys",
      "Humid weather",
      "Kangaroos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "In which place is there a high frequency of snowfall?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Antarctica",
      "Spain",
      "England",
      "Australia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to ask someone to come",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "worsen",
      "scribble",
      "linger",
      "summon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "basic",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "verse",
      "riot",
      "avail",
      "fundamental"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to get bigger",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "expand",
      "define",
      "stark",
      "organism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "to be afraid",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "dread",
      "shrine",
      "random",
      "horrifying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "not believing",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "solitude",
      "presently",
      "incredulous",
      "plague"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "plague",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a violent reaction",
      "different",
      "a disease",
      "without reason"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "solitude",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "being alone",
      "success",
      "afraid",
      "right now"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "define",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to last a longtime",
      "to get bigger",
      "to explain clearly",
      "to make easier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "organism",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a religious building",
      "a living thing",
      "not believing",
      "to send for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "horrifying",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to get worse",
      "basic",
      "to write quickly",
      "very unpleasant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "There was a __________ in the city yesterday, but the __________ was not damaged.",
    "options": [
      "shrine",
      "riot"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "riot",
      "shrine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "For the book report, I __________ the book and clearly __________ the author's purpose for writing it.",
    "options": [
      "paraphrased",
      "defined"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "paraphrased",
      "defined"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "There are 15 members in the group __________, but I expect that number to __________.",
    "options": [
      "expand",
      "presently"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "presently",
      "expand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "His attempt to catch the train was to no __________. He spent hours in __________ waiting for the next one.",
    "options": [
      "avail",
      "solitude"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "avail",
      "solitude"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ point of my speech was to show that people need to act. If we don\u2019t do something, things will __________.",
    "options": [
      "fundamental",
      "worsen"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "fundamental",
      "worsen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "I tried to __________ the information as fast as I could because I didn\u2019t have time to __________.",
    "options": [
      "linger",
      "scribble"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "scribble",
      "linger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "After seeing that __________ plane crash, I __________ flying.",
    "options": [
      "dreaded",
      "horrifying"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "horrifying",
      "dreaded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "She was __________ that there could be such a __________ contrast between boys' and girls' grades.",
    "options": [
      "incredulous",
      "stark"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "incredulous",
      "stark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We should __________ scientists from around the world to study this new __________.",
    "options": [
      "organism",
      "summon"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "summon",
      "organism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "At first we thought __________ people were getting sick. Then we realized that a __________ was spreading.",
    "options": [
      "plague",
      "random"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "random",
      "plague"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "A survey found that not very many people like the __________. So he is trying to think of ways to __________ his image and make people like him.",
    "options": [
      "enhance",
      "candidate"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "candidate",
      "enhance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "We live in a(n) __________ where people are very concerned about conserving our natural resources. Many people think using __________ energy is a good way to do this.",
    "options": [
      "era",
      "solar"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "era",
      "solar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The company doesn\u2019t want to __________ the air anymore, so they are going to __________ new rules for disposing waste.",
    "options": [
      "incorporate",
      "pollute"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "pollute",
      "incorporate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ files were locked in the basement. The information in them was about important customers and had to be kept __________.",
    "options": [
      "corporate",
      "confidential"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "corporate",
      "confidential"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "In the early 1900s, music records were an amazing __________. People back then would have been even more amazed by today\u2019s __________ music players.",
    "options": [
      "mobile",
      "phenomenon"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "phenomenon",
      "mobile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The old __________ was very large and difficult to drive. Jane had trouble parking it between the __________ lines in the parking lot.",
    "options": [
      "automobile",
      "parallel"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "automobile",
      "parallel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "Ben didn\u2019t listen to my advice about __________. Instead, he __________ me and continued to drive fast, eventually causing an accident.",
    "options": [
      "ridiculed",
      "transportation"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "transportation",
      "ridiculed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The __________ for the race are very simple: just run as fast as you can. There will be short __________ when you can stop for a drink of water.",
    "options": [
      "guidelines",
      "intervals"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "guidelines",
      "intervals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The government decided to __________ its borders. It made several of its __________ smaller so that it could create a new one.",
    "options": [
      "modify",
      "territories"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "modify",
      "territories"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "better_fit",
    "question": "The baseball __________ is always a lot of fun. It allows students from all over the city to __________ with each other.",
    "options": [
      "tournament",
      "interact"
    ],
    "correct": [
      "tournament",
      "interact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Factories built in the early 1900s contine to ",
    "correct": "pollute"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My soccer team is playing in a ",
    "correct": "tournament"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When the new buildings are finished, they will be ",
    "correct": "parallel"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "In order for my science project to work, I need to ",
    "correct": "modify"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Amy hurt Jane\u2019s feelings when she ",
    "correct": "ridiculed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "In this ",
    "correct": "era"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Kate is very shy and doesn\u2019t like to ",
    "correct": "interact"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Tom wants to ",
    "correct": "incorporate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My grandfather used to race ",
    "correct": "automobiles"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "candidate"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means confidential?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "soft",
      "compete",
      "moveable",
      "secret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the word solar related to?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Lines",
      "Land",
      "The sun",
      "A car"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these is mobile?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A tree",
      "A bus",
      "A building",
      "A sidewalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a form of transportation?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a friend",
      "an airplane",
      "a new job",
      "a meal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these words are related to corporate?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Business",
      "Time",
      "Competition",
      "Winning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a kind of storm?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A typhoon",
      "A bill",
      "A sergeant",
      "A boundary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would come from a farm?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Organic vegetables",
      "Wool textiles",
      "A person\u2019s wardrobe",
      "Short telegraphs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would help students taking a test?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Reading in chaos",
      "Sheer luck",
      "Taking martial arts classes",
      "Consistent studying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who should expect to receive something?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A brave sergeant",
      "A dead man\u2019s heir",
      "A man with a strong stance",
      "A man who needs a bill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would be loudest?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Cooked poultry",
      "A scrambling woman",
      "A doomed project",
      "Wailing children"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which word is not related to martial arts?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Taekwondo",
      "Karate",
      "Judo",
      "Tango"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What can a person get from poultry?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Meat",
      "Fruit",
      "Pants",
      "Soldiers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is part of a person\u2019s wardrobe?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A dog",
      "A vegetable",
      "A dress",
      "A teacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you most likely find a sergeant?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "In a store",
      "In an army",
      "In a factory",
      "In a class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which situation is full of chaos?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A man driving a car",
      "Students reading",
      "A girl walking",
      "Armies fighting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The heir of Mr. Smith\u2019s fortune __________.",
    "correct": "will become very rich",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "This is a martial matter, __________.",
    "correct": "and the soldiers should take care of it",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The kids started wailing __________.",
    "correct": "when their toys were taken away",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I used the telegraph to __________.",
    "correct": "never really changes his attitude",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "Everyone scrambled to __________.",
    "correct": "avoid the rushing water",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The sergeant ordered the __________.",
    "correct": "other soldiers to march",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He\u2019s very consistent and __________.",
    "correct": "never really changes his attitude",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "When the cyclone arrives, __________.",
    "correct": "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The boundary of my land __________.",
    "correct": "is the fence not the road",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "First we color the textiles, __________.",
    "correct": "and then we make them into clothes.",
    "options": [
      "there will be a lot of wind and rain",
      "when their toys were taken away",
      "is the fence not the road",
      "and the soldiers should take care of it",
      "other soldiers to march",
      "never really changes his attitude",
      "avoid the rushing water",
      "and then we make them into clothes.",
      "will become very rich",
      "tell my family about the new baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "During the summer, we always keep a supply of food and water in the basement __________.",
    "correct": "because that\u00e2\u0080\u0099s when tornados are common",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He didn\u2019t like a strong central government, __________.",
    "correct": "so we knew his stance on politics",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He failed the test, __________.",
    "correct": "but that doesn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t mean the school years is doomed",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "I won\u2019t go to fast food restaurants __________.",
    "correct": "because I only eat organic food",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "1 was disappointed __________.",
    "correct": "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "The police were called __________.",
    "correct": "because the event turned into chaos",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "We all took shelter, __________.",
    "correct": "since the typhoon was raging",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "He quickly took out his credit card, __________.",
    "correct": "so he could pay the bill",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "1 want to buy a new suit, __________.",
    "correct": "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "match",
    "question": "She lost a few kilos __________.",
    "correct": "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
    "options": [
      "because I only eat organic food",
      "because the event turned into chaos",
      "so he could pay the bill",
      "because she ate only poultry and fruit",
      "but that doesn\u2019t mean the school years is doomed",
      "because of their sheer lack of sportsmanship",
      "but my wardrobe is pretty full",
      "so we knew his stance on politics",
      "since the typhoon was raging",
      "because that\u2019s when tornados are common"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "You would have empathy if you ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "shared sad feelings",
      "lost in a game",
      "hurt your arm",
      "ate a large meal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you feel if there was a dearth of food?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Happy",
      "Hungry",
      "Full",
      "Sleepy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If something is a convenience, then it makes ______ .",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "you very angry",
      "you feel sick",
      "a lot of money",
      "a task easier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would a resourceful person deal with a problem?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Ignore it",
      "Give up",
      "Cry and ask for help",
      "Find a solution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If something was deliberate, then it was ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "done with pride",
      "done easily",
      "done on purpose",
      "not done at all"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you describe someone feeling a sense of outrage?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Peaceful",
      "Upset",
      "Tired",
      "Arrogant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What fanciful idea might a doctor have?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Give a patient medicine",
      "Be kind to them",
      "Tell them to rest",
      "Ask a fairy for advice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would a tired person likely opt to do?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Watch a movie",
      "Exercise",
      "Finish a book",
      "Go to bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "To rectify hurting your friend, you would ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "say sorry",
      "laugh at him",
      "hit him",
      "ignore him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might appall a teacher?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Smart students",
      "A happy student",
      "A mean attitude",
      "A long test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outrage",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "idea",
      "anger",
      "beauty",
      "personality"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rectify",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to correct",
      "to sadden",
      "to bore",
      "to be hard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sustenance",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "belief",
      "flowing",
      "food and drink",
      "torn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dire",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "terrible",
      "likely",
      "large",
      "small"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "opt",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to remove",
      "to yell",
      "to shout",
      "to choose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tedious",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "fun",
      "to read",
      "to shrink",
      "to love"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "appall",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to greet",
      "to lower",
      "to please",
      "to create"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "paltry",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "worthless",
      "large",
      "ugly",
      "absent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "grueling",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "rough",
      "exact",
      "easy",
      "necessary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "resourceful",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "foolish",
      "realistic",
      "impressive",
      "surprising"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I had a big breakfast. Many hours will ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Dan was a nice man, but no one would work for him because of his ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I was very grateful for my birthday gifts. I ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Because there was a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The puppy was happy to learn new tricks. Each one was very ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Mother ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy was proud of his trophies. He displayed them in a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Because he had planned for the trap to capture his victim, he was very ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The violent criminal was on the news this evening. His actions ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ That man is very selfish. He has ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would probably happen if you deprived someone of food?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "They could die.",
      "They could feel relieved.",
      "They could feel happy.",
      "They could feel peace."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A rugged surface would feel ______ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "very rough",
      "smooth",
      "cool and slippery",
      "warm and hard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you were speculating about something, you would be doing what?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Stating a fact",
      "Looking for truth",
      "Making a speech",
      "Making a guess"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would someone take an oath?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "At the subway",
      "In court",
      "On vacation",
      "In their sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If something were covered with moisture, then it would feel ______.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hard",
      "rough",
      "soft",
      "wet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Climbing up the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ There was no way he could mend the holes in his shirt. It was too ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In some countries, only people who owned land were ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The capital was in the middle of the country. They had to travel ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He knew she didn\u2019t like him, but he helped her ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "That part of the country is so ",
    "correct": "arid"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After getting off the boat, they took a train ",
    "correct": "inland"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "They survived through the ",
    "correct": "drought"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "This ",
    "correct": "abbey"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He knew he\u2019d get in trouble, but he stole the money ",
    "correct": "nonetheless"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He ",
    "correct": "speculated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The number of people helping to clean the trash near the river was ",
    "correct": "ample"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There was a small park that ",
    "correct": "adjoined"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Because his pants were ",
    "correct": "ragged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The long lines ",
    "correct": "deprived"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is geology the study of?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Earth\u2019s life forms",
      "Earth\u2019s structures",
      "Earth\u2019s orbit",
      "Earth\u2019s atmosphere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "In physiology, you would probably study something like ______ .",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "the ocean\u2019s waves",
      "the soil",
      "time and space",
      "parts of living things"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would NOT be considered celestial?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Stars",
      "Comets",
      "Navigation",
      "Meteors"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What else does sociology deal with besides people and their culture?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "People\u2019s problems",
      "Plant reproduction",
      "Alien life forms",
      "Ocean currents"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you excel at something, then that means you are ______.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "incompetent",
      "brave",
      "literate",
      "good at something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intellect",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "name",
      "ability",
      "speed",
      "growth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "calculus",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "content",
      "religion",
      "design",
      "math"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "assert",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "state",
      "explode",
      "purchase",
      "permit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cognitive",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "friendly",
      "expensive",
      "colorful",
      "learning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "diploma",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "money",
      "mammal",
      "license",
      "tower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mythology",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "folklore",
      "business",
      "freedom",
      "beauty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "analytic",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "official",
      "ancient",
      "logical",
      "patient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "harness",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "use",
      "expand",
      "discover",
      "insist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "competent",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "brave",
      "capable",
      "handsome",
      "broken"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "collision",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hammer",
      "scar",
      "school",
      "crash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She feared that if no one married her, she\u2019d be a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Many old factories ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her knowledge of different societies came from her work in ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If the two bikes hadn\u2019t turned at the last moment, there would have been a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The only proof that the new rocket would work was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The car ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Learning about ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The test proved that Mark was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She really learned a lot from just one class of ",
    "correct": "mythology"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When he ",
    "correct": "asserts"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The tests will prove whether or not his discovery is real and not just ",
    "correct": "theoretical"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The dangerous thing about nuclear power is the ",
    "correct": "radioactive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "John has good ",
    "correct": "cognitive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "celestial"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Having a ",
    "correct": "diploma"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Albert Einstein\u2019s ",
    "correct": "relativity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "You have to be very ",
    "correct": "keen"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Every day the ",
    "correct": "bachelors"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "merchandise",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "stores",
      "money",
      "goods",
      "fame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "corrupt",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "healthy",
      "bad",
      "angry",
      "nice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rubbish",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "trash",
      "power",
      "food",
      "truth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "transaction",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "meeting",
      "friend",
      "test",
      "sale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "revenue",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "concert",
      "guide",
      "income",
      "trade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "manipulate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "control",
      "explain",
      "decrease",
      "attempt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "infrastructure",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "education",
      "science",
      "religion",
      "roads"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "headquarters",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "material",
      "base",
      "dream",
      "section"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "audit",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "enjoy",
      "leave",
      "inspect",
      "prepare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "incentive",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "reason",
      "product",
      "waste",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This is the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He added his trash to the large pile of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The company ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This painting is an important part of the city\u2019s ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The store sold most of its ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The cook ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She took the food out of the refrigerator and then ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The company\u2019s bank records were ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Bigger kids sometimes find it easy to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "violate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "borrow",
      "respect",
      "approve",
      "explain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "affluent",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "smart",
      "quick",
      "poor",
      "evil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dispose",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "keep",
      "make",
      "feed",
      "speak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "administrator",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "singer",
      "student",
      "mother",
      "worker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "legitimate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "free",
      "pretty",
      "wrong",
      "alert"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Getting to play with her friends was ",
    "correct": "incentive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "transaction"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "By the end of the meeting, they had ",
    "correct": "legislated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She ",
    "correct": "bribed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It was a good year for the banks, but it was a bad year for ",
    "correct": "retail"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "administrator"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The papers that she needed were at ",
    "correct": "headquarters"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "corrupt"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Shawn is working for a ",
    "correct": "legitimate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "revenue"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "remedy",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "island",
      "instance",
      "movie",
      "poison"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "latter",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "first",
      "rough",
      "temporary",
      "trivial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "terminal",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "brief",
      "chilly",
      "pleasant",
      "curable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "commence",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "rescue",
      "finish",
      "require",
      "twirl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "precise",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "moist",
      "insane",
      "messy",
      "hungry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "synthetic",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "natural",
      "rhythmic",
      "shiny",
      "harmless"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "extract",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "manage",
      "anger",
      "insert",
      "explode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "publicity",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "gravity",
      "privacy",
      "bravery",
      "energy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "impulse",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "truck",
      "music",
      "revenge",
      "plan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fabulous",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "rude",
      "noisy",
      "fertile",
      "awful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Because she took the test with such ",
    "correct": "haste"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her anniversary had a ",
    "correct": "significance"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Though the ",
    "correct": "molecules"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "They ",
    "correct": "commenced"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "proximity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He could sleep late that day or get up early and start his work. He chose the ",
    "correct": "latter"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The noises on the computer sounded like they were ",
    "correct": "synthetic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Please ",
    "correct": "assess"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The best ",
    "correct": "remedy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Most of the advertisements on TV are ",
    "correct": "pharmaceutical"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would be hard to tolerate?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A nice summer day",
      "A good movie",
      "A tasty dinner",
      "A broken leg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that could be implemented?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A plan",
      "A cloud",
      "A school",
      "A storm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What has a ridge?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A person",
      "A mountain",
      "A swamp",
      "Fog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would be peculiar to find in the ocean?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A ship",
      "A shark",
      "A camel",
      "A piece of coral"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would impair vision?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "An eye test",
      "Rough fabric",
      "A strong smell",
      "A bright light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fracture",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a failure",
      "a break",
      "an idea",
      "a creation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "limb",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a party",
      "an activity",
      "a branch",
      "a belief"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thrust",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to push",
      "to grow",
      "to succeed",
      "to fall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "indigenous",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "rude",
      "extreme",
      "native",
      "cheap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "devise",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to impress",
      "beautiful",
      "to plan",
      "confusing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "optimism",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a good feeling",
      "to love",
      "to determine",
      "to reveal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "insight",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a skill",
      "a journey",
      "a method",
      "an understanding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "altitude",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "layer",
      "height",
      "station",
      "freedom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "migraine",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a headache",
      "a vehicle",
      "a chore",
      "a benefit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "quest",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a problem",
      "a search",
      "a hero",
      "a story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The little girl loves her cat. She ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Going away to college is scary, but I have ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My bike\u2019s tire is flat again. I guess I\u2019ll have to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her child is ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The tree is getting too big for our yard! Ask Jim to cut off some of the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I fell off my bike, but I didn\u2019t break any bones. I just got a slight ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This bush in my yard comes from another country. It\u2019s ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ From the mountain ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Mike is a very ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We were in awe of the professor\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You should ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I will get married to my ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Australia has a very long ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She is on a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If you don\u2019t like your job, you should ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She will have to get more ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The workers ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Nothing will ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Dogs do not have ",
    "correct": "tolerance"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "repetitive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My sister is a ",
    "correct": "prominent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I used my microscope to see the ",
    "correct": "nucleus"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "coarse"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In Biology class, we learned about the different parts of a cell\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ It is hard for some people to remain silent for the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I could listen to my favorite song all day. I have ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I will have to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This blanket is not very comfortable. It would be better if it was not so ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She has exactly twenty jelly beans, which is an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy became a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her new car is ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ There is no life on Venus, so researchers study its ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Fish must live in ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The circus performers were capable of many wonderful ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The cake ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I don\u2019t want to go alone. I wish I had a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Will you please ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The drawing of the earth showed the different elements of the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you need medication, you are probably ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "sick",
      "hungry",
      "bored",
      "skinny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you have a misconception about something, ______ .",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "you are clear",
      "you are complicated",
      "you are wrong",
      "you are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is true of a ceramic bowl?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It is metal.",
      "It is clay.",
      "It is wooden.",
      "It is plastic."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are adept at painting, you can ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "paint badly",
      "paint like a child",
      "paint well",
      "only use certain colors"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "When you peel a piece of fruit, you ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "remove the skin",
      "cut it into pieces",
      "eat the skin",
      "take a knife and chop it up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "oppress",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "cure",
      "print",
      "rule",
      "break"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "barren",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "ugly",
      "mountainous",
      "close",
      "lifeless"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "strive",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "attack",
      "struggle",
      "compete",
      "win"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dominate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "control",
      "trick",
      "encourage",
      "entertain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "culinary",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "growing",
      "creating",
      "cooking",
      "drinking"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ One of my classmates is very ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I chose an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In the past, many people suffered from ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Did you know that some flowers are ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The dog was hiding in a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ People enjoy Mark Twain\u2019s novels. They ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You can have health problems if your sugar ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You need to ask your teacher for a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After we lost the game, our coach showed his ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After the car accident, John needed a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ They are taking a break outside. Why don\u2019t we do ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ A month ago, I hurt myself playing soccer. The injury finally ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Many deserts are ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that is archaic?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A computer",
      "An Egyptian pyramid",
      "Some bread",
      "Space ships"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these things is often made of brass?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A saxophone",
      "A coat",
      "A chair",
      "A doll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these is a component in a radio?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Music",
      "Wires",
      "A television",
      "Diamonds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these things could be seen during the medieval ages?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Telephones",
      "Skateboards",
      "Castles",
      "Soda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are on a small peninsula, you will be quite near to ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "the mountains",
      "a forest",
      "the sea",
      "the moon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "weave",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to sew",
      "to create",
      "to pull apart",
      "to move"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "managerial",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "entry-level",
      "legislative",
      "ruling",
      "supervisory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prestige",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "fame",
      "honor",
      "sin",
      "lowliness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "drawback",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "artist",
      "benefit",
      "disadvantage",
      "boost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "obsolete",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "old",
      "innovative",
      "stale",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "benevolent",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "crazy",
      "kind",
      "angry",
      "dark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "diminish",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "buy",
      "decide",
      "ignore",
      "decrease"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "radical",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "new",
      "closure",
      "picture",
      "disadvantage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spectacular",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "unusual",
      "sad",
      "amazing",
      "sudden"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fad",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "trend",
      "annoyance",
      "equipment",
      "sale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Knights in armor and their squires were common sites in ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Our new boss hasn\u2019t made any changes to the company. He has very ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I don\u2019t want to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Our hotel was situated on a ",
    "correct": "peninsula"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Doctors say the exercise can ",
    "correct": "diminish"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Children\u2019s ",
    "correct": "dependence"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There are a number of ",
    "correct": "drawbacks"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A large ",
    "correct": "proportion"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I need to buy some new ",
    "correct": "components"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019m sorry to ",
    "correct": "impose"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The newspaper editor ",
    "correct": "refuted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The show at the theater was ",
    "correct": "spectacular"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "benevolent"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a type of enterprise?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A church",
      "A sign company",
      "A textbook",
      "A date"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What kind of person would most people have contempt for?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A killer",
      "A student",
      "A farmer",
      "A veterinarian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these things would you most likely want to maximize?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Your foolishness",
      "Your debt",
      "Your income",
      "Your weight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you most likely find a ditch?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "By a road",
      "In a person\u2019s backyard",
      "In a tree",
      "In a classroom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might a person sow?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Apple seeds",
      "Dresses",
      "Animals",
      "Cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "maximize",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "victory",
      "creation",
      "thought",
      "to make great"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sow",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to plant",
      "to fail",
      "to climb",
      "to understand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "upcoming",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "slow",
      "soon",
      "uncommon",
      "ready"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "exquisite",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "sure",
      "beautiful",
      "complete",
      "believable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enterprise",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a car",
      "a business",
      "an animal",
      "a group"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ditch",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a ride",
      "a river",
      "a channel",
      "a home"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "contempt",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "praise",
      "taste",
      "rating",
      "no respect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spade",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a fan",
      "a tool",
      "a trait",
      "a fact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "irrigate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to water",
      "to write",
      "to find",
      "to destroy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "simplicity",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "pride",
      "faith",
      "fondness",
      "easiness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I think the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jim said he would ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We all knew the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ It can be difficult to keep track of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The company ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I need to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The rain ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My favorite cake is made using ",
    "correct": "soy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The driver kept both hands on the wheel as a ",
    "correct": "precaution"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "People who keep financial accounts",
    "correct": "Accountants"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I wish 1 knew the ",
    "correct": "monetary"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "preliminary"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The spilled juice ",
    "correct": "saturated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Many wealthy companies ",
    "correct": "financed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "That ",
    "correct": "capitalist"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She is ",
    "correct": "indifferent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I want to ",
    "correct": "dedicate"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gorgeous",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "stiff",
      "unpleasant",
      "colorful",
      "cold"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "boost",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to lower",
      "to feel",
      "to increase",
      "to sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spontaneous",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "short",
      "crowded",
      "planned",
      "faked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "multiple",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "one",
      "lousy",
      "grand",
      "free"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inevitable",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "heavy",
      "pretty",
      "silly",
      "avoidable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I would like to write a ",
    "correct": "biography"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My little brother has an ",
    "correct": "acute"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The entire family decided to talk to Father about his constant ",
    "correct": "aggression"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The preacher strongly believed that kindness was the most important ",
    "correct": "virtue"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The action in the play was ",
    "correct": "narrated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The girl had a strong ",
    "correct": "partiality"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Black and white TVs are ",
    "correct": "outdated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The great actor left behind a great ",
    "correct": "legacy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She is ",
    "correct": "notorious"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I have no idea what would ",
    "correct": "compel"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The good father was ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We discussed the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We planned our ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ At the mayor\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ It is polite to wait until the end of a play to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This novel is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ When the child got scared, he hid in the closet to show his ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ A funny movie always ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The sunset was so ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I moved to a different climate because of my ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I will write my own ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My need to pay rent ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Screaming loudly in the library is a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ One coat of paint was not enough, so I put on ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The author of this book ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We knew a win was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I can be really mean. I wish I were better at controlling my ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which would need to be supervised?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A car",
      "An experienced pilot",
      "A new student",
      "A boat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is most likely something that is situated?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A building",
      "An apology",
      "A disease",
      "A thought"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something you can be appointed to?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A television",
      "A job",
      "An illness",
      "A holiday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone confers with another person, ______ .",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "they fight",
      "they eat",
      "they discuss something",
      "they sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that might be a cube?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A box",
      "A shirt",
      "An airplane",
      "A disc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I feel the best when the hours I sleep are ",
    "correct": "consecutive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Even though he was young, the boy\u2019s facial features were ",
    "correct": "masculine"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My girlfriend and I are happy because we are ",
    "correct": "compatible"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "muscular"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "undergraduate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My mother was shocked when she found out I had a ",
    "correct": "tattoo"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The first thing Al noticed about the new employee was his bad ",
    "correct": "posture"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "This snowflake has perfect ",
    "correct": "symmetry"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was embarrassed by his ",
    "correct": "ignorance"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "crude"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The rain made a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Our teacher was quick to give us ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The wall was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The baby ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The angry father ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The manager needed an assistant. She ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In the final revision, he made sure his work was ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The captain ordered the sailor to have better ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ On our trip, we visited the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ His ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My favorite subject in college was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She leaves the lights on at night because of her ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ When the couple got divorced, it was clear that they were ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Our basketball team won the championship for three ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is an external body part?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A nose",
      "A heart",
      "A brain",
      "A skull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which would NOT be considered a facility?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A sports stadium",
      "A surfboard",
      "An auditorium",
      "A library"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you live in the southern hemisphere, you ______ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "are on the southern half of the earth",
      "are warm all-year round",
      "can\u2019t travel very far north",
      "are on your head"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a pedestrian need the most?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Good shoes",
      "A driver\u2019s license",
      "A bus pass",
      "Fuel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of crust?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Hard cheese",
      "Outer part of a pizza",
      "A shell",
      "Pudding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cater",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "impressive",
      "to provide",
      "far away",
      "believable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "degrade",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "motherly",
      "likely",
      "ugly",
      "shame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "heap",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a flash",
      "a jar",
      "a pile",
      "a pact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "entitle",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to make happy",
      "to succeed",
      "to flee",
      "to give rights"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "criteria",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sadness",
      "letter",
      "market",
      "standard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We went to the track to watch the ",
    "correct": "hounds"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "crust"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The baseball player was yelled at by an angry ",
    "correct": "spectator"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "People who celebrate Christmas hang colorful ",
    "correct": "ornaments"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "What are the ",
    "correct": "criteria"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The church was made into a ",
    "correct": "sanctuary"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Concentration is an important ",
    "correct": "faculty"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The messy girl kept her clothes in a ",
    "correct": "heap"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boy sat by the ",
    "correct": "brook"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Buying the house will ",
    "correct": "entitle"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "informative",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "thoughtless",
      "careful",
      "helpful",
      "untrue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "coordinate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to work together",
      "to break",
      "to listen",
      "to finish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "premise",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "an important part",
      "a solution",
      "an idea",
      "a purpose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "aspect",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a valued thing",
      "a feature",
      "an idea",
      "a location"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "imprint",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "effect",
      "prison",
      "presence",
      "amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rack",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a baker",
      "a holder",
      "a shelter",
      "a waiter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "optic",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "visual",
      "thoughtful",
      "medical",
      "restful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Braille",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sign language",
      "hearing aid",
      "plant",
      "a system of writing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bud",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "tree",
      "sprout",
      "bark",
      "leaves"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wax",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "bee substance",
      "tight",
      "fire",
      "ice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "disprove",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to invent",
      "to validate",
      "to lie",
      "to guess"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "revere",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to disrespect",
      "to go fast",
      "to keep",
      "to put away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "humanitarian",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "animal",
      "parasite",
      "assistant",
      "artist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "simultaneous",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "frightening",
      "slow",
      "preceding",
      "lost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Renaissance",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "last",
      "modern",
      "art",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We received ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy waited for the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Alice placed the ball on the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The woman liked the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy was scared by the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The map was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The teacher ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Kelly had only met her uncle once and didn\u2019t know much about him. She ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In spring, all of the plants in the garden are covered with tiny ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He didn\u2019t think about the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The new hearing aid provides a wide range of ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The bad dream left an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He had to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The fruits looked real, but they were made of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her understanding has been a real ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I did an experiment to prove my ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Please use the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If you ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is marble often used to for?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "To make cars",
      "To make boats",
      "To make statues",
      "To make fires"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Accessories like earrings, purses, an ______ often make clothes book nicer.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "computers",
      "shoes",
      "eye color",
      "muscles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean to update something?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "To put away",
      "To leave as it is",
      "To make more modern",
      "To break"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that should not be imported?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Fruits",
      "Shoes",
      "Ideas",
      "Diseases"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Naval forces are designed to ______ a country from danger.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "protect",
      "fly",
      "incorporate",
      "lead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "adequate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "smart",
      "enough",
      "new",
      "safe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "facilitate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to make easier",
      "to do first",
      "to try once",
      "to find out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "elaborate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "beautiful",
      "small",
      "detailed",
      "welcoming"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dilemma",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "two parts",
      "contradiction",
      "problem",
      "rescue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inflate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to fill with air",
      "to enter",
      "to put away",
      "to utilize"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "innate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "strong",
      "natural",
      "evil",
      "full"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "saturated",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "wet",
      "likely",
      "uncommon",
      "unable to change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pouch",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a costume",
      "an animal",
      "a bag",
      "a part"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nausea",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "improvement",
      "strength",
      "lost",
      "sickness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fleet",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "shipbuilder",
      "structure",
      "group",
      "underwater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The man had an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The man helped the old woman ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We used the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The painting was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Someone with integrity ______ .",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "invents new things",
      "tricks people",
      "lies",
      "is honest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a person with a good understanding of a budget take care of?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Their safety",
      "Their possessions",
      "Their money",
      "Their pet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following might an archeological expert be interested in?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Reading about ancient devices",
      "Studying the effects of height and speed",
      "Learning how to save lives",
      "Finding his car keys"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does it mean to be a parachute addict?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "To want to be on land",
      "To want to jump from a plane with a parachute",
      "To always ride in hot-air balloons",
      "To want to be at sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "In order to refine an invention, one has to _______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "spend money on it",
      "make it better",
      "be ignorant",
      "know Italian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teacher held classes in the ",
    "correct": "courtyard"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The airport is usually ",
    "correct": "chaotic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teacher made sure the correct answers ",
    "correct": "corresponded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The student ",
    "correct": "cited"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The victim of the ",
    "correct": "fraud"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prehistoric",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "large",
      "old",
      "upsetting",
      "under"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outlook",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "outside",
      "plan",
      "work",
      "viewpoint"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "proponent",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "supporter",
      "teacher",
      "traveler",
      "scientist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "estate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "gas",
      "property",
      "airplane",
      "evidence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "brainstorm",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to come up with",
      "to read a lot",
      "to get wet",
      "to jump"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The farmer lived on a large ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The principal was a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He wanted to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The seat belt ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After an accident in the laboratory, ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy had a different ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The scientists found many ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Brian ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The people in the plane crash were saved by ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Ellen wanted to learn how to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The man was found guilty of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The woman showed her ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The chocolate ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The children ran into the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is a place that you would graduate from?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "An island",
      "A school",
      "A house",
      "A party"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following has a shaft?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A calendar",
      "A keyboard",
      "A basketball",
      "A pool stick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is one responsibility of a referee?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "To make sure a game is fair",
      "To stop crime",
      "To guard athletes",
      "To be a good parent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Why might somebody hire an attorney?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "To watch security tapes",
      "To pay for their bills",
      "To prove they didn\u2019t do a crime",
      "To help them decorate their home"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you describe chronic pain?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "It hurts a lot.",
      "It hurts all the time.",
      "It hurts in the morning.",
      "It hurts only when it is cold."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "kin",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "relatives",
      "boxes",
      "friends",
      "principals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "chronic",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "useless",
      "unskilled",
      "constant",
      "again"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "attorney",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "police officer",
      "lawyer",
      "teacher",
      "instructor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gossip",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "plans",
      "an untrue talk",
      "culture",
      "evil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sever",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to watch",
      "to cut off",
      "to keep",
      "to hit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stab",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to cut",
      "to prove",
      "to get help",
      "to wonder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "theme",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a book",
      "a preview",
      "a main idea",
      "a perspective"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "suspicion",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "lunch money",
      "classes",
      "mistrust",
      "clothes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "guardian",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a protector",
      "a judge",
      "intelligence",
      "truth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "terminate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to wait",
      "to end",
      "to destroy",
      "to hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I may not be able to go to college next year. I don\u2019t have enough money for ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy\u2019s parents didn\u2019t know howto control him. They taught him ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He was a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ His new stove will be a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Ellen didn\u2019t like the color of her walls, so she painted ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jason was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Besides her parents, Olivia had no other ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The gardener picked up the tool by the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The man was sent to prison for ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Leslie\u2019s father is a policeman. He is a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I took a knife and ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The food was being held on ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I spoke to my ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who would most likely serve in a corps?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A teacher",
      "A baby",
      "A minister",
      "A soldier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would you find near a compound?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A fence",
      "A napkin",
      "A parade",
      "A computer program"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which would you most likely see in an auditorium?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A shark",
      "A river",
      "A crowd",
      "Birds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who would most likely be involved in combat?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A warrior",
      "A teacher",
      "A swimmer",
      "A dancer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a dumb thing to do?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "To go swimming",
      "To chop wood",
      "To play with matches",
      "To trim your fingernails"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "foe",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "shovel",
      "friend",
      "room",
      "thumb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "amnesty",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "education",
      "prison",
      "energy",
      "highway"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "combat",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "peace",
      "brush",
      "carpet",
      "bird"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sacred",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "brave",
      "better",
      "evil",
      "warm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "distract",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "increase",
      "pretend",
      "return",
      "focus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dumb",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "kind",
      "wrong",
      "loud",
      "hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "commonplace",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "unusual",
      "fresh",
      "pleasant",
      "actual"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hack",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "mend",
      "sneeze",
      "blame",
      "dig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "aggressive",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "smart",
      "tall",
      "calm",
      "young"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "provoke",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "mash",
      "burn",
      "tire",
      "soothe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "realm",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "lunch",
      "area",
      "gown",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "auditorium",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "market",
      "assembly hall",
      "music",
      "present"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rust",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "morning",
      "speed",
      "truth",
      "decay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "corps",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "basin",
      "troop",
      "pace",
      "image"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "meditate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "think",
      "bake",
      "swim",
      "sweep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "compound",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "garbage",
      "pasture",
      "kilogram",
      "camp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reign",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "bath",
      "snow",
      "rule",
      "chalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "arena",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "stadium",
      "boulder",
      "camera",
      "believable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nick",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "scratch",
      "choice",
      "grain",
      "glove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "captive",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "challenge",
      "motor",
      "prisoner",
      "ticket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The wooden fence was covered in a thick layer of ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ His ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You will like Jack. You both have so much ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her perfume was too strong. I was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which person uses an anchor?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A mailman",
      "A sailor",
      "A writer",
      "A priest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If your jacket is made of genuine leather, it ______ .",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "is not expensive",
      "falls apart easily",
      "is real leather",
      "it is alive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might precipitate a fight?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Taking a nap",
      "Sharing lunch",
      "Doing homework",
      "Name calling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you most likely see a buoy?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "On the ocean",
      "On the street",
      "At the store",
      "In an airplane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If a problem is frequent, then it happens ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "several times",
      "only once",
      "almost never",
      "in the afternoon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I buy most of my clothes ",
    "correct": "secondhand"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "dock"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Be sure not to ",
    "correct": "distort"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The women sat on the ",
    "correct": "fore"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I have to add a stop to our trip, so adjust your plans ",
    "correct": "accordingly"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "To understand this show, you have to know the ",
    "correct": "context"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The new sewing machine was ",
    "correct": "intricate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Let\u2019s hope that our plans do not ",
    "correct": "overlap"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The city has decided to ",
    "correct": "designate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I think the gears need a little more ",
    "correct": "grease"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The key fit perfectly in the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jackets help to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I need to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The parade was a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ They had to water the tree four times a day. It was a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The weather ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We walked to the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The lion ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She was noted for creating some imaginative ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The guide asked us to be very quiet, so we acted ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The chef arranged the slices of bread so that they ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We knew from the beginning that the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We stood at the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The fireman who saved the family was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Check the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This looks like a good place to drop the boat\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you find a microchip?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "In a salad",
      "In a laptop",
      "In a chair",
      "In your dog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is found at a quantum level?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A comet",
      "Atomic particles",
      "A scale",
      "Biological theories"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a magnet attract?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Metal",
      "Trees",
      "Water",
      "Plastic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is an example of a ratio?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Rough to smooth",
      "Cat to dog",
      "Two to one",
      "Black and white"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the equivalent of 60 minutes?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "One hour",
      "30 minutes",
      "One day",
      "One century"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Walking was the most ",
    "correct": "prevalent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We are now ready to begin the first ",
    "correct": "phase"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Do the doctors know if the condition is ",
    "correct": "viral"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some people don\u2019t believe in taking ",
    "correct": "antibiotics"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We were offered a bottle of sparkling cider to ",
    "correct": "complement"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I seem to have lost some of the ",
    "correct": "input"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I wish they wouldn\u2019t store personal information in the ",
    "correct": "database"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His grandmother loves to ",
    "correct": "pinch"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I don\u2019t really understand my body\u2019s ",
    "correct": "metabolism"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A spring looks like a ",
    "correct": "spiral"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ People with fast ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You should ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I was amazed by the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The children played all day on the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Dressing and pepper ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This tuba is the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Cosmetics are typically used to make someone ______ .",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "look better",
      "think clearer",
      "feel stronger",
      "eat healthier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would NOT be considered a subject studied in humanities?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Film",
      "Literature",
      "Mythology",
      "Mathematics"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following could NOT be used to make a knot?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Lines of clouds",
      "Wire",
      "Thread",
      "Yarn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Positive attributes include being energetic, optimistic, and ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "dreary",
      "pessimistic",
      "cheerful",
      "arrogant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is similar in meaning to the word dash?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Stroll",
      "Run",
      "Sprint",
      "Meander"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "astounded",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "angry",
      "surprised",
      "interested",
      "bored"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "disgust",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "information",
      "detail",
      "money",
      "anger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gulf",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "island",
      "gap",
      "entrance",
      "partnership"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vague",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "pretty",
      "useful",
      "unclear",
      "dirty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "furious",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "lively",
      "quiet",
      "angry",
      "shocking"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bilingual",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "foreign",
      "surprised",
      "poison",
      "using two languages"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "clone",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "double",
      "extra",
      "light",
      "copy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "plausible",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "never",
      "always",
      "possible",
      "weak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "skinny",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "large",
      "thin",
      "tall",
      "short"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fluorescent",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "bright",
      "gloomy",
      "open",
      "ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Kevin was very ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Liam had a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Tom can only speak English. He is ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Emma likes studying ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Ivy doesn\u2019t have any ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The two brothers looked so much alike that they could be ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My mother was ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Miranda is so ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I was filled with ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Sarah and I really understand each other. There is a big ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Around the world, there are lots of different marriage ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We had lots of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Kay is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You should wear dark clothes for the interview, such as your ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You always ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I can\u2019t use this thread for sewing because it has too many ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jan wanted to make a cake, so she went to the shop to buy some ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The lesson was long and boring, and all the students felt ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I think Tom should get the job because he has all the right ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You shouldn\u2019t use ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something you want to eliminate?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A problem",
      "A present",
      "A statue",
      "A victory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would collect nectar?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A tree",
      "A bee",
      "A cat",
      "A housefly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you have good ethics, you _______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "dislike school",
      "know right from wrong",
      "rarely follow the rules",
      "are extremely smart"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is most closely related to something administrative?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Loss",
      "Fatigue",
      "Organization",
      "Swimming"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might cause erosion?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A strong wind",
      "A fast car",
      "A lonely person",
      "Loud music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Smoking makes people more ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We toured the factory that ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Eating a lot of fast food raises people\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The group decided on a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Businesses try to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He had a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The maid used a kind of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ It is important for a judge to have good ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Some factories produce energy by burning ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The lawyer hoped that the witness would tell an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My father works in construction while my mom has an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Be sure to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jim receives shots to treat his ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ All of the prisoners formed an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Dry weather, followed by sudden floods, caused the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The cutting ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "radiate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "measure",
      "release",
      "welcome",
      "allow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "breadth",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "path",
      "death",
      "mouth",
      "width"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "spectrum",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "colors",
      "amounts",
      "sounds",
      "places"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "comet",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "arrival",
      "meteor",
      "scissors",
      "image"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "atom",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "particle",
      "catch",
      "fast",
      "legal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "status",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "land",
      "rock",
      "rank",
      "cloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "astronomical",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "historical",
      "pleasant",
      "delicious",
      "huge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "embed",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "sleep",
      "soften",
      "bury",
      "burn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sphere",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "tide",
      "voice",
      "mass",
      "ball"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "debris",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "pieces",
      "troops",
      "cloths",
      "liquids"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "crater ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "basket ",
      "habit ",
      "spouse ",
      "hill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gloom ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "plan",
      "book",
      "light ",
      "hole "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "solitary ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "chain ",
      "group ",
      "home ",
      "card "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gigantic ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wild ",
      "tiny ",
      "next ",
      "free "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "roam ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "buy ",
      "break ",
      "get ",
      "stand "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fragment ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "whole ",
      "child ",
      "phone ",
      "point "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "despair ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "burn ",
      "hope ",
      "sing ",
      "make "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "galaxy ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "delivery ",
      "marriage ",
      "particle ",
      "agreement "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "crescent ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "circle ",
      "closet ",
      "problem ",
      "schedule "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "circumference ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "feeling ",
      "detail ",
      "center ",
      "helmet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that is astronomical? ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A planet ",
      "A book ",
      "An ant ",
      "A movie "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something you\u00e2\u0080\u0099d find in a galaxy?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A pear ",
      "A broom ",
      "A star ",
      " A motorcycle "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which would help you see through the gloom of a day? ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Glasses ",
      "A telescope ",
      "A candle ",
      "A cap "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a sphere? ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A globe ",
      "A bat ",
      "A golf club ",
      "A television set "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What describes someone whose waist has a large circumference? ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Tall ",
      "Fat ",
      "Strong ",
      "Skinny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The night was extremely dark because little light came from the ",
    "correct": "crescent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "They ",
    "correct": "roamed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The moon has large ",
    "correct": "craters"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "breadth"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mom couldn\u2019t fix the bowl because a ",
    "correct": "fragment"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A lot of energy is stored within just one simple ",
    "correct": "atom"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The bee\u2019s stinger was ",
    "correct": "embedded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Guarding the camp was a ",
    "correct": "solitary"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When it\u2019s low on fuel, the heater ",
    "correct": "radiates"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was so concerned about his ",
    "correct": "status"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following means the closest to mend?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Repair",
      "Highlight",
      "Exchange",
      "Plant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of following would NOT be considered part of an office\u2019s personnel?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Cleaning staff",
      "Technicians",
      "Executives",
      "Referees"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Plumbing involves work on _______ in a house or building.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "electrical wiring",
      "plants and bushes",
      "water pipes",
      "interior design"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If something is trendy, then it is ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "outdated",
      "in style",
      "almost empty",
      "very cheap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is NOT considered a utility?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Room service",
      "Electrical service",
      "Water service",
      "Gas service"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His company ",
    "correct": "employs"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Joan was ",
    "correct": "expelled"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mv new apartment in the city was ",
    "correct": "furnished"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The prisoner\u2019s ",
    "correct": "hygiene"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019m going to ",
    "correct": "lease"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I need to ",
    "correct": "mend"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was lucky to find ",
    "correct": "personnel"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We need to have our ",
    "correct": "plumbing"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "trendy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Did you remember to pay the ",
    "correct": "utility"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The sharp rocks mended his jeans into pieces.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The school sent a second bus whereby the students could get to school.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He had poor hygiene. He never washed his hands or brushed his teeth.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The dam on the lake became bankrupt, and soon water broke through the cracks.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The restaurant was a trendy place where all the rich and famous people went.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The first three cars to finish were given an award, but the forthcoming car got nothing.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She made a mistake and accidentally walked into the mandatory bathroom.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After he furnished dinner, the host gave him some dessert.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Rather than conforming to one religion, Mary chose what she liked from all of them.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I knew something was wrong with the plumbing once the hot water stopped working.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She graduated from university where she studied utility.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Because of an error, the game was given an extension of five more minutes.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He\u00e2\u0080\u0099s very hygienic because he bathes once a week and seldom changes his clothes.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The landlord owned several buildings throughout the capital city.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The factory needed more workers. It had to employ twenty more people.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Tom didn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t want to talk about his father\u00e2\u0080\u0099s new job. He thought it was too personnel.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ There was too much sugar in the recipe, so she leased the amount with a spoon.",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Because the rent was so expensive, all of the tenants are probably wealthy people.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ They were expelled from the restaurant because they couldn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t pay their bill.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In order to buy a house, most people have to get a mortgage.",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following might be eaten by a termite?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A log",
      "A brick",
      "A cake",
      "A feather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who would most likely use a drill?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A captain",
      "A carpenter",
      "A cowboy",
      "A lifeguard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What job would an executive do?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Clean floors",
      "Manage workers",
      "Teach science",
      "Prepare food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would best describe something that smells nasty?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Sweet",
      "Steamy",
      "Stinky",
      "Pleasant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How would you describe someone who could NOT perceive sound?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Deaf",
      "Blind",
      "Quiet",
      "Mute"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "perceive",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "notice",
      "share",
      "copy",
      "gain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "welfare",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "welcome",
      "blanket",
      "health",
      "sale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bias",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "herb",
      "sock",
      "box",
      "favoritism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "arrogant",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "proud",
      "bright",
      "loose",
      "loud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "creek",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "button",
      "truck",
      "stream",
      "arrow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nasty",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "slow",
      "small",
      "smooth",
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "executive",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "group",
      "boss",
      "monster",
      "finger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "trail",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "path",
      "moment",
      "song",
      "mirror"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "incline",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "rise",
      "cotton",
      "shoulder",
      "soldier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thereby",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "growth",
      "section",
      "dream",
      "so"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The kids gathered ",
    "correct": "twigs"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The glue was ",
    "correct": "sticky"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Early rocket development was ",
    "correct": "primitive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Monkeys, apes, and humans",
    "correct": "primates"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After walking 12 kilometers, I was filled with a sense of ",
    "correct": "fatigue"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What recurs when watching a funny movie?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Boredom",
      "Laughter",
      "Headaches",
      "Hunger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What orbits the Earth?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "The moon",
      "A car",
      "A bird",
      "A kite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Why do birds flap their wings?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "To eat",
      "To fly",
      "To whistle",
      "To exercise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is supernatural?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A frog",
      "A school",
      "A ghost",
      "An eclipse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you give an overview of a movie, you ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "describe the important parts",
      "watch it again",
      "tell others it was a good movie",
      "pay money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "relevant",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "important",
      "beautiful",
      "vast",
      "different"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "horizontal",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "heavy",
      "flat",
      "large",
      "nice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "a rite",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a story",
      "a belief",
      "a body",
      "a ceremony"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stall",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "to stop",
      "to fade",
      "to blink",
      "to react"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inventory",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "a brand",
      "a trait",
      "a supply",
      "a car"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My ",
    "correct": "previous"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "In ancient Greece, the ",
    "correct": "oracle"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The top of the fence was perfectly ",
    "correct": "horizontal"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I know about the piece because I saw the ",
    "correct": "preview"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The baker made an extra ",
    "correct": "loaf"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She is embarrassed of some of her ",
    "correct": "inward"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The fisherman liked to ",
    "correct": "hum"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The travelers were given a place to stay, but they had to ",
    "correct": "provide"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The company had to ",
    "correct": "stall"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We saw a cute polar bear jump into the water from the edge of the ",
    "correct": "glacier"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What thing is a result of heredity?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Eye color",
      "Clothing style",
      "A haircut",
      "A job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What process is biological?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Walking to school",
      "Taking a test",
      "Producing tears",
      "Getting dressed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that is prescribed?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A car",
      "A report card",
      "A cold medicine",
      "An illness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might be transplanted?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A file",
      "A liver",
      "A can",
      "A shoe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a surgeon wear?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Gloves",
      "Thick boots",
      "A swimming suit",
      "Goggles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The child received ",
    "correct": "therapy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The medical students learned which processes were ",
    "correct": "biological"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Unicorns only exist in a ",
    "correct": "fantasy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When he begins his rule, people will have to ",
    "correct": "adapt"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "At the ",
    "correct": "cellular"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We thought his rules were too ",
    "correct": "rigid"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "dynamic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The creative inventor was a ",
    "correct": "pioneer"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "There is a specific ",
    "correct": "sequence"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The brilliant doctor ",
    "correct": "revived"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The building materials must be ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The baby ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You can observe water\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Blood flow is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I never want to get a new house, so I ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Going to sleep at night is a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He needed plenty of rest after his liver ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The pieces must be put on the machine in the correct ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I admired how often he chose to be ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My ney school is great. I can\u2019t ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Hot dogs are one of my favorite surgical foods to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Please take the big, ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The hours of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He\u2019s always the last to understand a joke. He\u2019s such a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I was still hungry because I only ate a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would you find at an aquarium?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A blanket",
      "A squid",
      "A cow",
      "A coyote"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What can you do to improve your grades?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Copy them",
      "Study more",
      "Miss class",
      "Get less sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is the ultimate result of going to college?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Signing up for classes",
      "Taking many tests",
      "Getting a degree",
      "Dating"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What happens if you insulate a house in the winter?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Cold air stays outside.",
      "Fires cannot be lit.",
      "You can never get outside.",
      "It will float."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who would most likely publish an autobiography?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "An important person",
      "A five-year-old",
      "A shy teenager",
      "A dead person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "recipient",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "an attempt",
      "a giver",
      "a friend",
      "a follower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "misplace",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to try",
      "to help",
      "to find",
      "to declare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "naughty",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "wanting more",
      "over",
      "lacking",
      "behaving well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "longevity",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "short life",
      "plans",
      "answers",
      "tallness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "thrive",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to create",
      "to do bad",
      "to agree",
      "to move around"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gracious",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "mean",
      "silly",
      "kind",
      "smart"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "norm",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "abnormal",
      "common",
      "everyday",
      "average"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intrigue",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to excite",
      "to bore",
      "to reassure",
      "to trust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "arbitrary",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "accidental",
      "solar",
      "random",
      "planned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "probe",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "to touch",
      "to open",
      "to ignore",
      "to build"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Make sure to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The tigers in the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The greedy man loved ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The box broke when he ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The mechanics of computers ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Plants will ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Some people play the lottery in hopes that they will ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Paying for gasoline before pumping it is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Waiting your turn in line is a social ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My dog is a great ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She was the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Someday, I will write my father\u2019s ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I don\u2019t want to play with you anymore. You make up ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The store clerk was so ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following might humiliate someone?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Spilling a drink",
      "Getting a new car",
      "Working ten hours",
      "Sitting down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might be antique?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A sweet fruit",
      "An old sofa",
      "A good father",
      "A cell phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who is referred to as her majesty?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A queen",
      "A student",
      "A mother",
      "A teacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where might a job applicant go for job?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "An abandoned house",
      "A store with an available position",
      "A sandy beach",
      "A graveyard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What precedes waking up in the morning?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Going to sleep",
      "Going to school",
      "Buying a new bed",
      "Shopping"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "humiliate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "impress",
      "entertain",
      "destroy",
      "embarrass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "diplomat",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "a representative",
      "a user",
      "a creature",
      "a joker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "punctual",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "hurried",
      "on time",
      "too loud",
      "brave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "precede",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to fail",
      "to quit",
      "to rely",
      "to go first"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "register",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "a control",
      "a list",
      "an apartment",
      "a grave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The circus performer held on to the elephant\u2019s ",
    "correct": "tusk"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The salesman assured me that the artwork was ",
    "correct": "authentic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "At the end of the year, our club will ",
    "correct": "recruit"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Janet isn\u2019t ",
    "correct": "punctual"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It is difficult to follow the ",
    "correct": "chronology"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "DNA can be taken from a ",
    "correct": "fossil"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Please stand and read a(an) ",
    "correct": "excerpt"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I took a class at the university where I wrote ",
    "correct": "lyric"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The lliad is an wonderful ",
    "correct": "epic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her mother was a dancer of some ",
    "correct": "renown"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are an enigma, you are ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "funny",
      "mysterious",
      "dishonest",
      "sleepy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone is too talkative during a movie, then others may ______ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "get sleepy",
      "get angry",
      "start to sing",
      "join in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone has shivers, what should they do?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Stop running",
      "Put on a sweater",
      "Be quiet",
      "Sit down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How should someone deal with another that is overwhelming them?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Ask for help",
      "Forget it",
      "Keep quite",
      "Cry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would have the most innocence?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A grandparent",
      "A sea captain",
      "A teen",
      "A president"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What would someone consider a burden?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Working two jobs",
      "A happy child",
      "Resting",
      "Taking a walk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone exercised a moderate amount, they would be ______ .",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "stressed",
      "healthy",
      "very ill",
      "a good leader"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who would you probably see at a reunion?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Your family",
      "The police",
      "Your boss",
      "Your barber"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would a crook most likely end up for doing something wrong?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "At church",
      "In jail",
      "In school",
      "On vacation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a boat most likely to tow behind it?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A trailer",
      "A water skier",
      "A fisherman",
      "A rocket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I met a very ",
    "correct": "sociable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Marty ",
    "correct": "tramped"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "That lovely dresser was ",
    "correct": "crafted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The man had ",
    "correct": "rigged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The paint colors ",
    "correct": "merged"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fragile",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "sturdy",
      "strong",
      "robust",
      "weak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "shiver",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "jump",
      "fall",
      "shake",
      "stand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "currency",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "money",
      "recent",
      "waves",
      "spend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overwhelm",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "too much",
      "not enough",
      "completed",
      "unfinished"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sociable",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "rude",
      "friendly",
      "cunning",
      "wise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "craft",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "to bend",
      "to make",
      "to ruin",
      "to stir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enigma",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "public",
      "dramatic",
      "mystery",
      "parent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "crook",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "thief",
      "hermit",
      "wizard",
      "warrior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "merge",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "to pull apart",
      "to float",
      "to carry",
      "to combine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "burden",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "a deal",
      "a resolution",
      "an order",
      "a hard responsibility"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Let\u2019s ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jill\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The temperature in here is too ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We had a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Tonya\u2019s new car is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ It is such ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The snake ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He chose to paint a picture on the ",
    "correct": "hull"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When the plane crashed on the island, the passenger knew he was ",
    "correct": "stranded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I admired the ",
    "correct": "multitude"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I took some aspirin to ",
    "correct": "alleviate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The countries were concerned about the treaty\u2019s ",
    "correct": "permanence"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Australia\u2019s ",
    "correct": "latitude"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019m still not sure if the ",
    "correct": "equation"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When the rats got out of the cage, the girl was ",
    "correct": "frantic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "erroneous"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When he forgot his rope at home, he had to ",
    "correct": "improvise"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She loves to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Ice packs are sometimes used to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This math book is full of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The expert in ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This math problem is tricky, so be careful not to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After months of planning, the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The Earth and other planets ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Two flat tires ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ What ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He chose to make his sculpture out of ",
    "correct": "plaster"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Our ",
    "correct": "vicious"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The race was close, so it was difficult to determine an ",
    "correct": "outright"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "This is the perfect ",
    "correct": "locale"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Truck drivers often stay awake for many hours to make their ",
    "correct": "arduous"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The salesperson\u2019s claim seemed quite ",
    "correct": "dubious"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mike was thrilled to pass the driving test and ",
    "correct": "attain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Physics on the moon are much different than ",
    "correct": "terrestrial"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The prisoners were unable to ",
    "correct": "conceive"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "To plant these seeds, I will first need to buy a ",
    "correct": "shovel"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might a person with a large ego say?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "\u201c I am the best.\u201d",
      "\u201c I can\u2019t do it.\u201d",
      "\u201c I\u2019m hungry.\u2019",
      "\u201c I\u2019m sorry.\u201d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is likely to be jagged?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A doll",
      "A cliff",
      "A cloud",
      "A pillow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is likely to be excavated?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Water",
      "A sofa",
      "A computer",
      "The ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is part of the skeletal system?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "The skin",
      "The tongue",
      "The skull",
      "The fingernails"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is an example of an endeavor?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Waking up",
      "Inventing a new machine",
      "Making coffee",
      "Combing your hair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The alarm clock was set to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Experts ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Everyone loved to hug and kiss the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The elephant is one of the largest ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The concerned owner built a fence along the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Preparing for the difficult test was an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You\u2019ll need a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The delicate flower was a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Children cheered as the circus clown ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He filled the ugly holes in the ceiling with ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ At the factory, the workers made screws by pouring liquid metal into a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I hope she is able to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I cannot ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The small fights and arguments eventually led to an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ When the glass vase fell to the floor, we heard an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She bought a cute new ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We need to choose a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Derrick bought a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Although they were rivals, the stores were able to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vanity",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "truck",
      "pride",
      "dusk",
      "shelf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "aristocrat",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "noble",
      "painting",
      "weather",
      "angel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pad",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "pocket",
      "cushion",
      "alley",
      "subject"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vulgar",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "young",
      "faint",
      "short",
      "rude"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "predominant",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "mysterious",
      "gradual",
      "superior",
      "parallel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "attire",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "clothing",
      "wheel",
      "labor",
      "smell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tangle",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "knot",
      "tint",
      "slope",
      "spice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enlarge",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "fight",
      "rent",
      "greet",
      "swell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "absurd",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "hungry",
      "round",
      "funny",
      "polite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "signify",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "scribble",
      "symbolize",
      "consult",
      "remove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I broke the ",
    "correct": "strap"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Matt\u2019s ",
    "correct": "feminine"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "You must wear proper ",
    "correct": "attire"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He works for a ",
    "correct": "reputable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "pads"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We all felt that the new office rules were completely ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The bushes were ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Losing your memory as you get older is called ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ A strong smell is the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ It was easy to get lost in the big house. Its many hallways made it seem like a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The local ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After putting on too much ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Everyone may attend ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Talking to people with food in your mouth is not only gross. It is also quite ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Because he was an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "din",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "home",
      "supper",
      "silence",
      "ghost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outspoken",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "quiet",
      "little",
      "inside",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pungent",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "hurt",
      "mild",
      "kind",
      "young"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "civic",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "swollen",
      "happy",
      "private",
      "mature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "descent",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "climb",
      "odor",
      "plate",
      "bill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "attic",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "mouse",
      "square",
      "number",
      "cellar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fuss",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "complaint",
      "calm",
      "argument",
      "commerce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dissatisfy",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "cleanse",
      "leap",
      "trim",
      "please"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overwork",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "relax",
      "understand",
      "select",
      "repair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "chunk",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "bridge",
      "song",
      "whole",
      "lamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intrinsic",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "logical",
      "natural",
      "usable",
      "fragile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ministry",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "porch",
      "coast",
      "agency",
      "bush"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "snore",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "grunt",
      "fly",
      "rain",
      "call"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "kettle",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "cup",
      "bucket",
      "pot",
      "pan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "superintendent",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "diner",
      "manager",
      "sunrise",
      "beginning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gourmet",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "delicious",
      "comfortable",
      "legitimate",
      "pleasant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "soundly",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "slowly",
      "totally",
      "loudly",
      "briefly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hence",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "also",
      "instead",
      "still",
      "thus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ordeal",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "problem",
      "direction",
      "bargain",
      "request"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "particular",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "moody",
      "beaten",
      "exact",
      "secret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "descent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The berries were not ripe when he tried them. Their taste was extremely ",
    "correct": "pungent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A ",
    "correct": "chunk"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Please share your suggestions with the ",
    "correct": "superintendent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After toiling for hours in the hot sun, the prisoners were ",
    "correct": "overworked"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "For her birthday, her boyfriend took her out for a ",
    "correct": "gourmet"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "attic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She was respected by many because she was ",
    "correct": "outspoken"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He always dreamed of getting a job with one of the ",
    "correct": "ministries"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Getting lost in the desert would have been quite an ",
    "correct": "ordeal"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The caffeine in the tea gave him more energy. ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Mom, something smells good in the kitchen. I can\u2019t wait for ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The cat waited outside the door and made a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ See that politician over there? He works in the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The need to protect one\u2019s family is an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "An overdose of something is _______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "expensive",
      "too much",
      "not true",
      "not enough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might cause someone to gasp?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Falling asleep",
      "Getting a surprise party",
      "Eating too much",
      "Laying on a bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that can be sipped?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A plate of rice",
      "A bowl of fruit",
      "A glass of soda",
      "A piece of chicken"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you knew that a snake was benign, you would probably feel like this:",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Fine",
      "Scared",
      "Angry",
      "Hungry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "She felt apologetic about _______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "calling her friend back",
      "walking home alone",
      "forgetting her friend\u2019s birthday",
      "giving to charity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If people are negotiating, what are they doing?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Deciding on something",
      "Arguing about a silly topic",
      "Meeting for the first time",
      "Going on a date"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does charred meat look like?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "It is raw and not cooked enough.",
      "It is cooked perfectly.",
      "It is black on the outside.",
      "It is red on the outside."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If someone does something with reluctance, how do they feel?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Excited",
      "Unwilling",
      "Frightened",
      "Nervous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might ensue after someone has misplaced a lot of money?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A worried search",
      "A visit from the doctor",
      "The arrival of a friend",
      "A party"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might cause a teacher distress?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "All the students doing their homework",
      "Her students always arriving on time",
      "Her students not coming to class",
      "Her students all passing an exam"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reluctance",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "loneliness",
      "hesitance",
      "dependence",
      "lateness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "apologetic",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "unsure",
      "lucky",
      "sorry",
      "pitiful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "char",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "burn",
      "cook",
      "on fire",
      "dark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "relay",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "plate",
      "race",
      "desert",
      "snack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "persuasion",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "talent",
      "influence",
      "ripeness",
      "climate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "restate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "decide",
      "discuss",
      "lose",
      "summarize"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gasp",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "breathe",
      "announce",
      "mean",
      "drink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "negotiate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "decide",
      "discuss",
      "fair",
      "ask"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sesame",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "container",
      "food",
      "an animal",
      "shell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "verge",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "edge",
      "done",
      "plan",
      "last"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "benign",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "quick",
      "painful",
      "harmful",
      "warm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dogged",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "working",
      "arrival",
      "flexible",
      "serious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "clarify",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "confuse",
      "clean",
      "do again",
      "order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "waver",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "river",
      "determine",
      "chili",
      "solid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "distress",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "thoughtful",
      "reasonable",
      "peace",
      "surprising"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sip",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "gulp",
      "laugh",
      "provide",
      "keep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "alternate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "divide",
      "move",
      "travel",
      "continue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overdose",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "lack",
      "mixture",
      "teacher",
      "cottage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wary",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "tired",
      "mad",
      "small",
      "trusting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ensue",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "come before",
      "safe",
      "punish",
      "ask about"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What animal can survive ashore?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A dolphin",
      "An alligator",
      "A shark",
      "A goldfish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How can someone devoid of any happiness be described?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Lazy",
      "Content",
      "Depressed",
      "Humorous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "How do turtles elude predators?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "They walk fast.",
      "They hide in their shells.",
      "They have sharp teeth.",
      "They dig a hole in the ground."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is something that people can plunge into?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A school",
      "A car",
      "A cup",
      "A pool"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT used to obstruct sunlight?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Sunglasses",
      "Curtains",
      "A telescope",
      "A baseball cap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Human ",
    "correct": "embryos"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The concert was ",
    "correct": "publicized"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Ms. Hiller had a ",
    "correct": "surplus"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The philosopher ",
    "correct": "theorized"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The principal called Alex\u2019s house to ",
    "correct": "verify"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Margaret collected shells that had come ",
    "correct": "ashore"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Elliot ",
    "correct": "plunged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Oscar hid behind a tree to ",
    "correct": "elude"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The beads in the box were ",
    "correct": "homogenous"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The amount of hair he had on his head was ",
    "correct": "sparse"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prolong",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "show",
      "ensure",
      "extend",
      "destine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fictitious",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "invented",
      "realistic",
      "wonderful",
      "unseen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "contradict",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "move away",
      "disagree",
      "think about",
      "describe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "homogeneous",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "same",
      "weak",
      "unrelated",
      "barred"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vigorous",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "untamed",
      "skilled",
      "qualified",
      "energetic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ate a light snack to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The river ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Sheila ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I viewed this morning\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jason always ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Andrew ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Did you remember to take the hot pan off of the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Class was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Greg didn\u2019t like ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "credible ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "unbelievable ",
      " incorrect ",
      "sly ",
      "unprocessed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "deceased ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "healed ",
      "affected ",
      "young ",
      "alive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ornate ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "unworthy ",
      " simple ",
      "cruel ",
      "blessed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "therapeutic ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "valued ",
      "sickening ",
      "unavailable ",
      "extra"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dusk ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "moon ",
      "sunrise ",
      " eclipse ",
      "month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The journalist checked all her sources to make sure they were ",
    "correct": "credible"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The hospital had a separate section for ",
    "correct": "psychotic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The child\u2019s handwriting was almost impossible to ",
    "correct": "decipher"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The priest stood behind a(n) ",
    "correct": "altar"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her new sweater was colorful and ",
    "correct": "ornate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My dad ",
    "correct": "mashes"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "People with ",
    "correct": "arthritis"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some people think I have ",
    "correct": "psychic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Cows release so much ",
    "correct": "dung"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He didn\u2019t like attending the opera, but he did it to ",
    "correct": "gratify"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hone",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "game",
      "pain",
      "curse",
      "improve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gratify",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "admire",
      "please",
      "approve",
      "layer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mash",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "crush",
      "place",
      "leave",
      "gather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "strife",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "hurt",
      "death",
      "conflict",
      "weakness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sinister",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "evil",
      "futuristic",
      "willful",
      "thoughtless"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "congested",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "normal",
      "crowded",
      "distinct",
      "hostile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "exclusive",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "limited",
      "ancient",
      "inexpensive",
      "unruly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "unsettle",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "bring",
      "intend",
      "increase",
      "worry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "garment",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "clothing",
      "equipment",
      "criticism",
      "unplanned action"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "propel",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "avoid",
      "push",
      "capable",
      "toughen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The meeting of the citizens\u2019 group was ",
    "correct": "suppressed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The warm weather had ",
    "correct": "deformed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Dad says drinking milk before going to bed helps with ",
    "correct": "insomnia"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After I saw the scary movie, walking home in the darkness ",
    "correct": "unsettled"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After school, I\u2019m ",
    "correct": "liable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Dylan believed it to be his ",
    "correct": "privilege"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A gust of wind blew her scarf ",
    "correct": "overboard"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He didn\u2019t know what the proper ",
    "correct": "etiquette"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The train was full of ",
    "correct": "garments"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The wax candle ",
    "correct": "warped"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Allie could always count on her ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The weatherman said it was ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Jared couldn\u2019t stop ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Maxine suffers from ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Walter didn\u2019t know what to wear to the concert. All of his best ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "microbe",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "germ",
      "type",
      "liquid",
      "difficulty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "respiration",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "living",
      "sleeping",
      "breathing",
      "moving"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "artery",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "vein",
      "area",
      "medication",
      "tube"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pest",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "bug",
      "food",
      "toy",
      "victim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "induce",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "take out",
      "cause",
      "stop",
      "chase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "invalid",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hurt",
      "unproven",
      "critical",
      "untrue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rupture",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "burst",
      "reach",
      "sting",
      "bother"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "forage",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "plant",
      "cook",
      "search",
      "hide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "stun",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "shock",
      "injure",
      "threaten",
      "attack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "susceptible",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "helpful",
      "at risk",
      "informative",
      "suffering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The old house was full of ",
    "correct": "pests"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My brother-in-law always tries to ",
    "correct": "magnify"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Mr. Robinson owned a ",
    "correct": "savage"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "If you eat spicy food at night, it will ",
    "correct": "induce"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His ",
    "correct": "arteries"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "impede",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "allow",
      "start",
      "anger",
      "heal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "elusive",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "available",
      "under",
      "venomous",
      "shy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "paralysis",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "illness",
      "mobility",
      "problems",
      "doctor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mainstream",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "uncommon",
      "untested",
      "scientific",
      "wild"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "negligible",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "cared for",
      "reasonable",
      "important",
      "unexpected"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "magnify",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "release",
      "check",
      "save",
      "shrink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prevail",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "conquer",
      "fail",
      "take",
      "feel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "deterioration",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "improvement",
      "back-up",
      "function",
      "loss"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "savage",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "hungry",
      "cruel",
      "gentle",
      "unwilling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inseparable",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "protective",
      "dividable",
      "kind",
      "resigned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "omen",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "sign",
      "storm",
      "accident",
      "item"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "apparatus",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "method",
      "idea",
      "device",
      "name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "convection",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "weather",
      "belief",
      "heat flow",
      "movement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sob",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "watch",
      "serve",
      "wait",
      "cry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "seclude",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "study",
      "repair",
      "hide",
      "purchase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "ranger",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "forest worker",
      "police",
      "lumberjack",
      "guard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "avalanche",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "landslide",
      "snowstorm",
      "disaster",
      "believable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "accumulate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "impressive",
      "winning",
      "collect",
      "wave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rubble",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "boards",
      "dirt",
      "ruins",
      "ice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "upbringing",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "background",
      "routine",
      "schedule",
      "experience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The accident wasn\u2019t serious, and Ernest was ",
    "correct": "discharged"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "My grandfather says that if you have itchy hands, it\u2019s a(n) ",
    "correct": "omen"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The book\u2019s ",
    "correct": "poignant"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The photograph was perfect except for a ",
    "correct": "speck"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The child ",
    "correct": "sobbed"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overcast",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "warm",
      "bright",
      "morning",
      "apparent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "consistency",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "irregularity",
      "delicacy",
      "loyalty",
      "intelligence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "poignant",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "gloomy",
      "supportive",
      "thoughtful",
      "unemotional"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intact",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "alive",
      "broken",
      "aged",
      "tired"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mortal",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "natural",
      "content",
      "deadly",
      "everlasting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "speck",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "huge",
      "fragment",
      "far",
      "clear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sober",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "drunk",
      "caring",
      "calm",
      "ready"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "discharge",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "cure",
      "imprison",
      "pay",
      "arrive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "aerial",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "from ground",
      "technology",
      "emergency",
      "safety"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sideways",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "quickly",
      "forward",
      "again",
      "safely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who is a person with the power to authorize a war?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A teacher",
      "A guard",
      "A chef",
      "A president"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following might give you euphoria?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Winning a great prize",
      "Falling off your bike",
      "Having your jacket stolen",
      "Cutting your finger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What best describes a sage?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Alert",
      "Intelligent",
      "Heavy",
      "Unreliable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is a valuable commodity?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Oil",
      "Mountains",
      "Rainwater",
      "Grass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might cause unrest at a school?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Students receiving lunch for free",
      "Students getting rewarded for good grades",
      "Students having daily tests",
      "Students being told to go home early"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "authorize",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "make easy",
      "reinforce",
      "declare",
      "reject"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "conquest",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "combination",
      "liberation",
      "eliminate",
      "shortage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "disclose",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "conceal",
      "support",
      "dry out",
      "show as guilty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "euphoria",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "measurement",
      "suggestion",
      "depression",
      "untruthfulness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "unrest",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "no planning",
      "peace",
      "early stage",
      "generosity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sage",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "fool",
      "stubborn",
      "gloomy",
      "praiseworthy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "civilian",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "traditionalist",
      "salesman",
      "preacher",
      "soldier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "festive",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "honest",
      "penniless",
      "unhappy",
      "unchanging"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enroll",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "quit",
      "imply",
      "enlist",
      "make better"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "advocate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "fallen",
      "sinner",
      "antisocial",
      "oppose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lentil",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "prize",
      "bean",
      "nut",
      "coin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "envious",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "awkward",
      "sensible",
      "jealous",
      "cowardly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "commodity",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "product",
      "inactivity",
      "genius",
      "act of scolding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dynamics",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "angry speech",
      "edge of",
      "aspects",
      "enthusiasm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prophecy",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "comes before",
      "prediction",
      "true story",
      "large amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "morale",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "goodness",
      "confidence",
      "sympathy",
      "temperature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "marshal",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "assemble",
      "promise",
      "attempt",
      "contain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "jolly",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "inspiring",
      "appealing",
      "merry",
      "rational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "senate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "nice feeling",
      "aspiration",
      "school",
      "government"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sentiment",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "confidence",
      "effort",
      "acceptance",
      "opinion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Janice\u2019s dad was a part of the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Damon read about the Roman ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The teacher understood the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Mariah ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Sheldon was a vegetarian. He ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reckless",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "impressive",
      "careless",
      "fake",
      "colorful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "flaw",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "loss",
      "injury",
      "mistake",
      "relative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "farewell",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "goodbye",
      "maybe",
      "instead",
      "with luck"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "filth",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ice",
      "dirt",
      "tear",
      "track"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "bliss",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "boldness",
      "comfort",
      "greatness",
      "happiness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "mound"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Please call for the ",
    "correct": "butler"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I don\u2019t think we have enough ",
    "correct": "timber"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The playful puppy made the baby ",
    "correct": "grin"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We\u2019ll have to install a new ",
    "correct": "valve"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I got a ",
    "correct": "cramp"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "To reach the TV, the young girl stood on the ",
    "correct": "stool"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A high examination score is a ",
    "correct": "testament"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The man became worried when his arm was ",
    "correct": "numb"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He was hired to repair the house that had become ",
    "correct": "dilapidated"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The scientist\u2019s theory was full of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I hope we do not have to say ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The teacher was proud of the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After the initial pain of droppingthe hammer on my toe, it went ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He was not looking forward to cleaning the huge ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The scared child felt ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Huge stained-glass windows ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Fossil evidence is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The girl\u2019s jump rope has a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The weather report says ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My entire family helps with ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The mother ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He took off his shoes and leaned back into the comfortable ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Adjust the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The movie was great because it ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You can get hot or cold water from this ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "federation",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "motion",
      "union",
      "suction",
      "tension"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "render",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "stop",
      "tear",
      "rent",
      "make"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "smallpox",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "disease",
      "match",
      "arrive",
      "hide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "curb",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "drain",
      "excuse",
      "prevent",
      "breathe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "diagnose",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "smell",
      "continue",
      "extend",
      "identify"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "certify",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "apply",
      "reduce",
      "confirm",
      "listen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "rash",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "pants",
      "bumps",
      "lists",
      "pies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "needy",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "poor",
      "sweet",
      "moist",
      "short"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "onset",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "fork",
      "show",
      "light",
      "start"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "collaborate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "cooperate",
      "estimate",
      "understand",
      "determine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enact ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "open ",
      "travel ",
      "cancel ",
      "recline "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intolerable ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "chewable ",
      "washable ",
      "bearable ",
      "honorable "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pledge ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "lie ",
      "write ",
      "throw ",
      "fall "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "counteract ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "pretend ",
      "arrange ",
      "support ",
      "repair "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vow ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "command ",
      "gather ",
      "elect ",
      "deceive "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prohibit ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "examine ",
      "undo ",
      "allow ",
      "chew "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "transmit ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "ride ",
      "hold ",
      "dig ",
      "burn "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gross ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "little ",
      "similar ",
      "powerful ",
      "pretty "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "compile ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "tower ",
      "scatter ",
      "mound ",
      "dinner "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "humane ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "hairy ",
      "kind ",
      "close ",
      "cruel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The new law will ",
    "correct": "render"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some countries have a larger population of ",
    "correct": "needy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teachers ",
    "correct": "compiled"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "If you touch that plant, you might get a ",
    "correct": "rash"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The doctor ",
    "correct": "diagnosed"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I don\u2019t like those kinds of movies because they have scenes that are really ",
    "correct": "gross"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Many diseases are ",
    "correct": "transmitted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The companies agreed that it would be cheaper to ship the fruit if they formed a ",
    "correct": "federation"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her treatment of the patients was ",
    "correct": "humane"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The two artists decided to ",
    "correct": "collaborate"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "paw",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "foot",
      "fort",
      "fashion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cot",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "chamber",
      "bed",
      "fabric",
      "hut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "camouflage",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "disguise",
      "funny",
      "tired",
      "scared"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lush",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "shelf",
      "poem",
      "weather",
      "green"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "substantial",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "backward",
      "majestic",
      "large",
      "comfortable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "contend",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "give up",
      "ready",
      "quick",
      "ugly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "substantial",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "bright",
      "runny",
      "small",
      "handsome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hesitant",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "visible",
      "certain",
      "colorful",
      "broken"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "splendid",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "night",
      "whale",
      "terrible",
      "skin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "enlist",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "resign",
      "erase",
      "boil",
      "increase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I am so ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The pages in the book were ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Bill was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You can tell that the bones are old because they don\u2019t have any ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I have five siblings. We often ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After the meal, Father ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Mountains divide the northern ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He parked the car in the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I installed a new ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I had to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What can start an epidemic?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A kingdom",
      "A virus",
      "Afire",
      "A storm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is found inside intestines?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Books",
      "Students",
      "Food",
      "Electronics"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you replenish an empty refrigerator, you ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "turn the temperature down",
      "fill it with food",
      "clean it with a sponge",
      "replace the light bulb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a hazard on a street?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A stop sign",
      "A hole in the ground",
      "A carpool lane",
      "A crosswalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What can contaminate the air?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A poison",
      "A flower",
      "A mosquito",
      "A flag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is the most serious to have a deficiency of?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Addresses",
      "Vitamins",
      "Pencils"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What process is metabolic?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Sitting quietly",
      "Learning to spell",
      "Sleeping",
      "Digesting food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is paramount when swimming underwater?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Not getting wet",
      "Holding your breath",
      "Breathing regularly",
      "Stretching your limbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What needs to be sterile?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A hospital room",
      "An ocean",
      "A bicycle rack",
      "The soil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a practitioner do?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Make furniture",
      "Fight crime",
      "Make laws",
      "Treat the sick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "voluntary",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "heavy",
      "required",
      "obvious",
      "nonexistent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "imperative",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "unimportant",
      "faulty",
      "mastered",
      "chosen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "compassionate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "likely",
      "distant",
      "afraid",
      "uncaring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sterile",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "not fair",
      "not clean",
      "not free",
      "not working"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overcrowded",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "empty",
      "costly",
      "silly",
      "bland"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "They need to ",
    "correct": "upgrade"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "To save the boy, rushing into the burning house is ",
    "correct": "imperative"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Handing out rain jackets was a necessary ",
    "correct": "provision"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Sometimes, cold weather can ",
    "correct": "manifest"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The theory seems ",
    "correct": "viable"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "You must ",
    "correct": "adhere"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Joining the choir will be ",
    "correct": "voluntary"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The amusement park was no fun because it was ",
    "correct": "overcrowded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Who is going to ",
    "correct": "administer"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The criminal was certainly not ",
    "correct": "compassionate"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "culprit",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "sewer",
      "engine",
      "victim",
      "muscle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "segregate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "defend",
      "whisper",
      "combine",
      "improve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "uproar",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "calm",
      "particle",
      "jewels",
      "substance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "clumsy",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "helpful",
      "quick",
      "healthy",
      "graceful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "premature",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "smart",
      "late",
      "near",
      "great"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mob",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "broom",
      "crowd",
      "gun",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tumult",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "plan",
      "gate",
      "tent",
      "noise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "brute",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "monster",
      "camera",
      "smell",
      "temper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "resent",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "buy",
      "lose",
      "give",
      "hate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "scrutiny",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "tower",
      "part",
      "study",
      "dream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "testify",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "learn",
      "solve",
      "greet",
      "declare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "collide",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "sing",
      "crash",
      "float",
      "bake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "subject",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "force",
      "show",
      "sleep",
      "teach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "evacuate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "leave",
      "suck",
      "check",
      "share"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "satire",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "supper",
      "promise",
      "coffin",
      "comedy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We had very little time to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The guards sometimes ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Some people like to watch action movies. But I enjoy a good ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ When we heard the phone ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We whispered very quietly in all the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The women loved the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My brother was one of the angry people in the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Her father had to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I tried to solve the math problem several times and finally ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He has several large homes and his own airplane because he\u2019s a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "defect",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "perfect",
      "broken",
      "clean",
      "magical"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "innovation",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "obsolete",
      "cunning",
      "original",
      "compatible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "accelerate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "speed up",
      "slow down",
      "open",
      "melt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "meteorological",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "weather",
      "past",
      "body",
      "mind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dreary",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "bright",
      "fluorescent",
      "frigid",
      "dull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "You can hear because sound ",
    "correct": "stimulates"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Some worms are small enough to ",
    "correct": "penetrate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She tried to ",
    "correct": "duplicate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teacher offered the kids candy in order to ",
    "correct": "spur"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "In science class, we learned about ",
    "correct": "electrons"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Every time the children\u2019s fort fell down, they built it ",
    "correct": "anew"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She took classes in ",
    "correct": "meteorology"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The small airplane ",
    "correct": "glided"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A rocket requires a lot of fuel in order to ",
    "correct": "launch"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Amanda is quite an ",
    "correct": "ingenious"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Just when you thought you\u2019d caught up to Brian, he\u2019d ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The orchestra made a very ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Dan had ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Lions are dangerous hunters. They can ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ They had a picnic in the park and ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We made a small toy train that ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Cellular phones are one of the most popular ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The knight\u2019s sword could not ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The thought of his warm bed ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We didn\u2019t mind that our paintings got ruined. It was fun to start them ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Satellites are very important for gathering ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Fish use their fins for ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I wish Dad wasn\u2019t so ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Some metals are attracted to other metals due to an ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Certain kinds of light can ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ John is so ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I\u2019ve always been interested in meteors. That\u2019s why I want to study ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The lake was frightening. The water was still and ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Everyone who voted in the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The new pot looked perfect. It was covered in new, shiny ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who is someone that would most likely be hospitable?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "An enemy",
      "A host",
      "A singer",
      "A gangster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "At what temperature centigrade does water freeze?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "0 degrees",
      "32 degrees",
      "100 degrees",
      "132 degrees"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If the mist from fog condensed, what would happen to the ground?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "It would be wet.",
      "It would be dry.",
      "It would be sandy.",
      "It would be snowy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you are going on a trip, which is something you should do beforehand?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Exercise",
      "Take a walk",
      "Throw a party",
      "Pack clothes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who of the following would most likely perform a concerto?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A musician",
      "A pilot",
      "A swimmer",
      "A superhero"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "monastery",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "stairs",
      "currency",
      "abbey",
      "frown"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "winding",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "spiral",
      "stormy",
      "broken",
      "tiny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cove",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "tomb",
      "oven",
      "term",
      "bay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "freeway",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "road",
      "path",
      "slow",
      "farther"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "manor",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "polite",
      "hut",
      "large home",
      "field"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "parcel",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "landscape",
      "package",
      "battery",
      "moisture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nursery",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "auditorium",
      "nurse\u2019s lounge",
      "hospital",
      "infant\u2019s center"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vivacious",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "angry",
      "quiet",
      "cheerful",
      "tired"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "exterior",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "priest",
      "region",
      "bridge",
      "outside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "zip",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "close",
      "toss",
      "join",
      "walk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "They didn\u2019t want to get covered with sand, so they relaxed on an ",
    "correct": "outstretched"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boys were ",
    "correct": "chattering"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It\u2019s easy to go past the exit when you\u2019re driving on the ",
    "correct": "freeway"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "This building used to be a ",
    "correct": "monastery"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "winding"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The photograph showed ",
    "correct": "profile"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Their chances of escaping the room ",
    "correct": "deteriorated"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "exterior"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Lisa is a very ",
    "correct": "hearty"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019ll remember her forever. I had never before met such a ",
    "correct": "vivacious"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lunar",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "sun",
      "moon",
      "stars",
      "earth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reflex",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "response",
      "delay",
      "broken",
      "squeeze"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pertain",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "piece",
      "fact",
      "describe",
      "relate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "utensil",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "horn",
      "badge",
      "spoon",
      "glove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outmoded",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "old-fashioned",
      "new",
      "outdoors",
      "innovative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inhale",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "breathe",
      "exit",
      "sell",
      "borrow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "psychiatric",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "passionate",
      "cozy",
      "mental",
      "similar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "advent",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "start",
      "moment",
      "candle",
      "pipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "equate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "prepare",
      "drip",
      "sleep",
      "relate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "session",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "ocean",
      "sweater",
      "rubbish",
      "meeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "invoke",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "allow",
      "resist",
      "request",
      "divide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Almighty",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "fire",
      "capital",
      "god",
      "tower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "primal",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "basic",
      "bright",
      "wooden",
      "strict"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "airway",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "cloud",
      "throat",
      "road",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outmoded",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "wild",
      "whole",
      "dumb",
      "old"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The coach ",
    "correct": "personalized"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Jack\u2019s parents had a weekly ",
    "correct": "session"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "If you look at that ",
    "correct": "constellation"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The priest asked the ",
    "correct": "Almighty"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She ",
    "correct": "equated"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "reverse ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "spell ",
      "train ",
      "switch ",
      "camp "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "adverse ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "written ",
      "harmful ",
      "tense ",
      " blank "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "intermediate ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "amazing ",
      " safe ",
      "stupid ",
      "middle "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "regain ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "reclaim ",
      "book ",
      "member ",
      " length "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mentor ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "flavor ",
      "terror ",
      "teacher ",
      "painter "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inclusion ",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "energy ",
      "moment ",
      " peninsula ",
      "welcome "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "adhesive ",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "paste ",
      "floor ",
      "segment ",
      "treasure "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vibrant ",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "dangerous ",
      "messy ",
      "dynamic ",
      "hollow "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dependency ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "expanse ",
      "need ",
      "freshness ",
      "tone "
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "swarm ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "heat ",
      " group ",
      "truth ",
      " ledge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "inclusion",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "exclusion",
      "inside",
      "instant",
      "unclean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "regain",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "snow",
      "break",
      "lose",
      "smell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "eternal",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "great",
      "true",
      "flat",
      "brief"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "dump",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "gather",
      "explain",
      "solve",
      "glow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "fluctuate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "heal",
      "remain",
      "stutter",
      "choose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The branches moved to and ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Honeybees collect ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The meeting was ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ In order to get into the sports arena, we had to pay a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This past week the weather has ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Don\u2019t touch my knee. It ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ She ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ My level of Spanish is only at the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might be abolished?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A rule",
      "A toy",
      "A car",
      "A star"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who tackles crime?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Bankers",
      "Criminals",
      "Postal workers",
      "Police officers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who is infamous?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A trusting friend",
      "An evil king",
      "A tiny puppy",
      "A newborn baby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If a behavior is pathological, it ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "is envied",
      "cannot be controlled",
      "can be bad",
      "is pleasant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who might be lame?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "A healthy baby",
      "An athlete",
      "A young man",
      "Someone in a wheelchair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "A trance is most similar to ______.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "dancing",
      "eating",
      "showering",
      "sleeping"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is most likely to have a charter?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "An unknown island",
      "A new automobile",
      "A large company",
      "A basketball"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What might be censored?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A newspaper",
      "A fly",
      "A cruise",
      "Cell phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If your skills are phenomenal, they are ______.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "ordinary",
      "not appreciated",
      "in need of practice",
      "great"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which area is likely to be cosmopolitan?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A television set",
      "A bedroom",
      "A big city",
      "A small village"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "lame",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "rude",
      "kind",
      "smart",
      "healthy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "secrecy",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "well known",
      "hidden",
      "upset",
      "popularity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "abolish",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "great",
      "start",
      "round",
      "caring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "remorse",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "again",
      "grief",
      "happiness",
      "glow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "disseminate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "distribute",
      "collect",
      "open",
      "forget"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His moving speech caused a huge ",
    "correct": "outburst"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The main goal of the group was to ",
    "correct": "disseminate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The wounded soldier had to ",
    "correct": "limp"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We excitedly watched the results of the ",
    "correct": "poll"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boys ",
    "correct": "aspire"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When he saw how badly things had turned out, he felt ",
    "correct": "remorse"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It is a difficult process to ",
    "correct": "amend"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Those salesmen ",
    "correct": "flatter"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "constitution"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We were immediately suspicious of the boy because of his ",
    "correct": "secrecy"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Many different languages are spoken in this ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The doctor had to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The new country created a strong ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "No matter how much she begged, the older girls still ",
    "correct": "excluded"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Language based",
    "correct": "Linguistic"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Constant changes were ",
    "correct": "undermining"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boy made a ",
    "correct": "solemn"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The movie director gave the actors and actresses a ",
    "correct": "firsthand"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Everyone knew that Luke studied Chinese. But no one knew he was ",
    "correct": "fluent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The teacher was waiting for one of the students to be ",
    "correct": "earnest"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The Internet has made talking to people everywhere very natural. As a result, having a sense of ",
    "correct": "solidarity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Though he looked Greek, ",
    "correct": "nationality"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Today, no one lives in the old ",
    "correct": "imperial"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Peter is so ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If you like ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Though it\u2019s the same language, there are ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If you want someone to care for your cattle, you should call a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy said that the test was unfair, and his classmates showed ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The king said the princes had ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ \u201c I\u2019m sorry you can\u2019t eat here. This restaurant is ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The road going to the farmhouse is ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He had seen the battle ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If someone goes to court, then they are judged by the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This city\u2019s history is important. It was once the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ His friends had left him alone in the library, but he didn\u2019t mind being ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The criminals were ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ That college ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Many people wonder about her ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The mothers covered their children\u2019s heads because the rain was so ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I liked all the cars, but I bought the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ His method had a lot of ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "frigid",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "happy",
      "hot",
      "open",
      "clear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "wavy",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "straight",
      "pretty",
      "likely",
      "quick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "crisp",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "more",
      "slow",
      "nice",
      "soft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "replicate",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "flight",
      "original",
      "friend",
      "agreement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "allocate",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "take away",
      "freeze",
      "close",
      "fight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "No one else can open my ",
    "correct": "locker"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "How can we prevent ",
    "correct": "discord"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The brave travelers were not stopped by the ",
    "correct": "blizzard"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The organizers made sure that the parade was ",
    "correct": "multicultural"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The thief hid the money in a small ",
    "correct": "cavity"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I thought the hosts showed a lot of ",
    "correct": "courtesy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It was her job to ",
    "correct": "oversee"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "What can we do to ",
    "correct": "generate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "People cannot withstand ",
    "correct": "frigid"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "John used a knife to ",
    "correct": "pierce"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This is a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The valuables are kept in a secure ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ If things move ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The doctor ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The scientist tried to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ School was cancelled today because of the horrible ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After a brief ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Make sure to include an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The charity raised money for all of the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Tim was chosen to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We need to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He was not pleased with the movie. He thought it was too ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The brothers cannot work together. There is always ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The mother was disappointed with the extreme ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Seats will be ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is needed to subsist?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Rainy weather",
      "Clean water",
      "Fast cars",
      "The Internet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is someone penalized for?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Falling in love",
      "Winning a race",
      "An invention",
      "Breaking the law"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What does a business owner justify?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Her house",
      "Her decision",
      "Her workers",
      "Her family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which one of these uses a product made from petroleum?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A sandwich",
      "A telephone",
      "An automobile",
      "A cow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What releases fumes?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "An old truck",
      "A baby cat",
      "A tired worker",
      "A bicycle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The best theory was the one that was a ",
    "correct": "synthesis"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "When the power went out, he was forced to ",
    "correct": "suspend"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The brothers ",
    "correct": "subscribe"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The cutting tool was just a ",
    "correct": "prototype"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Her job was to get all of the goods ready to ",
    "correct": "export"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The chemist demonstrated the ",
    "correct": "conversion"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After the tornado, it was difficult for the family to ",
    "correct": "subsist"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The mechanic yelled when he stepped on the sharp ",
    "correct": "scrap"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It is the policeman\u2019s job to make sure people ",
    "correct": "abide"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We\u2019ll have to ",
    "correct": "defer"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The big city worked hard to prevent ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I tried to ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The machine\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Why don\u2019t we ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "veteran",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wet",
      "amateur",
      "young",
      "vague"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "harmonize",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "exaggerate",
      "disagree",
      "lessen",
      "mark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "misguided",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "lost",
      "lengthy",
      "common",
      "well-planned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "villain",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "supporter",
      "thief",
      "hero",
      "loud person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "scorn",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "respect",
      "weird",
      "delicate",
      "factory-related"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The animal rights ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He was well-liked by people in his class. A lot of people ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Going on a rollercoaster is a wild ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Items like sunscreen, towel and bathing suit are ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The hotel had a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The audience ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Chris\u2019s actions were ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The people of the small town were very ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Kayla watched the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The singers ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After his shoelaces tore, the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Mrs. Campbell\u2019s son was lazy and ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I\u2019m interested in getting a job as a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Some insects ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Long ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I\u2019m glad our teacher is so ",
    "correct": "tolerant"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Chewing gum creates a lot of ",
    "correct": "saliva"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She had to ",
    "correct": "restrain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Let\u2019s see who can ",
    "correct": "sprint"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Lots of people try to ",
    "correct": "emulate"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ache is coming deep from within her ",
    "correct": "guts"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Please take a ",
    "correct": "moist"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She wore a ring on her ",
    "correct": "forefinger"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "A lack of money might ",
    "correct": "constrain"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His answer is always an informal way of saving no.",
    "correct": "nope"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "prod",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "eat",
      "push",
      "speak",
      "believe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "nope",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "no",
      "free",
      "brave",
      "alive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "sprint",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "crave",
      "drive",
      "run",
      "pretend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "emulate",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "annoy",
      "proceed",
      "fear",
      "imitate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "vampire",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "car",
      "monster",
      "feather",
      "trait"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ After walking through the desert, the thirsty man had no ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ We\u2019ve been waiting at the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The joke was so funny that it made him ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I hope I don\u2019t have to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The boy\u2019s dream was to ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ He is usually a very calm person. His anger today was just an ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The evil man expected a large ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The rotten meal gave me a terrible pain in my ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ No one was impressed with Bobby\u2019s ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Using his ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Take plenty of water with you before you begin the journey across the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you invert a bottle, you ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "drink from it",
      "wash it with soap",
      "turn it upside down",
      "drop it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following would most likely require the use of a funnel?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "Snow",
      "Books",
      "Carrots",
      "Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is a wolfs prey?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "Its pups",
      "Its den",
      "Its food",
      "Its ally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which is hereditary?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Place of birth",
      "Eye color",
      "Favorite foods",
      "Hobbies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If something is fragrant, you ______.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "like to smell it",
      "want to eat it",
      "try to end it",
      "want to sing it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Who uses seasoning at work?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A teacher",
      "A chef",
      "A builder",
      "An electrician"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following describes a kind of deputy?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A supervisor",
      "A CEO",
      "A vice president",
      "A Manager"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is made from sodium?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Furniture",
      "Salts",
      "Toys",
      "Soda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you most likely hear a hymn?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "At work",
      "Under water",
      "At the zoo",
      "In a church"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If your brother is sarcastic, he ______.",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "wants to hit you",
      "insults you",
      "betrays you",
      "is ill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He liked to pour the ",
    "correct": "vinegar"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "To better explain the procedure, he used a great ",
    "correct": "analogy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "We were in awe of the performance of the skilled ",
    "correct": "archer"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The war was a means to overthrow the ",
    "correct": "tyranny"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I have a feeling that the robbery was a ",
    "correct": "conspiracy"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "At the library, we learned how to trace our ",
    "correct": "ancestry"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The people were convinced that the strange visitor was a ",
    "correct": "prophet"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The father acted like a ",
    "correct": "tyrant"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "earl"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The new mayor\u2019s first priority was to select a ",
    "correct": "deputy"
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The mechanic used a ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Because of the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ I think the addition of more ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hectare",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "violence",
      "10,000m2",
      "temple",
      "caven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "terrace",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "festival",
      "temper",
      "video",
      "patio"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "casualty",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "victim",
      "effect",
      "decision",
      "perfume"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "allege",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "reverse",
      "accuse",
      "assist",
      "digest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "renovate",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "refer",
      "apply",
      "repair",
      "compute"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "outnumber",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "count",
      "share",
      "exceed",
      "borrow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "adjoining",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "talking",
      "reflective",
      "adjacent",
      "absolute"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "revise",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "cover",
      "detest",
      "plea",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "arch",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "color",
      "feeling",
      "gift",
      "curve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "petition",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "request",
      "license",
      "animal",
      "station"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pasture",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "marsh",
      "scream",
      "future",
      "stance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "foul",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "meaningful",
      "dangerous",
      "pleasant",
      "muscular"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "slab",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "office",
      "freedom",
      "spit",
      "pebble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "assemble",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "believe",
      "scatter",
      "repeat",
      "obey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "overjoyed",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "stinky",
      "hidden",
      "expensive",
      "miserable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "turf",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "ocean",
      "name",
      "effort",
      "sport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "erect",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "approve",
      "destroy",
      "donate",
      "contain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "heighten",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "balance",
      "pretend",
      "elect",
      "reduce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "mansion",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "pencil",
      "shack",
      "female",
      "blouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "hospitality",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "medicine",
      "style",
      "unfriendliness",
      "silence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Once the weather was ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The scientists worked all day in then ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The amount of cows ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Why don\u2019t you connect those two large blue ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The worse ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The two enemies ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ Whenever Doug was in a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The glass was filled with a ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This is the kitchen, and the ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The visit lacked in ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ You can stay in the house tonight, but your dog has to sleep outside in the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ William ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The grandmother was ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ This room here is the ",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "type": "yes_no",
    "question": "______ The manager read his employees\u2019 ",
    "correct": true
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Binoculars help you to see things that are ______.",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "close by ",
      "under the sea ",
      "far away ",
      "covered in mud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "If you have dual responsibilities, then you have ______ things to take care of.",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "two ",
      "three ",
      "ten ",
      "twelve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is about the same as a tariff? ",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "A salary ",
      "A tax ",
      "A surplus ",
      "A bonus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where would you most likely see a pier?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "In the water ",
      "On a plane ",
      "Under the ground ",
      "On a road"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Fahrenheit is used to measure ______.",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "height ",
      "distance ",
      "weight ",
      "temperature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "comprise",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "return",
      "consist",
      "explain",
      "favor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "tilt",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "mix",
      "dig",
      "lean",
      "grip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "pier",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "dock",
      "cake",
      "chef",
      "fort"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "analogous",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "metric",
      "powerful",
      "secure",
      "similar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "paradox",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "illogical",
      "cattle",
      "calendar",
      "feather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "These mines produce several types of valuable ",
    "correct": "ore"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The company had to pay a ",
    "correct": "tariff"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She used the ",
    "correct": "binoculars"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The painting ",
    "correct": "depicted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "He had sent a letter from the city three days earlier. But his precise ",
    "correct": "whereabouts"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The ",
    "correct": "dual"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The meal was ",
    "correct": "comprised"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "If you\u2019re sick, take your temperature. The ",
    "correct": "thermometer"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "His promotion was a ",
    "correct": "paradox"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "It was difficult to lift the ",
    "correct": "bulk"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Where does a columnist work?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "At a university",
      "At a newspaper",
      "At a restaurant",
      "At an airport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of the following might a liberal person do?",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "Restrict freedoms",
      "Learn new ideas",
      "Reject free speech",
      "Support tyranny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What animal pecks?",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "A bee",
      "A cat",
      "A bird",
      "A tiger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "What is stored in a reservoir?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "Water",
      "Food",
      "Books",
      "Tools"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "Which of these animals have a long streak on their bodies?",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "A skunk",
      "A horse",
      "A rhino",
      "A gorilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "After seeing her house on fire, Jenna was ",
    "correct": "haunted"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The boy had ",
    "correct": "pebbles"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The bird ",
    "correct": "pecked"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The city made a ",
    "correct": "reservoir"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "She poured ",
    "correct": "detergent"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The woman was impressed by her friend\u2019s ",
    "correct": "courteous"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The scientist went to school for many years to earn her ",
    "correct": "credentials"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "I added some more ",
    "correct": "charcoal"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "Clara didn\u2019t want to offend her grandmother, so she used a ",
    "correct": "euphemism"
  },
  {
    "type": "similar",
    "question": "The land in the ",
    "correct": "delta"
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "columnist",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "singer",
      "journalist",
      "electrician",
      "CEO"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "cricket",
    "correct": "0",
    "options": [
      "grasshopper",
      "beetle",
      "ant",
      "mosquito"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "maze",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": [
      "disguise",
      "hoop",
      "tower",
      "puzzle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "gravel",
    "correct": "1",
    "options": [
      "boulder",
      "rock",
      "hill",
      "mound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "single_choice",
    "question": "haunt",
    "correct": "2",
    "options": [
      "calm",
      "play",
      "terrorize",
      "soothe"
    ]
  }
]